<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <link>http://www.gopconvention2012.com/media-portal/speakers/</link>
	<title>Craig Romney</title>
	<description>Craig Romney
(Remarks as Prepared for Delivery)
</description>

<item>
	<title>I am honored and humbled to speak with you tonight. I am incredibly proud of my father, and love him dearly. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line1</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>It is my privilege to say a few words in Spanish, so please bear with me for a moment. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line2</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Buenas Noches. Es un placer estar con ustedes. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line3</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Yo pase dos años viviendo y trabajando en Chile. A través de esa experiencia, pude valorar aún mas como hispanos han aportado a la diversa riqueza de los Estados Unidos. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line4</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mi padre ­ Mitt Romney ­ es un hombre de familia. Él es un gran esposo, padre y abuelo. Él sabe como unir a nuestro país y valora que somos una nación de inmigrantes, unidos en el deseo de lograr el sueno americano. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line5</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>El ama a nuestra nación. El luchará para confrontar los retos que tenemos y restaurar la grandeza de los Estados Unidos. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line6</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>It's easy to forget that the story of my father's success begins with the story of two immigrants ­ my grandfathers ­ who came to this country with little more than hope in the opportunity of America. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line7</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Through their hard work and perseverance they lived the American dream, and gave opportunities to their children they wouldn't have had anywhere else. The Republican Party is dedicated to preserving that opportunity for all Americans. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line8</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We've had the privilege of hearing about different chapters of this same inspiring American story from Governors Sandoval and Martinez and soon-to-be-Senator Cruz. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line9</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We're seeing this story play out in the lives of many other Hispanic Americans who have become leaders in the Republican Party and throughout our nation. These leaders, along with Hispanics across the country, will play a vital role in the Romney- Ryan comeback, as we fight to put America back on the path to prosperity. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line10</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thank you. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line11</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>                                               ### </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Craig-Romney-Thursday-Final.html#line12</link>
	<author>Craig Romney</author>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
