<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <link>http://www.gopconvention2012.com/media-portal/speakers/</link>
	<title>Keith Rothfus</title>
	<description>Keith Rothfus
Republican Candidate for Congress, 12th District of Pennsylvania
(Remarks as Prepared for Delivery)
</description>

<item>
	<title>Good afternoon. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line1</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We've heard, and will continue to hear, a great deal about health care and Medicare in this election -- and that's a good thing. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line2</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>As a cancer survivor, no issue is more personal to me than health care and the strength of our doctor-patient relationships. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line3</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Having developed and survived a very rare form of cancer that kills 75 percent of its victims within five years, I know all too well the importance of a health care system that empowers the doctor-patient relationship and respects the decisions of the family. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line4</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>There is no greater threat to the health care of our nation and the health care of our seniors than Obamacare. No matter what path we take to save Medicare, the very first step is to repeal Obamacare. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line5</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>My district, Pennsylvania-12, has one of the largest Medicare populations in the entire country. My opponent, Congressman Critz, voted over 20 times to support Obamacare, including voting against repeal of the Independent Payment Advisory Board, which empowers not doctors and patients, but bureaucrats in Washington, D.C. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line6</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>There is only one ticket that will defend patients, defend doctors and defend families in this health care battle. There is only one ticket that will save Medicare from bankruptcy, preserve Medicare for today's seniors and strengthen Medicare for the future. To repeal, to replace, to restore ­ choose Romney, Ryan and Rothfus. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line7</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thank you and God bless America. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line8</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>                                             ### </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Keith-Rothfus-1.html#line9</link>
	<author>Keith Rothfus</author>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
