<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <link>http://www.gopconvention2012.com/media-portal/speakers/</link>
	<title>Jeanine McDonnell</title>
	<description>Jeanine McDonnell
Iraq War Veteran
and
Chris Devlin-Young
Para-Olympian
(Remarks as Prepared for Delivery)
</description>

<item>
	<title>Jeanine McDonnell: </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line1</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Good evening, I am proud to be one of the 212,000 servicewomen who have served in Iraq and Afghanistan over the past decade. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line2</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>As a 24 year old Virginian in Iraq, I worked with some of the most courageous men and women this nation has to offer, and we were united in a singular cause: to protect the nation that we love. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line3</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>It has been my privilege to serve alongside heroes of every service. Defending this nation and its citizens is not without sacrifice for service members and the families who support them. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line4</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>And that's why we need leaders who don't play chicken with our nation's defense. We need leaders who will invest in defense--not abandon it. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line5</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>And that's why we need Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line6</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Now, it is my honor to introduce Chris Devlin-Young, a hero in his own right, a former Coast Guardsman and a two-time Paralympic gold medalist in alpine skiing. Chris. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line7</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Chris Devlin-Young: </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line8</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thank you. It's wonderful to be with you tonight. In 1982, while flying in heavy fog during a Coast Guard mission, our plane crashed, leaving me paralyzed from the waist down. While my career as a Coast Guardsman ended, a new world of service began for me. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line9</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>27 years ago, this California boy was introduced to ski racing at the first Veterans Administration Winter Sports clinic. I decided then and there to dedicate myself to racing and coaching other injured veterans. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line10</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Being a gold medal Paralympian gives me a whole new way to honor and serve my country. Being the coach of paralympic medalists gives me a way to honor and serve others. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line11</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>I believe that we can all serve no matter what our challenges. Because it's not about what you've lost in life but rather what you are able to give. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line12</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>And now, it is my honor to introduce a hero who has given of himself regardless of the price. He is the son and grandson of admirals, a decorated naval pilot, a war hero, and the senior senator from the great state of Arizona -- Senator John McCain. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line13</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>                                               ### </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/McDonnell-Young-Wednesday-FINAL2.html#line14</link>
	<author>Jeanine McDonnell</author>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
