<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <link>http://www.gopconvention2012.com/media-portal/speakers/</link>
	<title>Pam Finlayson</title>
	<description>Pam Finlayson
(Remarks as Prepared for Delivery)
</description>

<item>
	<title>In 1982, my husband Grant and I moved from California to Massachusetts, with our newborn son. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line1</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Being a church-going family, we looked for the nearest chapel and soon found ourselves in a congregation led by a clearly bright and capable man, named Mitt Romney. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line2</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>I knew Mitt was special from the start. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line3</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We didn't own a dryer, and the day he stopped by to welcome us, I was embarrassed to have laundry hanging all over the house. Mitt wasn't fazed. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line4</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>In fact, as we spoke, without a word, he joined me and started helpfully plucking clothes from around the room and folding them. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line5</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>By the time Mitt left, not only did I feel welcome, my laundry was done! </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line6</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>As Grant and I juggled school, jobs, church and family, we grew to love the Romneys. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line7</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>They became role-models and friends, and we were honored when Mitt and Ann regularly trusted us to stay with their five rambunctious - but very loving - sons when they traveled. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line8</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>It was when our daughter Kate was born three and a half months early that I fully came to appreciate what a great treasure of friendship we had in Mitt and Ann. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line9</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Kate was so tiny and very sick. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line10</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Her lungs not yet ready to breathe, her heart unstable, and after suffering a severe brain hemorrhage at three days old, she was teetering on the very edge of life. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line11</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>As I sat with her in intensive care, consumed with a mother's worry and fear, dear Mitt came to visit and pray with me. As our clergy, he was one of few visitors allowed. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line12</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>I will never forget that when he looked down tenderly at my daughter, his eyes filled with tears, and he reached out gently and stroked her tiny back. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line13</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>I could tell immediately that he didn't just see a tangle of plastic and tubes; he saw our beautiful little girl, and he was clearly overcome with compassion for her. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line14</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>During the many months Kate was hospitalized, the Romneys often cared for our two-year old son, Peter. They treated him like one of their own, even welcoming him to stay the night when needed. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line15</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>When Thanksgiving rolled around, Kate was still struggling for life. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line16</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Brain surgery was scheduled, and the holiday was the furthest thing from our minds. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line17</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>I opened my door to find Mitt and his boys, arms loaded with a Thanksgiving feast. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line18</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Of course we were overcome. When I called to thank Ann, she sweetly confessed it had been Mitt's idea, that most of the cooking and chopping had been done by him. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line19</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>She and the boys had just happily pitched in. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line20</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Eventually we moved from Boston. Our daughter Kate grew into an amazing girl of faith and love. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line21</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>But complications of her birth remained with her, and after 26 years of both miracles and struggle, she passed away just a year and a half ago. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line22</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>In the midst of making the final decision to run for President ­ which had to be the most difficult of their lives ­ when they heard of Kate's passing, both Mitt and Ann paused, to personally reach out to extend us sympathy, and express their love. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line23</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>It seems to me when it comes to loving our neighbor, we can talk about it, or we can live it. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line24</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>The Romney's live it every single day. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line25</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>When the world looks at Mitt Romney, they see him as the founder of a successful business, the leader of the Olympics, or a Governor. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line26</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>When I see Mitt, I know him to be a loving father, man of faith and caring and compassionate friend. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line27</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>It is with great excitement and a renewed hope, to know that our country will be blessed as it is led by a man who is not only so accomplished and capable, but who has devoted his entire life quietly serving others. That man is Mitt Romney. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line28</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>                                           ### </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Pam-Finlayson-Thursday-Final.html#line29</link>
	<author>Pam Finlayson</author>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
