<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <link>http://www.gopconvention2012.com/media-portal/speakers/</link>
	<title>Reince Priebus</title>
	<description>Reince Priebus
Chairman, Republican National Committee
(Remarks as Prepared for Delivery)
</description>

<item>
	<title>Ladies and gentlemen, fellow Republicans, it is my distinct honor to welcome you to the 2012 Republican National Convention. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line1</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Here we will nominate Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan to be the next President and Vice President of the United States of America! </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line2</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>But first I would like to offer our thoughts and prayers for the safety of all those in the pathway of the hurricane. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line3</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>On behalf of our party, let me extend our sincere gratitude to the people of Tampa. We're just thrilled to be here--and humbled by your hospitality. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line4</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thanks to the tireless work of our convention staff and volunteers, this will be an inspiring three days--a convention truly worthy of the next President of the United States. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line5</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>From this stage, we'll hear from some of our party's most inspiring leaders. With us and with the entire country, they will share their stories and our vision for a better future. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line6</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We have a message for America: Elect Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan, and they will get this country working again. We will restore the idea that every person in America can live the American Dream. We embrace success, and we want everyone to be successful. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line7</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>As we gather here, the nation we love is a country in turmoil. Twenty-three million of our fellow Americans are struggling for work. Families are hurting. Wages are shrinking. The debt is rising. And just to make sure no one forgets that, we've installed two big debt clocks to remind America of Obama's fiscal recklessness. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line8</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We've seen what Obama and Biden offer. It looks nothing like hope or change. Give them another term, and we'll just get four more years of failure. But with Mitt Romney's experience and Paul Ryan's expertise, we can expect great things from a Romney-Ryan administration. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line9</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We must send America's comeback team to Washington, so the middle class can thrive--and wages can rise--and our children can succeed once again. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line10</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Republicans believe American greatness comes from the American people--not from the federal government. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line11</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>But Barack Obama thinks the government is at the center of the economic universe. He thinks that if you started a business, "You didn't build that." </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line12</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Well, how would he know? President Obama's never run a company. He hasn't even run a garage sale or seen the inside of a lemonade stand. So it's time for a President with real experience in the real economy. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line13</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Mitt Romney will be that President. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line14</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Barack Obama and his party may be satisfied with attacking the American Dream. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line15</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>But Republicans won't be satisfied until we've rebuilt the American Dream. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line16</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We will fight for a future where government spends tax dollars wisely. Where every American has the education needed to succeed. Where energy is affordable because America is energy independent, and where the middle class is growing because incomes are rising. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line17</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>We invite all Americans who believe our children deserve this better future to join with us. A victory for the Romney-Ryan ticket is not merely a Republican victory. It is a victory for America. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line18</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>So welcome to Tampa, to our convention, and to the beginning of a better future. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line19</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>Thank you and God Bless you. Let's have a great week. </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line20</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>


<item>
<title>                                                    ### </title>
	<link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/RNC/clean/Reince-Priebus.html#line21</link>
	<author>Reince Priebus</author>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
