<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<!--
Things I am doing to this file for conversion:

* Add proper header information
* Convert each <Voice_of_Customer> into an <item> 
* Make the item title a combination of Sender and Subject (if available)
* Make the item description from the Contents
* Strip out unnecessary tags:
   - <Received> (Note: tried to convert to pubDate but format needs to be fixed)
   - <Sender_x0020_Name>
   - <Has_x0020_Attachments>

Additional things I am cleaning up manually:
* Removed cid: lines
* For forwarded messages, cleaned up unnecessary stuff and replace sender with original sender
-->
<channel>
  <title>Navistar Voice of Customer</title>
  <link>http://www.infomous.com</link>
  <description>Test of using Infomous to visualize Navistar's Voice of Customer messages
    </description>
  
<item>
<title>Kerri Podewell:
voice of the customer template - FL</title>
<description> 


Kerri Podewell

Director, Pricing &amp; Strategic Initiatives

phone: 331-332-6966  І   cell:  630-743-9079

 

Navistar, Inc.

2701 Navistar Drive

Lisle, IL  60532

 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerri Podewell:</title>
<description> 

We should include the parts in the ppt to our VOC database.

 

Thanks,
Kerri

 


 

Kerri Podewell

Director, Pricing &amp; Strategic Initiatives

phone: 331-332-6966  І   cell:  630-743-9079

 

Navistar, Inc.

2701 Navistar Drive

Lisle, IL  60532

 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Scott Zinsli:
Boyer Meritor </title>
<description>Starting of competitive knowledge…this one is old from 2009….would like some similar info more current on air bags if possible.

Here is the list from 2009.

 

I will follow up with you on Goodyear Pricing, from Freightliner, and local WD’s

 

Thanks for all your help.

 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Linda B Stone:
Pricing on AC29884PG...Direct Ship</title>
<description>For voice of customer

AA Wheel, Kansas City, Mo. sells this wheel to end user for $137………….our DN is $155.78

Dealer is buying from AA wheel….no freight and lower price.  I don’t know what our cost is, but would be good to check it out, since it is exact same product…apples for apples  

Linda Stone, PSM-Parts

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Dave Olson
pricing</title>
<description> 

Carlos,

 

Here is the list for all makes.

 

Please let me know if you have any questions.

 

Thanks

 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Scott Zinsli:
WD Pricing </title>
<description>

Kerri,

Here are some examples on WD pricing in Iowa and Minnesota.

I will be sending you updates as I receive them.

 </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rickey Hall:
Parts Pricing</title>
<description>More competitive intel
 
Here are some flyers from MHC Kenworth out of Memphis by Diamond International

Chuck Imbler, Jr.


Also see attachments

 
visit us at www.diamondtrucks.com &lt;http://www.diamondtrucks.com&gt;  or www.facebook.com/diamondtrucks &lt;http://www.facebook.com/diamondtrucks&gt; 

 
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Chuck Imbler, Jr.:
pricing eamples</title>
<description>Another….
 

Here is pricing examples from the Rush Enterprise people.

Chuck


Would you please forward to Kerri Podewell. Rich asked me to send some pricing examples.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ronnie Hartman:
pricing</title>
<description>While this is an email….the source info is good.


Can we note vendor in the database?  It would be compared to DNet  (but we will also compare to our cost in the end….)

 
Here is a pricing Issue from Ed Kyrish out of Houston Texas. We also buy product from the company he references TTAC and there prices are much cheaper than Navistar.

Chuck Imbler, Jr.

Ed

FYI

 

We need to discuss we can purchase from a company called TTAC cost is $175.00. 

Something is very wrong with Navistar’s pricing

 

Ronnie

 

Ronnie, as our conversation here are the part numbers and issues , first Cy Fair I.S.D. drivers heater core 2585989c1 natl fleet $ 909.00 , they said they

Can purchase this locally under a Kysor # 2612251 for $ 189.00, second pricing complaints on surge tank # 2602943c91 this price has increased

From 2010  for $ 95.00, to 2011 $ 221.00, to current price of $ 315.68   this is  a duel port sure tank with a long hose and a piece of reflective tape

There is another tank ( the tank itself is identical ) with a shorter hose and no tape 2602872c91 that sell for $ 153.09 customers do not understand

Why such an increase and price difference. Thanks Ray Z.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ed Kyrish:
Scanned from ToshParts 04/25/2012 14:44</title>
<description>Email and file….

More pricing issues from Houston Texas

Chuck Imbler, Jr.


  I TALKED WITH THREE DIFFERENT DEALERS.  IT  SEEMS LIKE AT THE MOMENT FLYERS ARE NOT IN VOGUE.

PRICING COMPARISONS ARE WORSE THAN EVER.  LET ME EXPLAIN THE ATTACHED.

ITEM # 1.  THIS IS A PTO WE ARE INSTALLING ON 50 NEW UNITS.  NAV. PRICE IS $ 581.96.  CUSTOMER WAS

QUOTED $ 495.02.  OBVIOUSLY OUR COMPETITION IS MAKING A PROFIT.   WE HAVE ASKED FOR AN SPA.  

WE WILL PURCHASE OUTSIDE IF WE DO NOT HEAR PROMPTLY.

ITEM # 2

IN THE SPIRIT OF DEALING WITH CARQUEST WE PURCHASED THIS BATTERY FOR 100.07.  NAV.DEALER NET

WAS $ 49.05 .  WHERE IS THE RECIPROCITY?

ITEM # 3.  

THIS IS A PAGE FROM A COMPETITOR SHOWING THE HEATER CORE REFERRED TO YOU IN THE MESSAGE

I FORWARDED YOUFROM RON HARTMAN.  THE PRICING IS RIDICULOUS.    

 

DISREGARD THE SEAL PRICING MEMO.  I ADDRESSED IT LAST YEAR.  DON&apos;T KNOW HOW IT GOT COPIED.

 

SORRY COULD NOT GIVE YOU MORE.  I WILL FORWARD JACK SAUMS RESPONSE.


Scanned from ToshParts.
Resolution:200x200 DPI
----------------------------------------
This is automated scan.  Please do not reply.
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerri Podewell:
FW: FL template to DL (2).xlsx</title>
<description> 


Lets try this again.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerri Podewell:
FW: Autocar Sales to Rush</title>
<description>This and Boyer should be top priority for review.

 

Thanks,

Kerri

 


Kerri – stop by and I’ll give you the background on this file.

 

Mike Harris

Director, Product Management - Vehicle Components Group

 

Navistar Inc | 2701 Navistar Drive, Lisle, IL 60532

P:  331-332-2125 | C: 813-376-9977  mike.harris@navistar.com

 

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Russell Benko:
FW: ATF Fluid - FATF27101D</title>
<description>Please add to VOC database.

 
PDC,

I think it is Fleetrite 


The supplier is BASF.

 
This is the part you asked me to follow up on.

 

Our price on this part is $2166.19

 

Our cost is $1,630

 

Alison’s price is $1,610.53 

 

Our cost is higher than the competitive price.

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kerri Podewell:
FW: Emailing: 20120518084632832</title>
<description>Price - Kenworth data for VOC

Gina - can you summarize how we compare - both our DNet, and our GM%  (to understand if a cost issue or price risk compared to Kenworth)

Thanks,
Kerri


Kerri    Here is another line of parts (Bendix) that might need to be looked
at.  


Mal

Check out the pricing on the 298818 bendix knob. I put that we purchased from Freightliner but seen that we got it from Kenworth.

Eddie
The message is ready to be sent with the following file or link attachments:

</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Gina Hoefferle:
FW: Competitive Information</title>
<description>Info to VOC

Vince,


Thank you for sharing the data.  I do have a question.  Can you tell me what price level these prices would be compared to?

 

·         For example, the Bendix 102657N is advertised at $21.91 in attachment 5.  Current Navistar National Fleet is $12.89 and Retail is $25.86 for part BX102657N.  Would you be competing at the Retail price level with this competitor?

 

·         Bendix Air Dryer Cartridge is 109685X is $157.91 in the advertisement.  Navistar National Fleet is $179.17 and Retail is $378.13.  What price level would we be comparing to in this example?

Thanks,


Greetings:

The six attachments, submitted for your information, are examples of competitive pricing we continuously face in our market area.

Please contact our Parts Manager, Todd Moyer, or me with any questions you may have.

Thank you,

Vince Wigfield,

Del-Val International Trucks, Inc.


</description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>

