<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Sample Surevey</title>
    <link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html</link>
    <description>This is the channel description</description>

<item><title>C000: Have it offsite....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C000</link><description>Have it offsite.</description></item>
<item><title>C001: no thanksgiving lunch right after thanksgiving since we just...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C001</link><description>no thanksgiving lunch right after thanksgiving since we just ate those dishes a few days ago, Otherwise, conference was very well executed</description></item>
<item><title>C002: More soda and coffee...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C002</link><description>More soda and coffee</description></item>
<item><title>C003: Create tracks for the tutorial so that topics of same intere...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C003</link><description>Create tracks for the tutorial so that topics of same interests don't run in parallel (to avoid situations like GaN running at the same time of power away for example)</description></item>
<item><title>C004: More food...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C004</link><description>More food</description></item>
<item><title>C005: I did not like the vodaphone guy....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C005</link><description>I did not like the vodaphone guy.</description></item>
<item><title>C006: Last year's speakers were better....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C006</link><description>Last year's speakers were better.</description></item>
<item><title>C007: I have no specific suggestion....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C007</link><description>I have no specific suggestion.</description></item>
<item><title>C008: Adding more keynote speech in technical session...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C008</link><description>Adding more keynote speech in technical session</description></item>
<item><title>C009: Make the information more readily available on the intranet,...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C009</link><description>Make the information more readily available on the intranet, and the sooner (before the conference) the better.</description></item>
<item><title>C010: Provide more chance for others to attend...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C010</link><description>Provide more chance for others to attend</description></item>
<item><title>C011: Have more keynotes during or shortly after lunch. Engineers...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C011</link><description>Have more keynotes during or shortly after lunch. Engineers arriving at 8am is a tall order and difficult for those who have to commute from home.</description></item>
<item><title>C012: Invite potential customers and ket them give their poerspect...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C012</link><description>Invite potential customers and ket them give their poerspective of the products they expect us to design.</description></item>
<item><title>C013: I would like to have more keynote speech by different compan...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C013</link><description>I would like to have more keynote speech by different companies or different departments.</description></item>
<item><title>C014: Some presentations and tutorials did not had summary/abstrac...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C014</link><description>Some presentations and tutorials did not had summary/abstract available beforehand.</description></item>
<item><title>C015: Give a summary of posters titles and demo summaries and when...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C015</link><description>Give a summary of posters titles and demo summaries and when they would be presented. A schudule for poster like that for speakers would be nice.</description></item>
<item><title>C016: have all presentation/tutorial so folks do not need t...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C016</link><description>have all presentation/tutorial locally so folks do not need to walk back and forth</description></item>
<item><title>C017: More outside speakers who represent our customers and their ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C017</link><description>More outside speakers who represent our customers and their needs.</description></item>
<item><title>C018: Definitely the food. Besides that, some of the speakers were...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C018</link><description>Definitely the food. Besides that, some of the speakers were not very good.</description></item>
<item><title>C019: Have product line VPs talk about the technologies thrust tha...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C019</link><description>Have product line VPs talk about the technologies thrust that they are interested in helping them to move in their market.</description></item>
<item><title>C020: Bring people in from Nokia, Apple, RIM, or Samsung to talk a...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C020</link><description>Bring people in from Nokia, Apple, RIM, or Samsung to talk about cell phone trends; from GM, Toyota, or Bosch to talk about automotive trends (not just the "infotainment" portion).</description></item>
<item><title>C021: Keep up the good work....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C021</link><description>Keep up the good work.</description></item>
<item><title>C022: Communicate to session chairs when a keynote speaker is behi...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C022</link><description>Communicate to session chairs when a keynote speaker is behind schedule and delay the start of the sessions (synchronize between all sessions)</description></item>
<item><title>C023: Have more variety of topics from the guest speakers on areas...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C023</link><description>Have more variety of topics from the guest speakers on areas focused by the KMS organization.</description></item>
<item><title>C024: The times on the presentations was too short. That could be ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C024</link><description>The times on the presentations was too short. That could be lengthened by a little.</description></item>
<item><title>C025: Start at 9am, instead of 8am....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C025</link><description>Start at 9am, instead of 8am.</description></item>
<item><title>C026: more big-time outside speakers...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C026</link><description>more big-time outside speakers</description></item>
<item><title>C027: More diverse keynote speakers. Most of the company is NOT wo...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C027</link><description>More diverse keynote speakers. Most of the company is NOT working on handset applications so there was little value for them.</description></item>
<item><title>C028: Provide more table for lunch (it was a bit hard to find tabl...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C028</link><description>Provide more table for lunch (it was a bit hard to find table for lunch on the first two days)</description></item>
<item><title>C029: Some of the tracks could not be attended because they were r...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C029</link><description>Some of the tracks could not be attended because they were running in parallel. It would be better if they can be moved to another day</description></item>
<item><title>C030: Maybe 5 more minutes between presentations to allow a bit of...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C030</link><description>Maybe 5 more minutes between presentations to allow a bit of chat inbetween.</description></item>
<item><title>C031: Cover more business areas with the keynotes. Especially inno...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C031</link><description>Cover more business areas with the keynotes. Especially innovative businesses: electric cars, medical.</description></item>
<item><title>C032: Maybe a keynote from a professor would also be nice. ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C032</link><description>Maybe a keynote from a professor would also be nice. </description></item>
<item><title>C033: Hire external tutorial presenters....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C033</link><description>Hire external tutorial presenters.</description></item>
<item><title>C034: Try to improve presentations....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C034</link><description>Try to improve presentations.</description></item>
<item><title>C035: Not much but if there had been different varieties of food s...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C035</link><description>Not much but if there had been different varieties of food such as Chinese,Indian,Continental etc it would have catered to everybodys palate.but nevertheless it was great.Good job.</description></item>
<item><title>C036: More information on presentation schedules, available earlie...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C036</link><description>More information on presentation schedules, available earlier would have been good.</description></item>
<item><title>C037: Closing the conference earlier in the day on Thursday would ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C037</link><description>Closing the conference earlier in the day on Thursday would have made travel easier.</description></item>
<item><title>C038: Conference is notably very power/mobile devices centric. A k...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C038</link><description>Conference is notably very power/mobile devices centric. A key-note speaker looking at an area more applicable to HSPD would be good.</description></item>
<item><title>C039: No suggestions, I was very satisfied....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C039</link><description>No suggestions, I was very satisfied.</description></item>
<item><title>C040: More technical and updates on business side....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C040</link><description>More technical and updates on business side.</description></item>
<item><title>C041: As a very small request, it would be nice if breakfast had b...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C041</link><description>As a very small request, it would be nice if breakfast had bagels or other non-sugary items.</description></item>
<item><title>C042: Arrange presentations so that power related stuff doesn't ge...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C042</link><description>Arrange presentations so that power related stuff doesn't get multi-tracked. It was all piled up in the 1st 1/2 day and nothing on the 2nd. This also happened in the tutorials with GaN vs MOSFET at the same time.</description></item>
<item><title>C043: Give more warning before hand for paper preparation....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C043</link><description>Give more warning before hand for paper preparation.</description></item>
<item><title>C044: Have greater communication on what type of information or le...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C044</link><description>Have greater communication on what type of information or level of information should be included. So that there is less overview but not too much detail. A better balance perhaps.</description></item>
<item><title>C045: Tutorial sessions were perhaps too long and really just a co...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C045</link><description>Tutorial sessions were perhaps too long and really just a collection of papers instead of coordinated presentations.</description></item>
<item><title>C046: Provide power strips so we can recharge laptops....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C046</link><description>Provide power strips so we can recharge laptops.</description></item>
<item><title>C047: Include all aspects of innovation, not just design but also ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C047</link><description>Include all aspects of innovation, not just design but also operational aspects.</description></item>
<item><title>C048: Ideally would have all in one building to better facilitate ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C048</link><description>Ideally would have all in one building to better facilitate travel. Lots of people came and went since it was on site - if offsite, there would be better networking and attendance.</description></item>
<item><title>C049: more seating at opening session...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C049</link><description>more seating at opening session</description></item>
<item><title>C050: in 2008 you proposed round table focusing innovation, kind o...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C050</link><description>in 2008 you proposed round table focusing innovation, kind of brainstorming on certain topic. I think that was a good experience that could be repeated.</description></item>
<item><title>C051: Would like to see speakers from other key technology areas. ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C051</link><description>Would like to see speakers from other key technology areas. Exp: medical devices/industry</description></item>
<item><title>C052: Hope the innovation conference can be held every year this w...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C052</link><description>Hope the innovation conference can be held every year this way so that we can all feel the energy and excitement that is present in the company all in one place.</description></item>
<item><title>C053: Expand the disapines that are represented at the conference;...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C053</link><description>Expand the disapines that are represented at the conference; i.e. Applications, Test/Product, Packaging</description></item>
<item><title>C054: Discuss specific tool challenges that have already been solv...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C054</link><description>Discuss specific tool challenges that have already been solved or can be solved.</description></item>
<item><title>C055: not scheduling tutorials on same area (process, design, cad)...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C055</link><description>not scheduling tutorials on same area (process, design, cad) against each other. </description></item>
<item><title>C056: Much better pre-conference communication to whole engineerin...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C056</link><description>Much better pre-conference communication to whole engineering community. No upper management approval should be required for any engineer to attend or be copied on emails !! Even paper authors were not informed of their paper schedule until the last minute. </description></item>
<item><title>C057: Poster sessions seemed a little sidelined. Would be better t...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C057</link><description>Poster sessions seemed a little sidelined. Would be better to have one giant poster session in E1. </description></item>
<item><title>C058: Many engineers work on IEEE commitees to organise techni...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C058</link><description>Many engineers work on IEEE commitees to organise technical conferences. Their insight should be sought out.</description></item>
<item><title>C059: Scheduling. Tutorials in particular. There were tutorials I ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C059</link><description>Scheduling. Tutorials in particular. There were tutorials I wanted to see that were at the same time.</description></item>
<item><title>C060: Provide a more balanced breakfast and maybe cut back a littl...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C060</link><description>Provide a more balanced breakfast and maybe cut back a little on lunch. Complex carbs and protien help with concentration. Limit events to 6:00pm. Except the main dinner.</description></item>
<item><title>C061: It's pretty good as is...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C061</link><description>It's pretty good as is</description></item>
<item><title>C062: The best networking times were the Poster and Demo sessions;...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C062</link><description>The best networking times were the Poster and Demo sessions; not a contrived group "solving" a problem (which was tried in 2009 and I was glad to see abandoned this year). How to enhance Posters and Demos?</description></item>
<item><title>C063: Maybe ask each accepted paper / presenter to also author a p...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C063</link><description>Maybe ask each accepted paper / presenter to also author a poster (yes, more work... but valuable) which could be displayed in a separate section for those who can't attend the paper presentation. This way, EVERYONE could get a chance to observe these new techniques/technologies and more connect-the-dots thinking would occur.</description></item>
<item><title>C064: Ask for at least two people capable of presenting each Demo....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C064</link><description>Ask for at least two people capable of presenting each Demo. Then encourage each Demo presenter to take some time off and make the rounds of the other Demos. Many of the Demo presenters were "stuck" at their Demo all night.</description></item>
<item><title>C065: Sponsor a "Poster Stage" in a separate adjacent area where a...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C065</link><description>Sponsor a "Poster Stage" in a separate adjacent area where any accepted Poster author could sign up for 5-7min slots to present their ideas in a rapid fire kind of forum.</description></item>
<item><title>C066: Sponsor "Competitive Alerts", which could be done by Design ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C066</link><description>Sponsor "Competitive Alerts", which could be done by Design Engr., Apps. or Mkt. to take even one competitor's part number and break it down - pros/cons, how we compare and compete against it. Alternatively, Mkt. folks could take on an entire competitor portfolio or market segment and do the same. Presentations could be short; 15min to 30min, but questions would be a valuable part of this.</description></item>
<item><title>C067: Sponsor a "How We Won the Socket" category to allow Mkt./ Ap...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C067</link><description>Sponsor a "How We Won the Socket" category to allow Mkt./ Apps. to describe a successful design win process from the "trenches". Some of these stories deserve more time than during an award presentation. There is valuable learning to be gained, especially for younger guys and gals, from these compelling stories.</description></item>
<item><title>C068: Overall it was a very good conference. One area of improveme...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C068</link><description>Overall it was a very good conference. One area of improvement would be more food choices for visitors especially vegetarian.</description></item>
<item><title>C069: Possibility to do brainstorming in a small (3-4) group of pe...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C069</link><description>Possibility to do brainstorming in a small (3-4) group of people about future improvements/products.</description></item>
<item><title>C070: More technical application coverage...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C070</link><description>More technical application coverage</description></item>
<item><title>C071: In the next conference I would like to hear/see examples of ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C071</link><description>In the next conference I would like to hear/see examples of National's innovative approaches to solve the issues brought up by the key-note speakers in 2010. In other words, we should demonstrate that we are willing to walk-the-talk, and that we are listening and responding to our customers' challenges.</description></item>
<item><title>C072: invite more technical key notes, the rest seems fine...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C072</link><description>invite more technical key notes, the rest seems fine</description></item>
<item><title>C073: More technical tutorials...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C073</link><description>More technical tutorials</description></item>
<item><title>C074: This time, some of the external speakers tended to focus on ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C074</link><description>This time, some of the external speakers tended to focus on their own companies or their own products. </description></item>
<item><title>C075: They did not cover the innovation processes, as such....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C075</link><description>They did not cover the innovation processes, as such.</description></item>
<item><title>C076: The demo night was a bit disappointment. I think the Marriot...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C076</link><description>The demo night was a bit disappointment. I think the Marriot hotel ballroom would serve better as the venue for this. There was also some meetings scheduled overlapping the demo night. Demoing teams should arrange that everyone has a change of visiting other stands.</description></item>
<item><title>C077: I think that there should be a break of 5 to 10 mins between...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C077</link><description>I think that there should be a break of 5 to 10 mins between the sessions, so that those who need to move to another lecture hall, would have enought time for that.</description></item>
<item><title>C078: Some of the tutorials were not well organized, for instance,...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C078</link><description>Some of the tutorials were not well organized, for instance, no one was present to introduce the speakers or the session started too late or had to end early because of the closing speach by Detlev.</description></item>
<item><title>C079: Extend one extra day....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C079</link><description>Extend one extra day.</description></item>
<item><title>C080: Better paper selection. They were inconsistent. Some excel...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C080</link><description>Better paper selection. They were inconsistent. Some excellent, some very weak. Judge by technical merit, not by equal BU participation!</description></item>
<item><title>C081: Do not have conference between Thanksgiving and Christmas. O...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C081</link><description>Do not have conference between Thanksgiving and Christmas. October would be better.</description></item>
<item><title>C082: Please accept more engineers to the conference in the future...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C082</link><description>Please accept more engineers to the conference in the future.</description></item>
<item><title>C083: Timing in early December is tough. I have a team of enginee...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C083</link><description>Timing in early December is tough. I have a team of engineers working hard to deliver to customer mielstones in March. We loose a week at Thanksgiving and 2 at Christmas. To loose another week in between is awful. I would recommend 2nd or 3rd week of September.</description></item>
<item><title>C084: Have inovative workshops...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C084</link><description>Have inovative workshops</description></item>
<item><title>C085: Changes may get it worse....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C085</link><description>Changes may get it worse.</description></item>
<item><title>C086: Allow electronic feedback on (1) posters (so many needing fe...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C086</link><description>Allow electronic feedback on (1) posters (so many needing feedback so fast) and also (2) presenters.</description></item>
<item><title>C087: It would have been nice to have all sessions in one building...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C087</link><description>It would have been nice to have all sessions in one building.</description></item>
<item><title>C088: More participation from remote design centers, although this...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C088</link><description>More participation from remote design centers, although this year was better than previous ones.</description></item>
<item><title>C089: PL and BU leaders should encourage participation...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C089</link><description>PL and BU leaders should encourage participation</description></item>
<item><title>C090: The tutorial day might be better spread out over multiple da...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C090</link><description>The tutorial day might be better spread out over multiple days. We might rethink the whole tutorial idea.</description></item>
<item><title>C091: Pls avoid sharing the rooms(accommodation). Very uncomfortab...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C091</link><description>Pls avoid sharing the rooms(accommodation). Very uncomfortable</description></item>
<item><title>C092: Better keynotes. All the keynotes were business related and...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C092</link><description>Better keynotes. All the keynotes were business related and seemed to be generally geared towards a very small portion of the audience (upper managment). A mix of business and technical keynotes, which will interest engineers, sales, upper management, marketing, etc. would be useful.</description></item>
<item><title>C093: Nothing much to be changed here. Well done....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C093</link><description>Nothing much to be changed here. Well done.</description></item>
<item><title>C094: seems like for some reasons, not as many joined the 8am sess...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C094</link><description>seems like for some reasons, not as many joined the 8am sessions. perhaps, a later start time of 8:30am will help.</description></item>
<item><title>C095: Give opportunities to have "networking time" during the day....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C095</link><description>Give opportunities to have "networking time" during the day.</description></item>
<item><title>C096: Individual hotel rooms. Breakfast...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C096</link><description>Individual hotel rooms. Breakfast</description></item>
<item><title>C097: Stop forcing people to share rooms. It causes such a negati...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C097</link><description>Stop forcing people to share rooms. It causes such a negative impression of this conference, it is not worth the money saved. When you consider that the rooms cost $90 plus tax, and you are putting two to a room, you are saving $49 plus tax per person (from out of town). In my opinion, this is such a small amount of money, it is not worth it to have such a bad impression with the attendees. I dont think people in Santa Clara appreciate the extreme negative impression it gives to people from the other sites. Many people refuse to attend solely for this reason.</description></item>
<item><title>C098: Eliminate room sharing....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C098</link><description>Eliminate room sharing.</description></item>
<item><title>C099: Cut it down to two days. maybe break up the flow a bit. less...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C099</link><description>Cut it down to two days. maybe break up the flow a bit. less speakers more interactive discussions based around common technology challenge or common customer issue - maybe some guided watering holes etc.</description></item>
<item><title>C100: more outside speaders...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C100</link><description>more outside speaders</description></item>
<item><title>C101: Add an extra day, and make the presentations 40 minutes long...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C101</link><description>Add an extra day, and make the presentations 40 minutes long instead of 25 minutes.</description></item>
<item><title>C102: Make it wide open for engineers...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C102</link><description>Make it wide open for engineers</description></item>
<item><title>C103: provide a microphone that wraps around the speaker's ear and...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C103</link><description>provide a microphone that wraps around the speaker's ear and cheek(like the rock stars use).</description></item>
<item><title>C104: List the time table of events/papers by their time, ie 2pm P...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C104</link><description>List the time table of events/papers by their time, ie 2pm Paper 1 2:30pm Paper 2 etc.</description></item>
<item><title>C105: expand to more attendee...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C105</link><description>expand to more attendee</description></item>
<item><title>C106: Make the presentation material (text and media) available fo...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C106</link><description>Make the presentation material (text and media) available for attendees.</description></item>
<item><title>C107: After all this new information, its important to be able to ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C107</link><description>After all this new information, its important to be able to process it so that it will actually make a difference in my work. However, there is often a rush to get stuff done since projects have been on hold. It would be nice to have some kind of debriefing or something a while after to make sure that we're able to make use of what we've learned.</description></item>
<item><title>C108: The sessions to be in the same building...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C108</link><description>The sessions to be in the same building</description></item>
<item><title>C109: Keep the venue for parallel tracks closer to each other (Wit...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C109</link><description>Keep the venue for parallel tracks closer to each other (Within Bldg E)</description></item>
<item><title>C110: Stagger tutorials, at least those in the same category (i.e....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C110</link><description>Stagger tutorials, at least those in the same category (i.e. technology vs design) to allow more opportunity to attend.</description></item>
<item><title>C111: It would be nice to have the demo night at the hotel. Being...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C111</link><description>It would be nice to have the demo night at the hotel. Being around campus all day, it is good to switch venues at night.</description></item>
<item><title>C112: Better program committee (for presentation selections), and ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C112</link><description>Better program committee (for presentation selections), and better conference organization and communication.</description></item>
<item><title>C113: No much, it was good....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C113</link><description>No much, it was good.</description></item>
<item><title>C114: Conference open to most technical people...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C114</link><description>Conference open to most technical people</description></item>
<item><title>C115: Figure out a configuration which allows more traffic to all ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C115</link><description>Figure out a configuration which allows more traffic to all of the posters.</description></item>
<item><title>C116: Mics (or repeat the question). Material (video) availabel ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C116</link><description>Mics (or repeat the question). Material (video) availabel online (I believe this is planned). Ability to watch at remote sites (ex. live feed) for those who can't travel (ex. budget restrictions).</description></item>
<item><title>C117: A minimum of take-away summary of the conference, e.g., a ti...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C117</link><description>A minimum of take-away summary of the conference, e.g., a titles or titles+abstracts booklet. The few pages of titles were good, though, but a booklet including the abstracts would have been better.</description></item>
<item><title>C118: A minimum of take-away summary of the conference, e.g., a ti...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C118</link><description>A minimum of take-away summary of the conference, e.g., a titles or titles+abstracts booklet. The few pages of titles were good, though, but a booklet including the abstracts would have been better.</description></item>
<item><title>C119: How to get more people offsite involved....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C119</link><description>How to get more people offsite involved.</description></item>
<item><title>C120: This year went a little better than last year, there was mor...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C120</link><description>This year went a little better than last year, there was more time for the networking and that was appreciated.</description></item>
<item><title>C121: Better food. some presentations were over flowed with people...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C121</link><description>Better food. some presentations were over flowed with people. Preregister to identify # so room size can be set by desire.</description></item>
<item><title>C122: Perhaps have more specific back outs of funtions such as des...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C122</link><description>Perhaps have more specific back outs of funtions such as design (already done) , layout, product, CAD, test. This would allow designers more face to face time with designers doing the same job.</description></item>
<item><title>C123: No ideas...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C123</link><description>No ideas</description></item>
<item><title>C124: Employ higher standards in selecting papers/presentations....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C124</link><description>Employ higher standards in selecting papers/presentations.</description></item>
<item><title>C125: Invite more design engineers and less PE/TD managers....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C125</link><description>Invite more design engineers and less PE/TD managers.</description></item>
<item><title>C126: It was all good...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C126</link><description>It was all good</description></item>
<item><title>C127: Off-site venue. Keeps all attendees captive and engaged....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C127</link><description>Off-site venue. Keeps all attendees captive and engaged.</description></item>
<item><title>C128: More talk on innovation successes at National. Is innovation...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C128</link><description>More talk on innovation successes at National. Is innovation only tied to 'mobility'? Maybe we should be clearer on messaging - re: Spark etc</description></item>
<item><title>C129: More customer presentation and sharing success story with Na...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C129</link><description>More customer presentation and sharing success story with National and their future roadmaps</description></item>
<item><title>C130: Better distribution of time slots for papers. Some of the to...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C130</link><description>Better distribution of time slots for papers. Some of the topics of common interest were clubbed to same time slots, had to choose one over the other</description></item>
<item><title>C131: Maybe some of the speaker choices could have been more relev...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C131</link><description>Maybe some of the speaker choices could have been more relevant or compelling. I'm not sure (for example) what Vodafone's business model in India teaches, since they don't seem to (or appears tried to) integrate the more efficient business practices in other areas (markets) to make more money or prevent a future obsolescence or replacement.</description></item>
<item><title>C132: Keep all the venues in one building....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C132</link><description>Keep all the venues in one building.</description></item>
<item><title>C133: More iPads!...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C133</link><description>More iPads!</description></item>
<item><title>C134: Fewer presentations with higher quality. Wider spectrum of s...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C134</link><description>Fewer presentations with higher quality. Wider spectrum of subjects for keynotes.</description></item>
<item><title>C135: stagger the tutorials. too many linked themes in parallel...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C135</link><description>stagger the tutorials. too many linked themes in parallel</description></item>
<item><title>C136: For the time period provided, it was great....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C136</link><description>For the time period provided, it was great.</description></item>
<item><title>C137: Add the SRI class for all designers, that is a good class fo...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C137</link><description>Add the SRI class for all designers, that is a good class for all of us.</description></item>
<item><title>C138: The major talks I heard had a pretty strong emphasis on wire...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C138</link><description>The major talks I heard had a pretty strong emphasis on wireless (cell phones). While a big growing market it may be becoming mature. Same with many of the automotive sensing applications. I like the possibilities of high power systems.</description></item>
<item><title>C139: Lots of information presented in a short amount of time, eve...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C139</link><description>Lots of information presented in a short amount of time, even though they were very long days. Made it very difficult to network, discuss papers and posters in the amount of time alloted.</description></item>
<item><title>C140: More experience sharing sessions....</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C140</link><description>More experience sharing sessions.</description></item>
<item><title>C141: Some of the internal presentations were a bit weak and techn...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C141</link><description>Some of the internal presentations were a bit weak and technologies dated. In the future, focus on fewer subjects and add higher protein.</description></item>
<item><title>C142: Incorporate more tech presentations/tutorials on emerging te...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C142</link><description>Incorporate more tech presentations/tutorials on emerging technologies and their usefulness in resolving customer problems.</description></item>
<item><title>C143: Would it be possible to load the shown documents to the pers...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C143</link><description>Would it be possible to load the shown documents to the personal laptops after the presentations on the conference arena. Then it would be easier to go through the presentations more deeply when they are still in fresh memory and ask more questions concerning that if needed.</description></item>
<item><title>C144: I think the delivery of some presentations could be greatly ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C144</link><description>I think the delivery of some presentations could be greatly improved with some basic presentation skills. The technical merit of some papers was obscured by poor delivery.</description></item>
<item><title>C145: A small break in the 3-hours technical presentations-track w...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C145</link><description>A small break in the 3-hours technical presentations-track would help to keep the audience attention strong throughout the track</description></item>
<item><title>C146: If possible hold offsite. Encourage feedback through a singl...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C146</link><description>If possible hold offsite. Encourage feedback through a single feedback form with a minmimum number of attendance options required.</description></item>
<item><title>C147: give more knowledge what type of digital and analog library ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C147</link><description>give more knowledge what type of digital and analog library available for designers</description></item>
<item><title>C148: start requests for papers earlier, provide some target topic...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C148</link><description>start requests for papers earlier, provide some target topic guidelines like spark an idea</description></item>
<item><title>C149: Maybe the tutorials or some of the sessions could be turned ...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C149</link><description>Maybe the tutorials or some of the sessions could be turned into group discussions about an area of interest.</description></item>
<item><title>C150: Should not make everyone attend every speech/presentation/se...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C150</link><description>Should not make everyone attend every speech/presentation/session. People get tired and loose interest when listening to different stuff they are not experts in. Should have more freedom.</description></item>
<item><title>C151: schedule time to travel between sessions...</title><link>http://www.infomous.com/site/mockups/Survey/AllComments.html#C151</link><description>schedule time to travel between sessions</description></item>


</channel>
</rss>
