<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="http://s3-media4.ak.yelpcdn.com/assets/2/www/css/b9ec5d4cf139/rss-en_US.css" type="text/css" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#">
	<channel>
		<copyright>Copyright 2013 Yelp, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright>
		<title>Recent Reviews Near San Francisco, CA</title>
		<link>http://www.yelp.com/sf</link>
		<description>Yelp - Recent Reviews Near San Francisco, CA</description>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:46:38  PST</pubDate>
			<title>J S.'s Review of Tempest Bar - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/tempest-bar-san-francisco#hrid:BeY3mEn-Y6Acbl5A8e_7Kg</link>
			<description>Tempest Bar is MY BAR OF CHOICE! It's such a wonderful feeling for an adult of age to have a regular bar to go to with your friends &amp; coworkers where you always feel at home &amp; with some seriously…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.406289056</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7811864641</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:45:22  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Alejandro E.'s Review of San Francisco Bay Computer Services - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/san-francisco-bay-computer-services-san-francisco-2#hrid:WbL1FUuyEjn1t20yDushqw</link>
			<description>Mi hermanito me dijo que le prestara mi laptop, se la preste y como 2 horas más tarde me la regreso y me dijo que él había bajado unos juegos del internet,  cuando la trate de encender me di cuenta…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4180284</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7493772</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:51  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Captain B.'s Review of Za Gourmet Pizza - San Francisco (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/za-gourmet-pizza-san-francisco#hrid:HlrHSlCh46GAgas4AiOYHQ</link>
			<description>The reviews are great, but honestly this is just another average pizza delivery place. I'm a bit shocked by all of the 5 star reviews.

Delivery was pretty fast, though the guy on the phone was a bit…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4190622</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7985523</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:44  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Matt S.'s Review of Elios Family Restaurant - San Leandro (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/elios-family-restaurant-san-leandro#hrid:-Yws_llnrilwUQ5zrsxVGw</link>
			<description>Big portions.  Great breakfast food anytime of the day.  I come here at least four times a month.  The crowd here is a bit older but a lot of younger adults are starting to come here also.  They are…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.14207</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.70138</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:23  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Nancy K.'s Review of Nan King Road Bistro - San Francisco (2/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/nan-king-road-bistro-san-francisco#hrid:AOTfbm2rsa5TErR0bRnM4Q</link>
			<description>Food took too long to come out (waited almost an hour), &amp; when it did come out, half the dishes had already gone cold. We ordered beef for one dish, but they brought chicken instead, so ended up with…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4661412</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7629304</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:05  PST</pubDate>
			<title>C J.'s Review of CB Tyler Carpenter - Emeryville (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/cb-tyler-carpenter-emeryville-3#hrid:eeo0BILSvWlffDOBTwPe3g</link>
			<description>A friend recommended Cassie Tyler as a great local general contractor with a specialization in carpentry, and based on her work I would highly recommend her to anyone looking for a contractor in the…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.291802</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.840701</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:43:36  PST</pubDate>
			<title>shakun k.'s Review of Nopalito - San Francisco (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/nopalito-san-francisco-3#hrid:edI0KwV25IH7essEnBPS3g</link>
			<description>Great spot for some delightfully good small plates and drinks. The ambience was very trendy with an interesting waitstaff. The dishes brought together a ton of different, clean and fresh flavors which…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4661653</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7654223</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:42:49  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Larry L.'s Review of Apple Store - San Francisco (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/apple-store-san-francisco-2#hrid:aFWLzulS7vmMAgGLL7RnIg</link>
			<description>The customer service reps are usually more than happy to answer questions or help you figure something out.  As an example, we were looking at cases for my GF's new phone.  A customer service rep came…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4064402</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7858516</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:42:33  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Sum W.'s Review of Salena Lee, OD - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/salena-lee-od-san-francisco#hrid:SCHQ8adVrdNN7hzsLmJ42Q</link>
			<description>Keeping it short.  It always feels so comfortable and warm when i walk into this place.  Nothing beats people knowing your name when you walk in through the door.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4795556</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7538576</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:41:06  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Carlton O.'s Review of Bourbon &amp; Beef - Oakland (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/bourbon-and-beef-oakland#hrid:ol4PY6IDsnRmiq0rXZLRfw</link>
			<description>Great new place on College. Had the Mussels, ribeye, Puerco con Curtido, lobster bisque,  All really good but really liked the mussels.  Hurts to say this but the mussels are better than a cote.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.251403</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8437709</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:40:52  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Andy G.'s Review of 7 Days A Week Smog Test - Berkeley (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/7-days-a-week-smog-test-berkeley-5#hrid:kei4_ftbqAd4NlfXMMqNLA</link>
			<description>This place is great. I went in this morning (a Sunday) and had such a nice experience in a business where I guess I wasn't expecting an awful lot. Mike was friendly and squared away, greeted me…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2911786</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8651953</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:40:52  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Debby C.'s Review of Brazil Fresh Squeeze Cafe - Berkeley (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/brazil-fresh-squeeze-cafe-berkeley#hrid:O1W4ZnbOBWb9nNdd-cd-NQ</link>
			<description>Great fresh bread and flavorful, juicy chicken at a reasonable price - did not try the famous tri tip though.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.266746457</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8725528522</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:40:44  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Melody K.'s Review of The Bashful Bull Too - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-bashful-bull-too-san-francisco#hrid:YIvOuVNlOC74TpBPyd9DWQ</link>
			<description>We love this place when we want a good filling breakfast. Clean, great food, friendly service : ) Pancakes and biscuits and gravy are my favorite!</description>
			<geo:long>-122.5048247</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7418804</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:37:24  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Melody K.'s Review of Park Chow - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/park-chow-san-francisco#hrid:eP3ybA5rwE129MaMwCLc_g</link>
			<description>Love this place. We like to sit upstairs. Food is delicious. Fish always cooked perfect and the spaghetti is my favorite.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4663968</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7651459</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:36:23  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Marie P.'s Review of Papa John&#39;s Pizza - San Francisco (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/papa-johns-pizza-san-francisco#hrid:hfOV1aBfC_xMm9G6obK9_g</link>
			<description>Here's how the millions of dollars in Football advertising works wonders. 
While watching our amazing Forty Niners play the Titans the Papa Johns commercial comes on, and we are craving for pizza. We…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4744066</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7177556</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:36:08  PST</pubDate>
			<title>David D.'s Review of Purple Kow - San Francisco (2/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/purple-kow-san-francisco-2#hrid:-8frYe82K3rMslSPGrEGkA</link>
			<description>the boba taste alright.  Def not the best I have ever had.  The one upside is the size of the boba and the price.  I don't think I have ever had this much boba milk tea for its price, but for me the…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.49782</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.775905</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:36:06  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Charlotte K.'s Review of Masson Veterinary Hospital - San Bruno (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/masson-veterinary-hospital-san-bruno#hrid:7F0M8wHN3_gyM4VrdkoKxA</link>
			<description>Wondering why there are only great reviews and one bad one, for cats at least. I don't like seeing such a imbalance as it spells out that this business is feeding the good reviews.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4137939</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.6300767</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:35:21  PST</pubDate>
			<title>shakun k.'s Review of Tonga Room &amp; Hurricane Bar - San Francisco (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/tonga-room-and-hurricane-bar-san-francisco#hrid:LoROilzPyIDvnS_jlJSk6g</link>
			<description>The ambience of this place is quite childish especially with the fake rain dripping in a pool, and the overly generic music. The wait staff is mehhh, and the doormen think this place is something…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4105175</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7923392</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:35:01  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Holla F.'s Review of Bacheesos - Oakland (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/bacheesos-oakland#hrid:HnkguEEEpf0PfN581pThaA</link>
			<description>Came here for the lunch Buffett. The spread looked beautiful and colorful. It's a good spot if you're vegetarian or beef eater. The salmon was dry or overbooked, but the one chicken option was pretty…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.258968</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.809921</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:34:35  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Melody K.'s Review of Green Chile Kitchen - San Francisco (2/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/green-chile-kitchen-san-francisco#hrid:MySWrZtndQrROgenqVI6-g</link>
			<description>Great food but they can never get my order right. Simple things like no green chili inside the burrito. Pork tamales when I ordered chicken. Happened about 4 times. You can't tell if the order is…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.441843608</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7772354305</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:34:03  PST</pubDate>
			<title>David D.'s Review of The Sweet House - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-sweet-house-san-francisco#hrid:r3oAh1XHJ6H18-PBf7s9qw</link>
			<description>This is the best place for some solid milk tea.  I usually get the almond milk tea with pearls.  The boba here is made fresh and always chewy.  I would come here over purple kow any day.  The service…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4964786</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7757684</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:33:40  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Erika E.'s Review of Nabi Salon - Burlingame (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/nabi-salon-burlingame#hrid:dTMhurWfnDtxn3p4gZfXhg</link>
			<description>Su Kim is the best! She recently did my hair and makeup for my wedding and did a fantastic job! We did a trial and I was hooked. I showed her what I wanted and she did exactly that and it came out…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.365511</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.585167</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:33:12  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Jackson Z.'s Review of Shooting Star Cafe - Oakland (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/shooting-star-cafe-oakland#hrid:-HCD43aCYp_sKZtDlQQ_bA</link>
			<description>the service was sucks, because when they tell you to wait a mins, they never come back to make your order. The food takes hella to be make.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2701346</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8011926</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:32:37  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Matthew G.'s Review of Amy&#39;s Hallmark - San Mateo (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/amys-hallmark-san-mateo#hrid:QqwFZGS07L33oTji3lrNCg</link>
			<description>from 99 cent cards to over 10 dollar cards.  this hallmark has a lot to offer.  bdays, congrats, sad, happy, thanks. they got it all.  stuffed animals, holiday theme gifts.  even lil donuts, oj, and…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.284055</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.559684</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:32:02  PST</pubDate>
			<title>David D.'s Review of Zephyr Cafe - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/zephyr-cafe-san-francisco#hrid:5NXgx-u6K7pcE-CrQP8rrg</link>
			<description>I use to come to this cafe a lot to study and work on my computer.  The drinks and food are standard, but the atmosphere here is great.  The spot is big and the booths are my favorite place to site.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4981397</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7755883</geo:lat>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>