<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="http://s3-media4.ak.yelpcdn.com/assets/2/www/css/b9ec5d4cf139/rss-en_US.css" type="text/css" media="screen"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#">
	<channel>
		<copyright>Copyright 2013 Yelp, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright>
		<title>Recent Reviews Near San Francisco, CA</title>
		<link>http://www.yelp.com/sf</link>
		<description>Yelp - Recent Reviews Near San Francisco, CA</description>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:23:33  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Meuy S.'s Review of Eclipxe Hair Salon - Berkeley (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/eclipxe-hair-salon-berkeley#hrid:KTtGc25suqBmbLUvQQYkJw</link>
			<description>My friend suggested this salon because they've both go to Marisa for haircuts. Since my hair is super straight and long I wanted someone who would listen to what I want, give me suggestions and is…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2731551</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.872608</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:23:25  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Keith G.'s Review of Taverna Aventine - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/taverna-aventine-san-francisco#hrid:6N9f5gWXnbhDVEv02QfmWg</link>
			<description>Great spot!
Excellent drinks!
Excellent bartenders!
The basement is a good place to have parties. It can easily hold 30-40 people. It is a fun atmosphere.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.40303</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.79556</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:21:02  PST</pubDate>
			<title>E D.'s Review of Atelier Crenn - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/atelier-crenn-san-francisco#hrid:23Fm0A6ir-LNaPjKA3M5Gw</link>
			<description>I've had tasting menus at many Michelin star restaurants, and I was excited to try Atelier Crenn.  We didn't see any of the service issues some of the other reviewers referenced.  The pacing was…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4360742</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.799033</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:20:28  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Adrienne L.'s Review of Royal Volkswagen Audi Mazda Volvo - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/royal-volkswagen-audi-mazda-volvo-san-francisco#hrid:yDNqIs4FfuwUElECnzgwLA</link>
			<description>I recently decided to lease an Audi and being new to the city I took a chance with Royal Automotive.  I was pleasantly surprised with my experience from the moment I stepped on the lot to the time I…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.418147</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.768697</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:20:10  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Matt B.'s Review of Safeway - San Francisco (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/safeway-san-francisco-6#hrid:xJ4q4vNxCkzMoaKa8eC6Mg</link>
			<description>No shopping carts. Like, literally, none available in the store or the parking lot. Customers struggling for each cart as it frees up.

In addition, store is understaffed. Expect very long lines and a…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4309756</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.783071</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:19:46  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Keith G.'s Review of Library Bar - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/library-bar-san-francisco#hrid:65IDPIfAYtYTQ6BxzsYuHg</link>
			<description>Since books are going out of fashion, this is a good place to offload them. I have literally seen a lady walk in with a few books and leave them at this place. Book clubs are usually places where…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4097939</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.789189</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:19:41  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Vanessa W.'s Review of Sam&#39;s Log Cabin - Albany (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/sams-log-cabin-albany#hrid:KM-0gXEGc1DSQrlEDt26Tw</link>
			<description>This is hands down my favorite breakfast place. Love the homey ambiance! The food is always fresh and delicious. Try the chilaquiles - they're the best!</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2982518</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8886129</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:18:40  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Ribec F.'s Review of Dunya - San Francisco (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/dunya-san-francisco#hrid:70GgcIGKFXOtjIOD0uqsew</link>
			<description>When they first opened the food was amazing recently grabbed lunch there and it was sub par, wine selection is great but would prob pass on the food.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4210518</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7917752</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:18:37  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Kosta V.'s Review of Top of the Mark - San Francisco (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/top-of-the-mark-san-francisco#hrid:EJ3QxYlrVe_3z23o8nx2BQ</link>
			<description>Enjoy the view from somewhere else. Waitstaff is snobby and pretentious for no reason.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.410408258</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7916932695</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:18:26  PST</pubDate>
			<title>wally i.'s Review of ClickAway Mobile - Verizon Wireless Premium Retailer - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/clickaway-mobile-verizon-wireless-premium-retailer-san-francisco-2#hrid:Ub90fnHc-7EXOCI0pD3kQA</link>
			<description>I first met Jimmy Lee in 2012 and then sent friends who purchased a phone and a plan.
Since then I have returned twice; once for my husband and this week to check out a new phone for myself.
This is…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4537025</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7818486</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:17:44  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Ken T.'s Review of Target - Alameda (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/target-alameda-4#hrid:eNRbm0IwmbT0ODLmTxtBuw</link>
			<description>Wow this Target is HUGE! too bad it's not 24hrs. I live much closer to this new target, I no longer have to travel to Emeryville, that's a big plus for me. Place was neat and tidy and well stocked. I…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2819065</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7837433</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:15:49  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Ribec F.'s Review of Russian Hill Academy - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/russian-hill-academy-san-francisco#hrid:pCRJpp0OwZ0T5tHzL081qw</link>
			<description>Amazing program I feel so lucky that my son got a spot here. If you want a mandarin immersion program this is the one. The school is super clean, organized and the kids are well cared for. I plan to…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.421495</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7988985</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:15:18  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Fattfreddie F.'s Review of 1000 Years Clinics - OPEN 7 DAYS - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/1000-years-clinics-open-7-days-san-francisco#hrid:kRUG5tkREWKA6FWa9I3IXg</link>
			<description>A little more than a year later, and I must say that 1000 Years has only gotten better. My renewal was smooth and simple, and Dr. Ari continued to show compassionate professionalism. I'll be a patient…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.417606</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7765181</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:14:08  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Tiff W.'s Review of Fitness SF - San Francisco (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/fitness-sf-san-francisco#hrid:GLDyO4VUxT4LzZ4H63oaQg</link>
			<description>notch up from 24 fitness =)</description>
			<geo:long>-122.406948</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.769594</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:13:49  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Rommel H.'s Review of The Home Depot - San Mateo (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-home-depot-san-mateo-3#hrid:KTgxkpHNB0zCzdVt_lSZTA</link>
			<description>I wish Yelp allowed negative reviews. I have heard horror stories of this place but thought, this cannot be true.

Long story short, I am renovating a business having different contractors in and out.…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.280750235</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.5638703765</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:13:48  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Lisa P.'s Review of Professor Plumb - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/professor-plumb-san-francisco#hrid:Awk2qQq14adeZ3FLA-3v3A</link>
			<description>I love Professor Plumb!     We were in need of kitchen sink, bathroom sink and shower valve repair and they were on top of it.       Sean and crew came over twice and both times they were very…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4150537</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7638958</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:13:48  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Tiff W.'s Review of Shabu House - Burlingame (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/shabu-house-burlingame#hrid:d31yKzLcUp9iwg7pxUbTpw</link>
			<description>really slow service but servers were nice. i didn't enjoy my experience as much this time due to other patrons making too much noise.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.3646977</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.5853489</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:12:40  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Davis J.'s Review of The Liberty Cafe - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-liberty-cafe-san-francisco#hrid:E1PR5_HjZQsY_r3Rsm2zMA</link>
			<description>Gotta leave these folks a five star review. We had an incredible meal here that was so exceptional because:
- the service was fantastic
- they had lovely music by a live mandolin/guitar duo in the…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.41714</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.73912</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:12:30  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Ken T.'s Review of Shooting Star Cafe - Oakland (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/shooting-star-cafe-oakland#hrid:xpJfRGzZp9PYrVSEtW3D1g</link>
			<description>I love the new space! They tore the wall between 2 commercial spaces and combined them together. It seats way more people now. The decor is fabulous! Pretty blue LED fiber optic lighting and starry…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2701346</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8011926</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:11:40  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Imran M.'s Review of Temple Nightclub - San Francisco (2/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/temple-nightclub-san-francisco-2#hrid:GcKnVPb72MJff_YvjMrgSQ</link>
			<description>This review is strictly for their Halloween party on 11/1/13. I am only giving them two stars because the decor was well done and the staff were friendly but damn, the drinks were bumped up to…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.3971219</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7877156</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:10:33  PST</pubDate>
			<title>SoCal Foodie M.'s Review of Health Feet Massage - San Francisco (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/health-feet-massage-san-francisco#hrid:OCpBdTte3WV1Nn1ZXOql7g</link>
			<description>Horrible... they don't change the towels in between customers. Gross!!! they did it infront of me...really?

its like a massage sweat shop. pictures are better than they are. never coming back.
And…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4219784</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7658389</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:09:36  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Keith G.'s Review of San Francisco Marriott Union Square - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/san-francisco-marriott-union-square-san-francisco-3#hrid:ZQRHMrMY1V2A6S88hyC-mA</link>
			<description>The lobby bar is a hidden gem. The menu is decent and the drinks are well made. 
The wine selection would be the main reason to come to this place. 
Highly recommended for small groups. Also an…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4082675</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7893949</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:08:26  PST</pubDate>
			<title>John M.'s Review of Ramon Garcia Plastering - Berkeley (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/ramon-garcia-plastering-berkeley#hrid:qUR6XK_N6VSNqop6N4Mkdg</link>
			<description>I am a licensed contractor with 10 years' experience and have worked with Ramon on a number of occasions. I wish I could give him more than 5 stars. He is one of the most skilled, organized and…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2513374</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8620156</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:07:36  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Elisa F.'s Review of CREAM - Berkeley (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/cream-berkeley-2#hrid:SGSjIiXC5WebcAPUJT6ltA</link>
			<description>Every time we go to Berkeley, we've seen a line around the block for this place. At 9:30 Friday night, the crowd had finally dispersed, so hubby and I decided to go in and see what all the hype was…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2587134</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8670217</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 10:07:11  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Nila N.'s Review of CertaPro Painters of Berkeley - Oakland (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/certapro-painters-of-berkeley-oakland#hrid:4p6TfsaJQVSkws9YGSJLpQ</link>
			<description>My Spanish-style home exterior was recently painted by CertaPro and I could not be more pleased. The house is one-story in front and three-story in back. The ground slopes on three sides, and is very…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2865477</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8149125</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:46:38  PST</pubDate>
			<title>J S.'s Review of Tempest Bar - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/tempest-bar-san-francisco#hrid:BeY3mEn-Y6Acbl5A8e_7Kg</link>
			<description>Tempest Bar is MY BAR OF CHOICE! It's such a wonderful feeling for an adult of age to have a regular bar to go to with your friends &amp; coworkers where you always feel at home &amp; with some seriously…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.406289056</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7811864641</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:45:22  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Alejandro E.'s Review of San Francisco Bay Computer Services - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/san-francisco-bay-computer-services-san-francisco-2#hrid:WbL1FUuyEjn1t20yDushqw</link>
			<description>Mi hermanito me dijo que le prestara mi laptop, se la preste y como 2 horas más tarde me la regreso y me dijo que él había bajado unos juegos del internet,  cuando la trate de encender me di cuenta…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4180284</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7493772</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:51  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Captain B.'s Review of Za Gourmet Pizza - San Francisco (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/za-gourmet-pizza-san-francisco#hrid:HlrHSlCh46GAgas4AiOYHQ</link>
			<description>The reviews are great, but honestly this is just another average pizza delivery place. I'm a bit shocked by all of the 5 star reviews.

Delivery was pretty fast, though the guy on the phone was a bit…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4190622</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7985523</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:44  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Matt S.'s Review of Elios Family Restaurant - San Leandro (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/elios-family-restaurant-san-leandro#hrid:-Yws_llnrilwUQ5zrsxVGw</link>
			<description>Big portions.  Great breakfast food anytime of the day.  I come here at least four times a month.  The crowd here is a bit older but a lot of younger adults are starting to come here also.  They are…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.14207</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.70138</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:23  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Nancy K.'s Review of Nan King Road Bistro - San Francisco (2/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/nan-king-road-bistro-san-francisco#hrid:AOTfbm2rsa5TErR0bRnM4Q</link>
			<description>Food took too long to come out (waited almost an hour), &amp; when it did come out, half the dishes had already gone cold. We ordered beef for one dish, but they brought chicken instead, so ended up with…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4661412</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7629304</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:44:05  PST</pubDate>
			<title>C J.'s Review of CB Tyler Carpenter - Emeryville (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/cb-tyler-carpenter-emeryville-3#hrid:eeo0BILSvWlffDOBTwPe3g</link>
			<description>A friend recommended Cassie Tyler as a great local general contractor with a specialization in carpentry, and based on her work I would highly recommend her to anyone looking for a contractor in the…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.291802</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.840701</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:43:36  PST</pubDate>
			<title>shakun k.'s Review of Nopalito - San Francisco (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/nopalito-san-francisco-3#hrid:edI0KwV25IH7essEnBPS3g</link>
			<description>Great spot for some delightfully good small plates and drinks. The ambience was very trendy with an interesting waitstaff. The dishes brought together a ton of different, clean and fresh flavors which…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4661653</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7654223</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:42:49  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Larry L.'s Review of Apple Store - San Francisco (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/apple-store-san-francisco-2#hrid:aFWLzulS7vmMAgGLL7RnIg</link>
			<description>The customer service reps are usually more than happy to answer questions or help you figure something out.  As an example, we were looking at cases for my GF's new phone.  A customer service rep came…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4064402</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7858516</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:42:33  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Sum W.'s Review of Salena Lee, OD - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/salena-lee-od-san-francisco#hrid:SCHQ8adVrdNN7hzsLmJ42Q</link>
			<description>Keeping it short.  It always feels so comfortable and warm when i walk into this place.  Nothing beats people knowing your name when you walk in through the door.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4795556</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7538576</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:41:06  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Carlton O.'s Review of Bourbon &amp; Beef - Oakland (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/bourbon-and-beef-oakland#hrid:ol4PY6IDsnRmiq0rXZLRfw</link>
			<description>Great new place on College. Had the Mussels, ribeye, Puerco con Curtido, lobster bisque,  All really good but really liked the mussels.  Hurts to say this but the mussels are better than a cote.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.251403</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8437709</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:40:52  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Andy G.'s Review of 7 Days A Week Smog Test - Berkeley (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/7-days-a-week-smog-test-berkeley-5#hrid:kei4_ftbqAd4NlfXMMqNLA</link>
			<description>This place is great. I went in this morning (a Sunday) and had such a nice experience in a business where I guess I wasn't expecting an awful lot. Mike was friendly and squared away, greeted me…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2911786</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8651953</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:40:52  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Debby C.'s Review of Brazil Fresh Squeeze Cafe - Berkeley (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/brazil-fresh-squeeze-cafe-berkeley#hrid:O1W4ZnbOBWb9nNdd-cd-NQ</link>
			<description>Great fresh bread and flavorful, juicy chicken at a reasonable price - did not try the famous tri tip though.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.266746457</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8725528522</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:40:44  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Melody K.'s Review of The Bashful Bull Too - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-bashful-bull-too-san-francisco#hrid:YIvOuVNlOC74TpBPyd9DWQ</link>
			<description>We love this place when we want a good filling breakfast. Clean, great food, friendly service : ) Pancakes and biscuits and gravy are my favorite!</description>
			<geo:long>-122.5048247</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7418804</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:37:24  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Melody K.'s Review of Park Chow - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/park-chow-san-francisco#hrid:eP3ybA5rwE129MaMwCLc_g</link>
			<description>Love this place. We like to sit upstairs. Food is delicious. Fish always cooked perfect and the spaghetti is my favorite.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4663968</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7651459</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:36:23  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Marie P.'s Review of Papa John&#39;s Pizza - San Francisco (4/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/papa-johns-pizza-san-francisco#hrid:hfOV1aBfC_xMm9G6obK9_g</link>
			<description>Here's how the millions of dollars in Football advertising works wonders. 
While watching our amazing Forty Niners play the Titans the Papa Johns commercial comes on, and we are craving for pizza. We…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4744066</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7177556</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:36:08  PST</pubDate>
			<title>David D.'s Review of Purple Kow - San Francisco (2/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/purple-kow-san-francisco-2#hrid:-8frYe82K3rMslSPGrEGkA</link>
			<description>the boba taste alright.  Def not the best I have ever had.  The one upside is the size of the boba and the price.  I don't think I have ever had this much boba milk tea for its price, but for me the…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.49782</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.775905</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:36:06  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Charlotte K.'s Review of Masson Veterinary Hospital - San Bruno (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/masson-veterinary-hospital-san-bruno#hrid:7F0M8wHN3_gyM4VrdkoKxA</link>
			<description>Wondering why there are only great reviews and one bad one, for cats at least. I don't like seeing such a imbalance as it spells out that this business is feeding the good reviews.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4137939</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.6300767</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:35:21  PST</pubDate>
			<title>shakun k.'s Review of Tonga Room &amp; Hurricane Bar - San Francisco (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/tonga-room-and-hurricane-bar-san-francisco#hrid:LoROilzPyIDvnS_jlJSk6g</link>
			<description>The ambience of this place is quite childish especially with the fake rain dripping in a pool, and the overly generic music. The wait staff is mehhh, and the doormen think this place is something…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4105175</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7923392</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:35:01  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Holla F.'s Review of Bacheesos - Oakland (3/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/bacheesos-oakland#hrid:HnkguEEEpf0PfN581pThaA</link>
			<description>Came here for the lunch Buffett. The spread looked beautiful and colorful. It's a good spot if you're vegetarian or beef eater. The salmon was dry or overbooked, but the one chicken option was pretty…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.258968</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.809921</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:34:35  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Melody K.'s Review of Green Chile Kitchen - San Francisco (2/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/green-chile-kitchen-san-francisco#hrid:MySWrZtndQrROgenqVI6-g</link>
			<description>Great food but they can never get my order right. Simple things like no green chili inside the burrito. Pork tamales when I ordered chicken. Happened about 4 times. You can't tell if the order is…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.441843608</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7772354305</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:34:03  PST</pubDate>
			<title>David D.'s Review of The Sweet House - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-sweet-house-san-francisco#hrid:r3oAh1XHJ6H18-PBf7s9qw</link>
			<description>This is the best place for some solid milk tea.  I usually get the almond milk tea with pearls.  The boba here is made fresh and always chewy.  I would come here over purple kow any day.  The service…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4964786</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7757684</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:33:40  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Erika E.'s Review of Nabi Salon - Burlingame (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/nabi-salon-burlingame#hrid:dTMhurWfnDtxn3p4gZfXhg</link>
			<description>Su Kim is the best! She recently did my hair and makeup for my wedding and did a fantastic job! We did a trial and I was hooked. I showed her what I wanted and she did exactly that and it came out…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.365511</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.585167</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:33:12  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Jackson Z.'s Review of Shooting Star Cafe - Oakland (1/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/shooting-star-cafe-oakland#hrid:-HCD43aCYp_sKZtDlQQ_bA</link>
			<description>the service was sucks, because when they tell you to wait a mins, they never come back to make your order. The food takes hella to be make.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.2701346</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.8011926</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:32:37  PST</pubDate>
			<title>Matthew G.'s Review of Amy&#39;s Hallmark - San Mateo (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/amys-hallmark-san-mateo#hrid:QqwFZGS07L33oTji3lrNCg</link>
			<description>from 99 cent cards to over 10 dollar cards.  this hallmark has a lot to offer.  bdays, congrats, sad, happy, thanks. they got it all.  stuffed animals, holiday theme gifts.  even lil donuts, oj, and…</description>
			<geo:long>-122.284055</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.559684</geo:lat>
		</item>
		<item>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 15:32:02  PST</pubDate>
			<title>David D.'s Review of Zephyr Cafe - San Francisco (5/5) on Yelp</title>
			<link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/zephyr-cafe-san-francisco#hrid:5NXgx-u6K7pcE-CrQP8rrg</link>
			<description>I use to come to this cafe a lot to study and work on my computer.  The drinks and food are standard, but the atmosphere here is great.  The spot is big and the booths are my favorite place to site.</description>
			<geo:long>-122.4981397</geo:long>
			<geo:lat>37.7755883</geo:lat>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>