<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Mia Love</title><description>Remarks of Mia Love to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Let me tell you about the America I know.</title></item><item><title>My parents immigrated to the U.S. with ten dollars in their pocket, believing that the America they had heard about really did exist.</title></item><item><title>When times got tough they didn't look to Washington, they looked within.</title></item><item><title>So the America I came to know was centered in personal responsibility and filled with the American dream.</title></item><item><title>The America I know is grounded in the determination found in patriots and pioneers, in small business owners with big ideas, in the farmers who work in the beauty of our landscape, in our heroic military and Olympians.</title></item><item><title>It's in every child who looks at the seemingly impossible and says, "I can do that." That is the America I know! President Obama's version of America is a divided one -- pitting us against each other based on our income level, gender, and social status.</title></item><item><title>His policies have failed! We are not better off than we were 4 years ago, and no rhetoric, bumper sticker, or campaign ad can change that.</title></item><item><title>Mr. President I am here to tell you we are not buying what you are selling in 2012.</title></item><item><title>The American Dream is our story.</title></item><item><title>It is a story of human struggle, standing up and striving for more.</title></item><item><title>It's been told for over 200 years with small steps and giant leaps; from a woman on a bus to a man with a dream; and the bravery of the greatest generation, to the entrepreneurs of today.</title></item><item><title>This is our story.</title></item><item><title>This is the America we know because we built it.</title></item><item><title>With Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan we can restore the America we know and love.</title></item><item><title>The world will know it, our children will tell it and our grandchildren will possess it for years to come! God bless America. </title></item></channel></rss>