<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Deb Fischer</title><description>Remarks of Deb Fischer to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Thank you. I'm not your typical politician. I'm a wife. I'm a mother of three grown sons, a rancher, a small business owner and a citizen-legislator.</title></item><item><title>Becoming a U.S. Senator has never been an ambition of mine.</title></item><item><title>But over the last four years, I've become dismayed with the record spending, the record debt, and the record unemployment.</title></item><item><title>The Obama administration has been out of touch with the American people, and they've driven our country towards the edge of a fiscal cliff.</title></item><item><title>We're on track to become the first generation that passes on fewer opportunities to the next.</title></item><item><title>And that is unacceptable.</title></item><item><title>But it doesn't have to be this way. I'm running for the U.S. Senate because I know we can do better. I've been a Senator in the Nebraska legislature these past eight years.</title></item><item><title>And in Nebraska, we have an unemployment rate of only 4 percent.</title></item><item><title>How did we get there? We cut spending.</title></item><item><title>We balance our budget every year.</title></item><item><title>We passed the biggest tax relief package in the history of our state.</title></item><item><title>And most importantly, we got government out of the way and let the private sector do what it does best: grow our economy and create jobs.</title></item><item><title>We've done it in Nebraska, and I know we can do the same thing in Washington, because we only have two options left.</title></item><item><title>We can either continue the same failed policies of the past, or we can begin to make the tough decisions and lead our country responsibly.</title></item><item><title>We have a tremendous opportunity to set our country in a new, more prosperous direction, and it begins in November.</title></item><item><title>Thank you so much, and may God Bless America. </title></item></channel></rss>