<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>John Sununu</title><description>Remarks of John Sununu to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>In these critical times America needs a leader. Our economy is stagnant. Our vitality has been sapped. Our confidence is down. We are saddled with a failed presidency, with an incumbent president who has not led. America needs real change, and we are here to affirm a leader who will produce that change. There are many reasons America needs Mitt Romney at the helm. We have 23 million Americans unemployed or underemployed because Barack Obama cannot figure out what makes free enterprise work. Mitt Romney will get our private sector moving again, and will respect the successes of our entrepreneurs who deserve credit because they really did build it. In these difficult times our nation still depends on others for our energy resources ­ even though we share the largest overall supplies of energy in the world ­ because we have an administration that shuns those assets and keeps us dependent on fragile foreign supplies. Mitt Romney will unshackle our assets, and lead us to real energy independence.</title></item><item><title>We also are a nation that has seen erosion of our respect around the world because we have a president who prefers to lead from behind. Mitt Romney will restore our strength, support our friends, face up to our foes and regain honest respect for an America willing to lead. My wife Nancy and I have gotten to know Mitt and Ann Romney well. We have developed a deep and sincere appreciation for these two friends and their family ­ we like them and we respect them. Tonight we all gather here to put in motion the final phase of our campaign to help America know them better, and to appreciate why our nation needs them as our president and first lady. Mitt Romney is a good man, and a smart man. He is compassionate and generous. He is a great father and a supportive friend. He has been a very successful businessman and a very effective governor. He knows how to fix the unfixable, and to help people perform to their highest potential. Mitt Romney is the right man at the right time and will be a great leader for our country. It is my honor to nominate Mitt Romney for the Office of President of the United States of America. </title></item></channel></rss>