<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Rob Portman</title><description>Remarks of Rob Portman to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Good evening America, and hello to the fired-up delegation from the Buckeye State right in front of me.</title></item><item><title>My name is Rob Portman and they say I was on Governor Romney's short list of vice presidential candidates.</title></item><item><title>Apparently, it wasn't short enough.</title></item><item><title>But it's been a great convention and I am delighted to be here tonight to talk about the fundamental differences between Mitt Romney and Barack Obama when it comes to understanding our economy.</title></item><item><title>Let's begin by talking about something the Democrats love to demonize - Mitt Romney's success in the private sector.</title></item><item><title>He built a company from the ground up, created lots of jobs, and yes, he made money.</title></item><item><title>He made it the old fashioned way . . . He earned it.</title></item><item><title>Then you have Barack Obama, who has never started a business--never even worked in business.</title></item><item><title>And he claims those who have should give credit to the government or someone else for their success.</title></item><item><title>So, you have one candidate who understands that success comes from working hard, competing and taking risks.</title></item><item><title>And you have another candidate who believes success comes from government.</title></item><item><title>Which one do you think knows how to turn this economy around? Which one would you choose to invest your life's savings?</title></item><item><title>Should it be any different for safeguarding our nation's economy? Or let's say you don't have any savings.</title></item><item><title>Let's say you're worried about how to pay September's rent or mortgage.</title></item><item><title>Let's say you are one of the millions of Americans out of work or the millions more who have given up looking.</title></item><item><title>You've gotta be running out of patience ­ and hope.</title></item><item><title>You have to be tired, looking for a new start.</title></item><item><title>Well, you don't have to be patient any longer.</title></item><item><title>Through your vote this fall you can change the leadership of this country and the opportunities for you and your family.</title></item><item><title>America, it has been nearly four years of over eight percent unemployment ­ and double digit unemployment for young people, Hispanics and African-Americans.</title></item><item><title>Four years. FDR and Truman won an entire world war in four years.</title></item><item><title>America is tired of waiting.</title></item><item><title>In business, if you don't move rapidly, you are out of business.</title></item><item><title>You are finished.</title></item><item><title>We want a president who operates at business speed not government speed.</title></item><item><title>President Obama says he deserves reelection because his economic policies have worked. NOT in this universe they haven't.</title></item><item><title>In fact, the experts tell us that if we don't change our policies we are going back into recession next year.</title></item><item><title>Tens of millions of Americans are not out of the last recession! Governor Romney had a plan to build his business.</title></item><item><title>He now has a detailed plan to restore our economy and strengthen the middle class. I ask you: Where is the president's economic plan? Blaming others does not qualify as a plan.</title></item><item><title>Now the president did submit a budget.</title></item><item><title>It was so bad that not a single Republican or a single Democrat in the entire United States Congress would vote for it.</title></item><item><title>He got zero votes.</title></item><item><title>That is a failure of leadership.</title></item><item><title>President Obama has been right about at least one prediction he's made about the economy.</title></item><item><title>He said, "If I don't have this done in three years, then there's going to be a one-term proposition." I think you are right about that, Mr.</title></item><item><title>President.</title></item><item><title>It hasn't worked, because you cannot spend your way, regulate your way, tax your way or blame your way out of the economic mess we are in.</title></item><item><title>You have to liberate the productive power of the American people through policies that encourage innovation, risk taking, investment and jobs.</title></item><item><title>And you have to compete and win in the global economy.</title></item><item><title>Governor Romney understands this.</title></item><item><title>In contrast, President Obama is the first president in 75 years--Democrat or Republican--who hasn't even sought the ability to negotiate export agreements and open markets overseas.</title></item><item><title>Now why is this important? Because 95 percent of the world's consumers live outside our borders.</title></item><item><title>And to create jobs, our workers and our farmers need to sell more of what we make to those people.</title></item><item><title>While this administration has been dragging its feet, other countries have been busy negotiating hundreds of new trade agreements to benefit their workers and their farmers, taking away our opportunities.</title></item><item><title>President Obama has been so driven to advance his big government ideology that he has abandoned the daily economic work that a government must do to open markets, restore business confidence and create the climate for job growth.</title></item><item><title>This is the work President Romney would begin on day one.</title></item><item><title>Take trade with China.</title></item><item><title>China manipulates its currency giving it an unfair trade advantage.</title></item><item><title>So why doesn't the president do something about it? I'll tell you one reason ­ President Obama could not run up his record trillion dollar deficits if the Chinese did not buy our bonds to finance them.</title></item><item><title>We are as beholden to China for bonds as we are to the Middle East for oil.</title></item><item><title>This will end under Mitt Romney.</title></item><item><title>We need to knock down these trade barriers abroad, but we also need to knock down the selfimposed barriers to success right here at home.</title></item><item><title>We need to reform our outdated and complicated tax code.</title></item><item><title>We need to fix our burdensome regulatory system and we need an energy policy that encourages development of our resources right here, in the ground, in America.</title></item><item><title>America has a choice between Mitt Romney, who seeks to grow the economy, and Barack Obama who seeks to redistribute it.</title></item><item><title>Which one do you think will liberate America's entrepreneurial spirit? At the other party's convention, you will hear the chant, "Four more years.</title></item><item><title>Four more years." Folks ­ we can't afford four more years.</title></item><item><title>How about no more years? Governor Romney chose a terrific partner in Paul Ryan of Wisconsin ­ Paul is a close friend with a great family and a reformer's heart.</title></item><item><title>Vice President Biden has told people out of work to just, "hang in there." So much for hope and change.</title></item><item><title>Paul Ryan is not asking America to continue to hang in there.</title></item><item><title>He is proposing new policies that will give poor and middle class families opportunities and hope for the future.</title></item><item><title>Mitt Romney made his mark turning around businesses and solving problems.</title></item><item><title>Paul Ryan made his mark as a respected reformer focused on results.</title></item><item><title>Together they will do what President Obama has not done: They will lead in breaking through the partisan gridlock in Washington, D.C. America, give them the chance to restore America's economy and restore the American dream. I have seen that dream up close.</title></item><item><title>When I was a kid, my dad left his job as a salesman and started his own business selling forklift trucks.</title></item><item><title>My Mom was the bookkeeper.</title></item><item><title>He had to borrow money from her uncle because the bank wouldn't give him a loan.</title></item><item><title>He lost money for the first few years, but he never lost his dream.</title></item><item><title>And by the time he retired and my brother took over, the business had 200 employees ­ supporting 200 families in Southwest Ohio.</title></item><item><title>This is the classic American story ­ not of government telling us what to do ­ but of free men and free women willing to work hard and take a risk to build something of value for themselves, their families and their community.</title></item><item><title>About a year into the Obama Administration ­ I asked my dad whether he would do it again.</title></item><item><title>He said, "Rob ­ with all the uncertainty out there today ­ I don't know if I would take the risk." In that one sentence, he summed up what I've heard from hundreds of small business owners across Ohio and around this great country.</title></item><item><title>They're afraid to make the investment and jobs are the casualty.</title></item><item><title>Ladies and gentlemen, we need new leadership and new policies to bring back the dream and renew America's promise.</title></item><item><title>No more excuses, no more blaming others, no more waiting.</title></item><item><title>We need Romney /Ryan and we need them now! And with your help, it will happen.</title></item><item><title>Thank you and God bless our great country. </title></item></channel></rss>