<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Dan Benishek</title><description>Remarks of Dan Benishek to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Thank you.</title></item><item><title>My story is like many from Northern Michigan. I grew up in a little town called Iron River.</title></item><item><title>My family didn't have much when I was growing up and we lost my dad when I was young.</title></item><item><title>But I worked hard, saved money, and was able to become a doctor and raise my family in Northern Michigan.</title></item><item><title>That was my American Dream.</title></item><item><title>Along the way, it never occurred to me to get into politics, let alone run for Congress.</title></item><item><title>But I did, two years ago.</title></item><item><title>Because, like many of you, I was disgusted by what was going on in Washington.</title></item><item><title>They are spending away our children's and grandchildren's futures.</title></item><item><title>Today, the American Dream is being threatened. I know our nation is facing enormous challenges.</title></item><item><title>Unemployment is far too high.</title></item><item><title>We have a nearly $16 trillion debt.</title></item><item><title>It's hard for Michigan families to make ends meet.</title></item><item><title>But I believe we can fix these problems by staying true to what has always made this country great: individual liberty, free enterprise, and limited government.</title></item><item><title>People from Northern Michigan are tough.</title></item><item><title>We don't give up when times are hard.</title></item><item><title>Like you, we will keep working to protect the American Dream, and to ensure our best days are yet to come.</title></item><item><title>So we need you to keep the American Dream alive and deliver this election for America.</title></item><item><title>Thank you and may God bless you all. </title></item></channel></rss>