<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Reince Priebus Chairman2</title><description>Remarks of Reince Priebus Chairman2 to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the 2012 Republican National Convention! Once again, we thank the people of Tampa for their hospitality. Tonight, we embark on a path toward A Better Future. Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will lead us. Our timeless, tested Republican principles will light the way. Free enterprise, individual opportunity, limited government. They made America great; only they can keep America strong. The last four years under President Obama have been trying and troubling for this entire country. The tired big government policies of the past have failed us. We can't afford more disappointments. We need a new direction. We need a new president. I know just the man for the job. He's a family man and a businessman. He spent his career building successful companies. Then, he saved the 2002 Olympics and brought pride to our nation. As governor, he balanced the budget, cut taxes, and created jobs. The president America needs is Mitt Romney! Governor Romney has a record of tremendous accomplishments. But he never asks for accolades. He just asks, "How can I help?" That's the mark of a true leader: A humble focus on getting the job done. Mitt Romney spent his life turning around failing enterprises, and America needs a turnaround. Specifically, we need Barack Obama to turn around and go back to Chicago. Let me tell you about my friend Paul Ryan--a man of true integrity. He doesn't descend to the gutter politics of the other side. He rises above it to chart a better path. He's my buddy, my congressman, and I can't wait to call him our vice president!</title></item><item><title>And won't it be nice to have a second-in-command who can spend his days doing more than prying his foot out of his mouth? Paul and Janna's three children are the lights of their lives. In Congress, Paul doesn't worry about his political future. He worries about his children's future. In the same way, Sally and I worry about the future of our two kids, Jack and Grace. Their future is in jeopardy because President Obama has added five trillion dollars to the national debt for all our children to pay off. That's unacceptable. Our Founders did not declare our independence only to see us become dependent on the borrowed money of foreign nations. We still have time to chart a better course. But if Barack Obama gets four more years, it might be too late. We're not just spending borrowed money; we're living on borrowed time. Look at the record of the outgoing administration: 23 million Americans, struggling for work. Forty-two months of unemployment over 8 percent. The worst jobs record since the Great Depression. It's time to elect Mitt Romney so we can get moving on the Great Recovery. Now the Obama apologists in the mainstream media - they say, oh, it's not his fault. Well, I have news for the media. We know things were bad. But that's no excuse for making things worse. Four years ago, Barack Obama was an unproven leader. Today, he has proven himself. He has proven that he's not up to the job. Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will be up to the job on Day One. Like Paul Ryan, I'm from Wisconsin, where Republicans have done pretty well in recent years. Here's why: because we governed like we campaigned. We made promises and we kept promises. That's what Americans want - leaders of their word. President Obama is a man of many words - but he's not a man of his word. He broke his promise to cut the deficit in half. And he broke his promise to fix the economy. And adding insult to injury, he actually attacks success. This president looks down on American free enterprise. He says, "If you've got a business, you didn't build that." That makes me think Barack Obama has a problem with the American Dream. I grew up in a place called Kenosha, Wisconsin. My dad was a union electrician and retired from the Racine Unified School District. You know, when we drove through town, he didn't point at that big beautiful house on the corner and say, "Hey look at those lousy people over here."</title></item><item><title>He did what every one of your parents did. He said, "Listen up pal, if you work hard and go to school, you're going to be in that house. And mom and dad pray it's three times bigger." No parent, Democrat or Republican, wants the kind of negative, glass-half-empty view of America that President Obama is trying to sell. We're the party that celebrates success, that believes in the American Dream and wants all of our children to have a chance to succeed. So this convention is an invitation to all Americans to join us as we fight for a better future. This is our generation's Rendezvous with Destiny. It's our Time for Choosing. If you believe America can do better than the last four years, we stand with you. If you believe the next generation deserves a shot at the American Dream, Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan stand with you. Thank you and God bless. </title></item></channel></rss>