<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bob Buckhorn</title><description>Remarks of Bob Buckhorn to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>To Chairman Priebus and to my fellow Americans who have traveled from every corner of this great country to be in Tampa today, thank you for the honor to be hosting the 2012 Republican National Convention.</title></item><item><title>Your faith and trust in us is much appreciated.</title></item><item><title>Now, let me tell you about my city.</title></item><item><title>We were built by people who worked hard and dreamed big.</title></item><item><title>Immigrant families came here from Germany, Spain, Italy, and Cuba.</title></item><item><title>They were cigar rollers and port workers.</title></item><item><title>They were the economic engine that powered Tampa Bay.</title></item><item><title>Today, we are a city that represents all that is good about America.</title></item><item><title>We are leading Florida out of the recession.</title></item><item><title>Unemployment is declining faster here than almost anywhere else.</title></item><item><title>We are one of the fastest growing cities in the country.</title></item><item><title>We've been called one of the best American cities to do business.</title></item><item><title>We are attracting some of the brightest young people who want to be part of our tech industry.</title></item><item><title>We are curing diseases -- on the cutting edge of science and health care.</title></item><item><title>And, Tampa remains proud to be the home of MacDill Air Force Base - the headquarters of the United States Central Command and Special Operations Command. I can tell you with certainty that we are open for business and are ready to embrace all that the future holds.</title></item><item><title>As mayor, I stand here today representing an extraordinary group of law enforcement, fire rescue personnel, and thousands of local volunteers.</title></item><item><title>They have worked hard to make this convention a success.</title></item><item><title>Each of them, proud Americans, excited to be part of the democratic process and eager to tell Tampa's story to the world. I trust you will fall in love with our city just as I do every day.</title></item><item><title>Have a great week in Tampa! </title></item></channel></rss>