<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Brian Sandoval</title><description>Remarks of Brian Sandoval to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Thank you. I stand here tonight humbled to share with you the story of a nation, a state and of one man.</title></item><item><title>It is the story of America itself ­ of courageous, freedom-loving visionaries who believed in the promise of opportunity, rather than the divine right of kings.</title></item><item><title>Who dared to dream that anyone could rise above the circumstances of their birth.</title></item><item><title>It is also the story of the great Silver State: Battle Born Nevada! We joined the Union to help keep Abraham Lincoln in the White House and fulfill the promise of opportunity, as he ended forever the scourge of slavery.</title></item><item><title>And, it is my story: the child of working-class Hispanic Americans who has lived the American dream.</title></item><item><title>The Proverbs tell us "from small beginnings come great things." My father was one of ten children.</title></item><item><title>My mother and her family lived in a tiny, two-bedroom house in the Southwest.</title></item><item><title>Dad worked his entire career as an aviation technician.</title></item><item><title>Mom was a legal secretary who became a teacher.</title></item><item><title>We lived a simple American life.</title></item><item><title>When I was a boy, my parents brought us to Nevada in search of opportunity.</title></item><item><title>My first job was cleaning sheep pens.</title></item><item><title>In college, I worked in a hospital cafeteria. I worked my way through law school.</title></item><item><title>Encouraged by my parents' love for this country, I dreamed of public service. I became a state legislator, a gaming regulator, and attorney general of my state.</title></item><item><title>My story could end there, but this is America.</title></item><item><title>And so, in 2005, a simple son of promise was appointed by President Bush, and confirmed by the United States Senate as a federal judge. I saw in my courtroom the fulfillment of all that our forefathers sought to create. A nation of laws. A nation of due process and merit and justice for all.</title></item><item><title>And, yes, a nation of immigrants.</title></item><item><title>One of the greatest duties I performed was to administer the oath of citizenship to new Americans ­ immigrants who embody our dream of opportunity and prosperity.</title></item><item><title>But from the federal bench, I also saw a nation beset on all sides by unprecedented challenges. I watched my state's economy falter, stagnate and slide into decline.</title></item><item><title>Nevadans lost their jobs and their homes.</title></item><item><title>Nevada was hit hardest by the recession ­ highest unemployment, highest foreclosure rate, highest bankruptcy rate.</title></item><item><title>Like so many, I looked around for help.</title></item><item><title>And what did I find? A president who promised change, but turned instead to the same tired strategy of ever-larger government. A president who abandoned hope and embraced only blame.</title></item><item><title>So I stepped down from a lifetime appointment to make a difference. I ran for governor, was elected and, like Republican governors all across this nation, I chose to make the tough decisions: On issues like economic development, education reform and redesigning how state government operates.</title></item><item><title>On job creation, and reducing state spending, and eliminating red tape.</title></item><item><title>It hasn't been easy.</title></item><item><title>And we're not through it yet.</title></item><item><title>But I have put my faith in the people of my great state ­ because they are the ones who will grow our economy. I have seen Hispanic business owners and families from backgrounds -- not unlike my own -struggle in this economy. I have seen young children from all walks of life begin to wonder if their future holds any hope at all.</title></item><item><title>Make no mistake: The current administration's failed experiment with big government gets in the way of economic recovery.</title></item><item><title>Their love affair with government regulation is a drag on business confidence.</title></item><item><title>From personal experience, I can tell you what will help states like Nevada and families like mine: elect the team that understands how to get America working again.</title></item><item><title>Send Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan to the White House! This administration sings the siren song that this is all there is.</title></item><item><title>They tell us government is the answer, but we know it's the problem.</title></item><item><title>They tell us we didn't build our businesses, but somebody else made it happen.</title></item><item><title>They tell us not to dream but to settle.</title></item><item><title>You and I know America is better than that.</title></item><item><title>Our national story is one of confronting challenges ­ and winning.</title></item><item><title>We have overcome economic devastation, defeated mighty oppressors and lifted up generation after generation of Americans.</title></item><item><title>We can ­ and we will ­ do it again.</title></item><item><title>For that is our birthright as members of the American family ­ white, black, Hispanic, Asian, immigrant or descendent of the Founding Fathers themselves.</title></item><item><title>We must leave Tampa this week on a mission to remind Americans they deserve more than the status quo.</title></item><item><title>They deserve to dream big.</title></item><item><title>We must remind Americans that the promise of opportunity remains unbroken ­ that every person in this great nation can succeed through hard work, courage and personal responsibility.</title></item><item><title>For that is the real American story.</title></item><item><title>Thank you.</title></item><item><title>And now, let me introduce to you one of those Hispanic business owners that I mentioned are struggling in this economy, Mr.</title></item><item><title>Phil Archuletta of New Mexico.</title></item></channel></rss>