<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Steve King</title><description>Remarks of Steve King to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Good evening.</title></item><item><title>In two short months, our country faces a momentous decision.</title></item><item><title>We will decide whether to continue our slide into debt and dependence, or whether to restore opportunity and self-determination. I believe, at this time, America is looking for leadership.</title></item><item><title>Americans are searching for substance.</title></item><item><title>We are here tonight because Mitt Romney has chosen the first real leader of his generation, a man who can help us believe in America again -- and his name is Paul Ryan! We are here tonight, as Republicans, united and excited for a Romney-Ryan presidency! I remember talking with Paul when he was weighing his first congressional race.</title></item><item><title>Even at the age of 27, he was a man with big ideas and the courage of his convictions.</title></item><item><title>Paul's time in politics has been a family affair.</title></item><item><title>His brother Tobin helped lead Paul's first campaign.</title></item><item><title>His mother Betty and sister-in-law Oakleigh knocked on doors and handed out fliers.</title></item><item><title>Now Paul is joined by his wife Janna, his daughter Liza, and his sons Charlie and Sam.</title></item><item><title>You'll find them in church and later watching a Packers or Brewers game, or swapping hunting and fishing stories with family.</title></item><item><title>From his very first campaign, Paul Ryan asked voters directly: "Hire me." And has since always reminded his constituents: "Remember, I work for you!" He never forgets who he works for.</title></item><item><title>And no one has been more diligent and effective in working for the good of Wisconsin and America.</title></item><item><title>Paul Ryan has the courage to tell the truth ­ even when the truth is hard to hear.</title></item><item><title>Paul Ryan has big, thoughtful ideas.</title></item><item><title>Paul Ryan has the determination to tackle tough challenges ­ even those that others choose to ignore.</title></item><item><title>Paul Ryan is the leader we need at this critical moment in our nation's history.</title></item><item><title>Mitt Romney believes that.</title></item><item><title>Do we? Ladies and gentlemen, it is my singular great honor and distinct privilege to nominate my good friend, my fellow citizen of Janesville, Wisconsin, a genuinely good man from the Midwest -- Paul D. Ryan -- to be vice president of the United States of America! Thank you! </title></item></channel></rss>