<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Sher Valenzuela</title><description>Remarks of Sher Valenzuela to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Good evening.</title></item><item><title>My name is Sher Valenzuela.</title></item><item><title>Two years ago, I never would have imagined that I would be here tonight, speaking at the Republican National Convention. I've seen these on TV ­ what an honor to be here with you. I'm a mother from Delaware, a co-owner with my husband of First State Manufacturing.</title></item><item><title>And after this November, I plan on taking on a new title: the next Lieutenant Governor of the Great State of Delaware.</title></item><item><title>Tonight, it is my honor to talk about the three themes that inspired me to run for office:    My family.</title></item><item><title>The business we built.</title></item><item><title>And my belief in America's unlimited potential.</title></item><item><title>But it starts with a wonderful story.</title></item><item><title>Shortly after our son was born, my husband and I received some news that would change our lives forever.</title></item><item><title>We learned that our son Simon was autistic.</title></item><item><title>We loved him with every fiber in our being.</title></item><item><title>But the "experts" told us not to expect much. "Your son will never learn to read, write, or communicate effectively," they said. "Accept these limits," they seemed to say.</title></item><item><title>It was a tough time.</title></item><item><title>We quickly realized that the jobs we had wouldn't pay for the professionals Simon needed to overcome the odds.</title></item><item><title>So we followed a deep and long-standing American tradition.</title></item><item><title>We took a risk.</title></item><item><title>We bet on the future.</title></item><item><title>We started our own business.</title></item><item><title>When he was serving in the Army, my husband had taken a mail order course on upholstery.</title></item><item><title>One day I came home to find him pulling out the second hand sewing machine he'd learned his craft on.</title></item><item><title>He called her "Old Betsy." A second-generation Mexican-American, my husband will do whatever it takes to provide for his family.</title></item><item><title>Our friends thought we were crazy.</title></item><item><title>Didn't we have enough challenges trying to raise Simon? Why not just accept our lot in life? That's when I remembered something my dad used to say.</title></item><item><title>My dad was an old school guy. A former drill sergeant.</title></item><item><title>Blue collar union worker his whole life.</title></item><item><title>He taught us to work hard and think big. I remember he once pulled off the road and pointed at a big factory. "That's more than a building," he told me. "It took a lot of work to get that big.</title></item><item><title>It started out as just an idea at some guy's kitchen table." I guess you could say our upholstery business was OUR kitchen table idea.</title></item><item><title>Fifteen years later we employ more than 70 people in our 70,000 square foot factory.</title></item><item><title>And we're so proud of what we do.</title></item><item><title>We make umpire vests for Little Leagues.</title></item><item><title>Products for the men and women serving our country.</title></item><item><title>Restaurant seats for pizza chains.</title></item><item><title>And protective gear for our allies in the Israeli military.</title></item><item><title>We're actually taking work away from Chinese and Mexican competitors ­ and bringing it back to Delaware! How did it happen?</title></item><item><title>We defied the odds.</title></item><item><title>We rolled the dice on losing ­ or gaining ­ everything.</title></item><item><title>We didn't listen to the experts.</title></item><item><title>We grew our dream.</title></item><item><title>And with our son Simon, we didn't listen to the experts either.</title></item><item><title>Yes, he still struggles with autism.</title></item><item><title>But this past June, he completed his first year at the University of Delaware. I can't tell you how much this means to him ­ and how much it means to me, the mom of a special needs child.</title></item><item><title>Raising our family and building our business have been the passions of our lives, and what struck me is how similar they are.</title></item><item><title>If you've ever raised a child or started a business, you know what I'm talking about.</title></item><item><title>You put your heart and soul into it.</title></item><item><title>You work to find the 25th hour in the day You struggle to overcome insurmountable odds.</title></item><item><title>And you do it all because you believe in an unlimited future. "An unlimited future." Isn't that what America is all about? But today, when I talk to the young families and the struggling businesses I meet throughout Delaware, I have to ask: are we creating an unlimited future for them? A Gallup report recently said nearly 50% of small businesses owners aren't hiring because of what they call "regulatory uncertainty." Can you blame them? This Administration has imposed 106 new major regulations.</title></item><item><title>They are on track to create 109 million new paperwork burden hours.</title></item><item><title>And by year's end, $110 billion dollars' worth of new regulatory costs will be laid on the backs of business owners and taxpayers.</title></item><item><title>You might call that "regulatory uncertainty." I call it an all-out assault on free enterprise.</title></item><item><title>That's what worries me about this Administration.</title></item><item><title>They seem so eager to "fix" society.</title></item><item><title>But they don't have a clue about how to fix the economy.</title></item><item><title>In the end, it all comes down to what you believe.</title></item><item><title>And yes, they are believers! The Obama Administration believes in "experts" and blue ribbon panels.</title></item><item><title>They believe in creating new agencies and boards.</title></item><item><title>They believe in all that ­ but they just don't trust the entrepreneur's ability to grow her own business and to create jobs.</title></item><item><title>Mitt Romney not only believes in the values of economic freedom.</title></item><item><title>His entire life has been committed to advancing it.</title></item><item><title>Last April, I was privileged to be one of a dozen business leaders in Delaware to sit down and meet with Mitt Romney.</title></item><item><title>This wasn't some scripted photo op; this wasn't a staged event; this was a real discussion with someone who understands where small business is coming from.</title></item><item><title>You see, for Governor Romney, free enterprise isn't just a theory you study in graduate school.</title></item><item><title>It's a creed. A commitment. A world view.</title></item><item><title>It's what connects Americans, families, and communities, to an unlimited future.</title></item><item><title>That's why this election is so important to our small businesses and to our country. I represent the small businesses, the women, and the families working so hard to rebuild our communities.</title></item><item><title>In order to secure our unlimited future, we need a leader who understands the moral case for free enterprise.</title></item><item><title>Someone who believes in an unlimited future.</title></item><item><title>These aren't just words to Mitt Romney.</title></item><item><title>His track record proves it.</title></item><item><title>Let's secure that future together by sending Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan to the White House in November! Dios lo Bendiga! God Bless America!</title></item><item><title></title></item></channel></rss>