<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Jack Gilchrist</title><description>Remarks of Jack Gilchrist to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Thank you very much, Senator. I'm glad to have you as a champion of small business for New Hampshire. Like many small businessmen, my dad borrowed against our house to purchase the machinery to start Gilchrist Metal Fabricating. Machines making equipment for drilling oil, generating power, broadcasting television, processing food and many other industries. Machines run by taxpaying Americans. We employ about 40 people, most of them with families, including my son Stuart. Though we have enjoyed success, we face more global pressure every day. So do our suppliers and customers. If we don't continually improve and streamline our processes to stay efficient, we will lose out to our competition. We don't have a choice. Often the decisions we make are difficult. Running a business means taking responsibility:    Presenting a certain future to the management team. Developing a functional budget. Insuring that we have adequate supplies.</title></item><item><title>Making a commitment to fulfill our customer's orders on time.</title></item><item><title>Sure, there are things which I cannot control. But running the business is my job and mine alone. I blame no one else for the challenges we face. I am often reminded of something Lee Iacocca said: "lead, follow or get out of the way." Everyone who runs a business understands this. Everyone but our federal government. They won't lead. Their rules and regulations are too hard to follow. And they won't get out of our way. This Administration is killing us out here. Small business needs a leader. A leader who understands the entire spectrum of business and industry. A leader who can work with all parties involved. A leader who will not avoid dealing with difficult issues. A leader with the experience to understand what it takes. A leader who is in touch with America's small businesses. Mitt Romney is exactly that leader. Thank you!</title></item><item><title></title></item></channel></rss>