<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Reince Priebus Chairman2</title><description>Remarks of Reince Priebus Chairman2 to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the 2012 Republican National Convention! Once again, we thank the people of Tampa for their hospitality.</title></item><item><title>Tonight, we embark on a path toward A Better Future.</title></item><item><title>Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will lead us.</title></item><item><title>Our timeless, tested Republican principles will light the way.</title></item><item><title>Free enterprise, individual opportunity, limited government.</title></item><item><title>They made America great; only they can keep America strong.</title></item><item><title>The last four years under President Obama have been trying and troubling for this entire country.</title></item><item><title>The tired big government policies of the past have failed us.</title></item><item><title>We can't afford more disappointments.</title></item><item><title>We need a new direction.</title></item><item><title>We need a new president. I know just the man for the job.</title></item><item><title>He's a family man and a businessman.</title></item><item><title>He spent his career building successful companies.</title></item><item><title>Then, he saved the 2002 Olympics and brought pride to our nation.</title></item><item><title>As governor, he balanced the budget, cut taxes, and created jobs.</title></item><item><title>The president America needs is Mitt Romney! Governor Romney has a record of tremendous accomplishments.</title></item><item><title>But he never asks for accolades.</title></item><item><title>He just asks, "How can I help?" That's the mark of a true leader: A humble focus on getting the job done.</title></item><item><title>Mitt Romney spent his life turning around failing enterprises, and America needs a turnaround.</title></item><item><title>Specifically, we need Barack Obama to turn around and go back to Chicago.</title></item><item><title>Let me tell you about my friend Paul Ryan--a man of true integrity.</title></item><item><title>He doesn't descend to the gutter politics of the other side.</title></item><item><title>He rises above it to chart a better path.</title></item><item><title>He's my buddy, my congressman, and I can't wait to call him our vice president!</title></item><item><title>And won't it be nice to have a second-in-command who can spend his days doing more than prying his foot out of his mouth? Paul and Janna's three children are the lights of their lives.</title></item><item><title>In Congress, Paul doesn't worry about his political future.</title></item><item><title>He worries about his children's future.</title></item><item><title>In the same way, Sally and I worry about the future of our two kids, Jack and Grace.</title></item><item><title>Their future is in jeopardy because President Obama has added five trillion dollars to the national debt for all our children to pay off.</title></item><item><title>That's unacceptable.</title></item><item><title>Our Founders did not declare our independence only to see us become dependent on the borrowed money of foreign nations.</title></item><item><title>We still have time to chart a better course.</title></item><item><title>But if Barack Obama gets four more years, it might be too late.</title></item><item><title>We're not just spending borrowed money; we're living on borrowed time.</title></item><item><title>Look at the record of the outgoing administration: 23 million Americans, struggling for work.</title></item><item><title>Forty-two months of unemployment over 8 percent.</title></item><item><title>The worst jobs record since the Great Depression.</title></item><item><title>It's time to elect Mitt Romney so we can get moving on the Great Recovery.</title></item><item><title>Now the Obama apologists in the mainstream media - they say, oh, it's not his fault.</title></item><item><title>Well, I have news for the media.</title></item><item><title>We know things were bad.</title></item><item><title>But that's no excuse for making things worse.</title></item><item><title>Four years ago, Barack Obama was an unproven leader.</title></item><item><title>Today, he has proven himself.</title></item><item><title>He has proven that he's not up to the job.</title></item><item><title>Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will be up to the job on Day One.</title></item><item><title>Like Paul Ryan, I'm from Wisconsin, where Republicans have done pretty well in recent years.</title></item><item><title>Here's why: because we governed like we campaigned.</title></item><item><title>We made promises and we kept promises.</title></item><item><title>That's what Americans want - leaders of their word.</title></item><item><title>President Obama is a man of many words - but he's not a man of his word.</title></item><item><title>He broke his promise to cut the deficit in half.</title></item><item><title>And he broke his promise to fix the economy.</title></item><item><title>And adding insult to injury, he actually attacks success.</title></item><item><title>This president looks down on American free enterprise.</title></item><item><title>He says, "If you've got a business, you didn't build that." That makes me think Barack Obama has a problem with the American Dream. I grew up in a place called Kenosha, Wisconsin.</title></item><item><title>My dad was a union electrician and retired from the Racine Unified School District.</title></item><item><title>You know, when we drove through town, he didn't point at that big beautiful house on the corner and say, "Hey look at those lousy people over here."</title></item><item><title>He did what every one of your parents did.</title></item><item><title>He said, "Listen up pal, if you work hard and go to school, you're going to be in that house.</title></item><item><title>And mom and dad pray it's three times bigger." No parent, Democrat or Republican, wants the kind of negative, glass-half-empty view of America that President Obama is trying to sell.</title></item><item><title>We're the party that celebrates success, that believes in the American Dream and wants all of our children to have a chance to succeed.</title></item><item><title>So this convention is an invitation to all Americans to join us as we fight for a better future.</title></item><item><title>This is our generation's Rendezvous with Destiny.</title></item><item><title>It's our Time for Choosing.</title></item><item><title>If you believe America can do better than the last four years, we stand with you.</title></item><item><title>If you believe the next generation deserves a shot at the American Dream, Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan stand with you.</title></item><item><title>Thank you and God bless. </title></item></channel></rss>