<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>John Hoeven</title><description>Remarks of John Hoeven to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Fellow delegates, Ladies and Gentlemen: We Republicans believe in this great country, and we believe in the American people.</title></item><item><title>We know that our people are our greatest natural resource.</title></item><item><title>Our plan to build a brighter future for our country is built on the strength of the American people ­ on their vision, their work ethic, and their deep desire for a brighter future.</title></item><item><title>At the heart of it is job creation, because job creation must be job number one for our country at this critical point in our history.</title></item><item><title>What Americans want today is what America has always offered in abundance: opportunity.</title></item><item><title>And opportunity begins with a good job. A decade ago, we in North Dakota worked to forge a pro-growth, pro-business agenda that encouraged private-sector investment and innovation in all of our key industries, including energy.</title></item><item><title>We built a strong, competitive environment where businesses could grow ­ and hire ­ without red tape or high taxes.</title></item><item><title>The result was jobs and a thriving economy.</title></item><item><title>Today, North Dakota has the lowest unemployment rate and the fastest growing economy in the nation.</title></item><item><title>Instead of discouraging businesses with bureaucracy, we helped them to do things right, with good environmental stewardship.</title></item><item><title>But the Obama Administration doesn't see it that way, and the Keystone XL pipeline is a good example.</title></item><item><title>This $7 billion, high-tech project would not only reduce our dependence on Middle Eastern oil, but also help hold down the cost of fuel at the pump and create thousands of American jobs.</title></item><item><title>After four years of environmental review, however, the administration just says no ­ no to jobs, no to economic growth, no to lower fuel prices for consumers.</title></item><item><title>That's not what the American people want.</title></item><item><title>What they want is reliable and affordable energy to power their homes, run their businesses, and fuel their cars.</title></item><item><title>They want jobs and real opportunity to build a good life ­ and to leave that same legacy to their children.</title></item><item><title>We can provide that opportunity and get our nation's economy back on track again ­ if we focus on the things that actually encourage job growth and economic opportunity for the American people.</title></item><item><title>They know that our country is at a crossroads of history.</title></item><item><title>They also need to know that we offer a brighter alternative for our country's future.</title></item><item><title>Thank you and God bless the United States of America.</title></item><item><title>It is now my pleasure to introduce my fellow co-chair, Representative Marsha Blackburn of Tennessee. </title></item></channel></rss>