<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Marsha Blackburn</title><description>Remarks of Marsha Blackburn to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Co-chairing your platform committee has been a great honor.</title></item><item><title>It's also been a lot of work ­ and a lot of fun.</title></item><item><title>You can be so proud of the members of your state delegations.</title></item><item><title>They were smart, conscientious, and opinionated in the best way.</title></item><item><title>They knew what they and you believed, and weren't afraid to say so.</title></item><item><title>And neither were the thousands of American people who responded to our call and through social media offered us their solutions to the challenges that face our country.</title></item><item><title>It has been a remarkable exercise in grassroots democracy and, from this day forward, the GOP will be known as the Great Opportunity Party.</title></item><item><title>If you want to know how our economy can create the millions of jobs we need in order to get America back to work; If you want to know how we're going to get the unlimited energy we need to power our economy so that this really will be an American century; If you're alarmed by our country's declining position in the world, and wondering what can be done to reverse it; Read this platform.</title></item><item><title>Read it to learn how, together, we can assure a quality education for every child, regardless of where they live or what their family income might be.</title></item><item><title>Read it to discover how the American people can replace Obamacare with patient-centered, quality healthcare.</title></item><item><title>Read it to learn about the Republican Party's commitment to true federalism -- where the states take the lead in providing smaller, smarter and more efficient government.</title></item><item><title>If you want to know how Republicans ­ Republicans like Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan ­ are going to get America back on track, and back into the black, go online and read this platform.</title></item><item><title>And you will find that where we stand is right with you, with every American who wants a better future for their children, a more secure future for the elderly and a renewed promise of the American dream.</title></item><item><title>Thank you. </title></item></channel></rss>