<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Jason Chaffetz</title><description>Remarks of Jason Chaffetz to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>America is in trouble.</title></item><item><title>If you spent $1 million every day, it would take you almost 3,000 years to get to $1 trillion.</title></item><item><title>We are now nearly $16 trillion in debt.</title></item><item><title>Each day we pay more than $600 million in interest on that debt - and we deficit spend $3 billion a day.</title></item><item><title>Excessive regulations choke businesses.</title></item><item><title>Our tax code punishes success, discourages entrepreneurs, and stifles growth.</title></item><item><title>President Obama's solution: more government and more taxes.</title></item><item><title>This isn't the American Dream.</title></item><item><title>Our nation isn't just one good tax increase away from prosperity.</title></item><item><title>American success hasn't come from Czars, "Cash for Clunkers," endless bailouts, a limitless government credit card, or more taxes for more government.</title></item><item><title>The American Dream was built on the sweat and blood of Americans who took pride and personal ownership in themselves and their country.</title></item><item><title>When times were tough, generations before quietly rolled up their sleeves and built a stronger, more prosperous nation.</title></item><item><title>The government didn't build it.</title></item><item><title>They built it.</title></item><item><title>America was built with hard work, dedication to principles, and a belief that success was predicated on liberty and ownership.</title></item><item><title>Restoring the American Dream will require fiscal discipline, limited government, accountability, and a strong national defense.</title></item><item><title>We need to make tough choices.</title></item><item><title>We need leadership.</title></item><item><title>We need to elect Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan.</title></item><item><title>We need to believe in America again.</title></item><item><title>Thank you. </title></item></channel></rss>