<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Tad True</title><description>Remarks of Tad True to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Thank you.</title></item><item><title>Ladies and Gentlemen: Energy powers everything we do and America depends on reliable and affordable energy.</title></item><item><title>This is a simple concept, but the Obama administration does not get it.</title></item><item><title>His policies are driving us away from energy independence, not towards it.</title></item><item><title>Mitt Romney knows that we need an "All of the Above" energy policy that includes oil, gas, and coal and renewable sources -- like wind and solar -- so that we can finally secure energy independence for our country.</title></item><item><title>Infrastructure is fundamental to all energy systems.</title></item><item><title>And infrastructure is critical to achieving energy independence infrastructure -- like pipelines.</title></item><item><title>Which prompts me to ask: Mr.</title></item><item><title>President, where is the Keystone Pipeline? I am part of the third generation of family-owned businesses, and we operate pipelines in the great states of Wyoming, North Dakota, and Montana.</title></item><item><title>These companies were started by my grandfather, and then run by my father and uncles.</title></item><item><title>Between them -- and our 152 dedicated and incredibly talented employees -- we built almost 4,000 miles of pipeline. A lot of our recent work has been constructing new pipeline infrastructure in western North Dakota to support the development of the Bakken oil shale -- an exciting and important development for America.</title></item><item><title>Some time ago, we agreed to build the "on-ramp" to the Keystone XL pipeline, so that it could take American produced oil to American markets.</title></item><item><title>If Keystone had received timely approval of their permit, it would be under construction today.</title></item><item><title>Instead, Americans have missed out on jobs from this pipeline because the Obama Administration has played politics with the Keystone project.</title></item><item><title>My hope is that my 3 boys -- Henry, Sam, and Charlie -- will be part of the fourth generation of our family business.</title></item><item><title>And although my kids think pipelines are boring, I know and you know and Mitt Romney knows that pipelines are vital to America's energy system.</title></item><item><title>Ladies and Gentlemen: This is not about just one pipeline.</title></item><item><title>This is about a fundamental transformation of America's energy system so that we can achieve that long-sought after goal of energy independence.</title></item><item><title>More importantly, it's about my 3 boys and your children and about re-building a nation that can once again power itself.</title></item><item><title>We need a president who understands that we need all of that energy all of that oil all of those jobs.</title></item><item><title>And we need a president that understands that America needs that pipeline.</title></item><item><title>That president is Mitt Romney.</title></item><item><title>Thank you.</title></item><item><title></title></item></channel></rss>