<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Sharon Day</title><description>Remarks of Sharon Day to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Thank you, Mr.</title></item><item><title>Chairman.</title></item><item><title>Welcome everyone to my home State of Florida! We are honored to host you and I am honored to serve as the RNC Co-Chair.</title></item><item><title>Every election we hear that this is the most important election of our lifetime.</title></item><item><title>This election is more than that.</title></item><item><title>It is the most important election in our nation's lifetime.</title></item><item><title>In 1775 our Founding Fathers rose up to establish our liberty.</title></item><item><title>Today, we need to defeat a President whose actions threaten our liberty! In this way, we are in a similar position as our Founding Fathers.</title></item><item><title>Just as they were called upon, we are being called upon.</title></item><item><title>What they started, what they believed in, we must defend! The danger for America is already here, in the form of the Democratic leaders in Washington.</title></item><item><title>We have a Democrat Senate leader who refuses to meet his moral obligation to pass a budget for the government.</title></item><item><title>We have a Democrat House leader that wouldn't allow a major piece of legislation--Obama Care--to be read before it was passed.</title></item><item><title>She stated to the world, and I quote "We have to pass the bill so that you can find out what is in it." We have a President that has bypassed the Senate confirmation process in order to appoint unaccountable czars to make and enforce policies on America's citizens. A President that by executive action has changed immigration laws, imposed unconstitutional burdens on our states, and issued over-reaching regulations.</title></item><item><title>We know the problem, America--their names are Obama 足 Biden 足 Reid 足 Pelosi 足 Holder.</title></item><item><title>What they have done--and will continue to do, should Obama be re-elected--runs contrary to the values we believe in and the principles we stand for.</title></item><item><title>It is our duty, as citizen activists, of this great Republican Party, to fight to restore the values of our Founding Fathers.</title></item><item><title>My fellow members, this fight is not just about an election, and it is not about our party.</title></item><item><title>Our fight is about our country, and we must not lose! Our Founding Fathers made huge personal sacrifices for what they believed in.</title></item><item><title>The time is now for us to do the same! I am a proud grassroots activist, one of many in my state and countless others from across the country.</title></item><item><title>Today we need as many grassroots activists from all walks of life and throughout this great nation to stand with us.</title></item><item><title>The sacrifices we need to make are nothing compared to the sacrifices our children and our grandchildren will face if we don't take back our country on November 6th.</title></item><item><title>We must take this election house-by-house, precinct-by-precinct, city-by-city, state-by-state, to bring our proud conservative message of Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan to every voter.</title></item><item><title>When we leave Florida in a few days, let's commit ourselves to give all that we can to help the Romney/Ryan ticket.</title></item><item><title>Together, let's make history.</title></item><item><title>Together, let's defeat Barack Obama.</title></item><item><title>Together, let's save our country for the next generation.</title></item><item><title>Thank you.</title></item><item><title>God bless each of you.</title></item><item><title>God bless our proud military and their families and may God continue to bless the United States of America. </title></item></channel></rss>