<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Steve Cohen</title><description>Remarks of Steve Cohen to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Good evening, My name is Steven Cohen and I am president of Screen Machine Industries, a family-owned manufacturer of construction and mining equipment located in the great Buckeye State of Ohio. And, yes, we did build this company. Our country's nearly 30 million small businesses serve as the American backbone for job creation and product innovation. The opportunity to create new products and open new markets is the American Dream. This capitalistic spirit has supported our economy since its founding. As a manufacturer, our products are the heartbeat of our business. We can't tolerate other companies stealing our hard work without compensation. It can take several years and tens of thousands of dollars to achieve patent status. Once granted, we expect it to be protected. Our products are often stolen and copied overseas for a mere fraction of the price. All too often tariffs and unfair trade practices make it difficult for American businesses to export. We need a new president that will protect America's patented inventions, guard the value of our currency and open new markets for American products. American small businesses face a mountain of regulations and taxes. In addition, our international competitors do not have to face the upcoming costs associated with funding a multibillion dollar health care plan, overreaching emission standards, and the</title></item><item><title>unnecessary "War on Coal." These factors create a tremendous disadvantage in the global market place. We need an administration that will lessen tax burdens and government regulations that strangle small businesses. While we face higher government-imposed costs, cheaper imports from overseas companies flood our markets. Unnecessary regulations and mandates imposed on business make our products more expensive to make and less competitive to sell. We need a Romney administration to ensure our country's competitiveness and give our companies the opportunity to expand and hire again. Let's bring back that original American will to invent, employ and prosper! Thank you. </title></item></channel></rss>