<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cathy McMorris Rodgers</title><description>Remarks of Cathy McMorris Rodgers to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Good evening ladies and gentleman. Thank you. My name is Cathy McMorris Rogers, and I am proud to represent eastern Washington in Congress. Tonight, we're going to do things a little differently. I have the pleasure of being your host for the night guiding you through the next few hours. I'm delighted to report that we have a wonderful lineup for you. Each speaker will be joining together to send a message to President Obama. And that message is three simple words: We built it. Before I ran for office I worked in my family's business, the Peach Crest Fruit Basket, for 13 years. I worked hard every day, and I can assure you that my family built that business from the ground up. Today, that hands-on experience guides my decision-making in Congress. Unlike President Obama, I know that small businesses are the true engine of our economy ­ not the government ­ and what businesses need to grow and create jobs is less taxes and regulation, not more. Tonight you'll hear a variety of stories from people who work hard every day to build our economy. You'll hear from Jack Gilchrist, the owner of a family-owned metal fabricating business in New Hampshire.</title></item><item><title>A number of our nation's leading governors are with us tonight. The chief executives from states like Ohio, Wisconsin, Oklahoma, South Carolina, Nevada and Virginia ­ places where they have created an environment that unleashes American ingenuity instead of stifling it. They will tell us how the job creators in their communities aren't found in the state house ­ they're found on Main Street. And one of the speakers I'm most looking forward to hearing from tonight is someone who I think we all can agree will make a fabulous First Lady, Ann Romney. To close out the evening, we will hear from a dynamic and engaging leader who is shaking up the way they do business in New Jersey ­ Governor Chris Christie. So let's get started. Our next speaker is from the Granite State and was elected to the United States Senate in 2010. Ladies and gentlemen, Senator Kelly Ayotte. </title></item></channel></rss>