<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Jackie Walorski</title><description>Remarks of Jackie Walorski to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Good afternoon. I'm proud to represent Indiana, which we affectionately refer to as the Hoosier State.</title></item><item><title>Hoosiers cherish values like common sense, hard work and problem solving.</title></item><item><title>And there's a lot Washington can learn from the Hoosier state.</title></item><item><title>When Indiana faced a massive budget shortfall, we didn't play partisan games.</title></item><item><title>We came together, rolled up our sleeves and turned a billion-dollar deficit into a surplus.</title></item><item><title>We understood that when you have a deficit, spending more money isn't the solution.</title></item><item><title>In the face of record unemployment, we understood that more government spending won't create jobs.</title></item><item><title>That's why we passed common-sense reforms that made it easier to do business ­ and create jobs -- in our great state.</title></item><item><title>As a result, Indiana was rated as the best Midwest state to do business in and we are among the nation's leaders in job growth.</title></item><item><title>In the Hoosier state, we proved a very simple lesson: Working together is the best way to solve our problems.</title></item><item><title>And Washington can do the same.</title></item><item><title>By cutting spending and reducing the red tape, we can unleash our small businesses to create jobs.</title></item><item><title>And with Hoosier common sense, we can balance the budget and get our nation's economy working again.</title></item><item><title>American workers and American entrepreneurs are the best in the world.</title></item><item><title>I'm ready to carry their torch to Washington and prove there will never be a mountain too high for us to climb.</title></item><item><title>The American spirit will always persevere.</title></item><item><title>Fellow Hoosiers it's your time to take back our country.</title></item><item><title>Thank you and God bless! </title></item></channel></rss>