<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Alex Schriver</title><description>Remarks of Alex Schriver to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>As the elected leader of 250,000 College Republicans on more than 1,800 campuses, I've got one of the best jobs in the country. I get to push back against the bastions of liberalism ­ America's colleges and universities.</title></item><item><title>Every day, I'm thankful to be employed.</title></item><item><title>Yet, unfortunately, many of my peers are not as lucky.</title></item><item><title>Half of my generation didn't get up and go to a job this morning.</title></item><item><title>Many of them, in fact 3 out of 10, graduated this year and moved back in with their parents.</title></item><item><title>The fact is: we're young.</title></item><item><title>We're focused.</title></item><item><title>We're driven.</title></item><item><title>And we need to be out making our mark on the world.</title></item><item><title>Instead, our generation is having a mark made on us.</title></item><item><title>Our country is nearly $16 trillion in debt ­ a burden placed on our generation's back.</title></item><item><title>We're tired of it.</title></item><item><title>And we're tired of a President and his cronies in Congress being all-too-willing to kick the nation's fiscal crisis down to our road.</title></item><item><title>Governor Mitt Romney has a plan to get America back to work, to rein in our out-of-control spending, and to get our great country back on a sustainable path.</title></item><item><title>That plan is just what we need.</title></item><item><title>At the end of the day, Barack Obama has failed young Americans.</title></item><item><title>We're out of jobs, we're out of "hope" and we're out of "change." Our generation can do better.</title></item><item><title>My generation deserves better.</title></item><item><title>Thank you very much, God bless you! </title></item></channel></rss>