<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Kelly Ayotte</title><description>Remarks of Kelly Ayotte to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Live free or Die! That's the motto of the great state of New Hampshire.</title></item><item><title>But I believe tonight we all share that view ­ as have generations of Americans before us.</title></item><item><title>Like most Americans ­ our family's life changed after 9/11.</title></item><item><title>My husband Joe ­ who was on track to be a commercial pilot ­ instead served our great country flying combat missions in Iraq.</title></item><item><title>When he returned home from the war ­ he found himself in the same position as so many Americans ­ he needed a job.</title></item><item><title>So he started a family business ­ a landscaping and snowplowing company.</title></item><item><title>And when I say he ­ I mean we ­ because I spent many a sleepless night shoveling snow.</title></item><item><title>And I'm proud of the fact that in addition to being a United States Senator ­ I'm also pretty good with a snow plow! We are no different from most families who take risks starting their own business.</title></item><item><title>We borrowed money to pursue our dreams.</title></item><item><title>And believe me, there was no guarantee of success.</title></item><item><title>We certainly were not too big to fail ­ we had to make it work.</title></item><item><title>Yet through all the hard work and sacrifice ­ we pulled together as a family.</title></item><item><title>As the business grew so did our extended family.</title></item><item><title>And I speak to you tonight with great concern ­ for our employees ­ their families ­ my family ­ and your family.</title></item><item><title>My concern is that President Obama is making it very difficult for small businesses to get started ­ to create jobs ­ and to survive. I hear this all the time from the small business owners I speak with.</title></item><item><title>They want to focus on their business.</title></item><item><title>The Obama Administration wants to bury them with rules, regulations and red tape.</title></item><item><title>From the National Labor Relations Board ­ to the Department of Labor ­ to the EPA. Under this Administration, the regulations are up ­ and the job creation is down.</title></item><item><title>President Obama's view is clear: he actually believes that as a family business grows ­ the federal government should take a larger share of its earnings.</title></item><item><title>That's punishment for expanding and creating more jobs. I call it a "success tax." And the very best example is Obamacare.</title></item><item><title>Let me tell you what I hear in the real world about Obamacare.</title></item><item><title>Just a couple of months ago ­ a successful restaurant owner in Concord, New Hampshire, told me about his dilemma.</title></item><item><title>He wanted to open up a second restaurant ­ and hire more employees.</title></item><item><title>But he realized that if he did ­ he would trigger penalties under Obamacare and he couldn't afford it.</title></item><item><title>So he never opened up that restaurant.</title></item><item><title>Is that what we want for small businesses in America ­ to be afraid to grow because of the government? To face penalties when you create more jobs? To be told "you're earning too much"? Isn't it time we had a leader who believes that creating jobs ought to be celebrated not penalized? That is why Mitt Romney is running for president.</title></item><item><title>He'll get the federal government out of the business of small business.</title></item><item><title>He'll fight to lower and simplify taxes.</title></item><item><title>He'll work to eliminate job-killing red tape.</title></item><item><title>And he will roll back Obamacare starting on Day One! In both the private sector and as Governor of Massachusetts, Mitt Romney always asked: how can I help small businesses grow, innovate, and compete? It's the right question.</title></item><item><title>And it's the question that this Administration never thinks to ask.</title></item><item><title>But why should we be surprised? President Obama has never even run a lemonade stand ­ and it shows.</title></item><item><title>So what we need to do is clear.</title></item><item><title>For the sake of the future of small business ­ we need to replace Barack Obama.</title></item><item><title>We need to replace Barack Obama with Mitt Romney. A man who truly gets it.</title></item><item><title>Mitt understands the hopes and dreams of small business owners throughout our great country.</title></item><item><title>But don't just take my word for it. I want you to hear directly from someone on the front lines of small business.</title></item><item><title>Jack Gilchrist is a small business owner from Hudson, New Hampshire.</title></item><item><title>Three generations of his family have used their own hands to build Gilchrist Metal Fabricating.</title></item><item><title>It's a true family business ­ founded over 30 years ago by Jack's father ­ and carried on by Jack and his son.</title></item><item><title>Jack Gilchrist is the face of small business in America, and yes he did build it.</title></item><item><title>Please join me in welcoming my friend Jack Gilchrist. </title></item></channel></rss>