<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Al Austin</title><description>Remarks of Al Austin to the Republican National Convention, Tampa, August 2012</description><item><title>Good afternoon.</title></item><item><title>It has been my pleasure to serve as chairman of the 2012 Tampa Bay Host Committee.</title></item><item><title>On behalf of the Tampa Bay community, welcome.</title></item><item><title>We're glad you are here.</title></item><item><title>You may know that we were finalists for the last two conventions, which ultimately went to New York City and then to Minneapolis/St.</title></item><item><title>Paul.</title></item><item><title>Apparently, the third time is a charm.</title></item><item><title>With more than 15,000 members of the media here from around the globe, I am pleased that Tampa Bay will no longer be the best kept secret in the world.</title></item><item><title>For me, to stand on this stage, in this city, is the realization of a long-time dream.</title></item><item><title>There has not been a convention for either party in the state of Florida since 1972.</title></item><item><title>That same year, I was a delegate to the convention in Miami Beach. I have been a delegate or alternate at every convention since then.</title></item><item><title>And I've been working hard at building my community, and creating jobs and opportunity for the Tampa Bay area.</title></item><item><title>Having you all here in this Forum will have a significant impact on the future of our region.</title></item><item><title>Because you chose us, thousands of people have the opportunity to get to know our people, our businesses, our attractions -- and our food.</title></item><item><title>You are creating jobs for caterers, waiters, taxi drivers, and so many more Floridians.</title></item><item><title>And you are filling up hotel rooms that often sit empty after the summer tourism season ends and families head back for their children to start school.</title></item><item><title>So thank you for stimulating our economy.</title></item><item><title>Hundreds of volunteers have spent countless hours to prepare for the next few days.</title></item><item><title>We trust that you will enjoy our city and our hospitality, and that you come back often.</title></item><item><title>Thank you for entrusting us with the great honor of hosting the 2012 Republican National Convention. </title></item></channel></rss>