<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
  <title>April 2013 top stories from USA Today, brought to you by GEICO</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com</link>
  <description>April 2013 Top News from USA Today
  </description>


<item>
  <title>Student wrongly tied to Boston bombings found dead</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2013/04/25/boston-bombing-social-media-student-brown-university-reddit/2112309/
</link>
  <description>A body pulled from the water in a Rhode Island park has been identified as a Brown University student who was mistakenly linked by amateur sleuths on a social media site to the Boston bombings.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 10:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Man tries to take photo of beaver; it kills him</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/11/newser-beaver-kills-man/2074145/
</link>
  <description>Forget sharks: It's beavers that are truly terrifying. A fisherman in Belarus was bitten to death by one, and all he was doing was trying to take its picture, Sky News reports. The man spotted the beaver while</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 12:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>At least 3 dead, 141  injured in Boston Marathon blasts</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/15/explosions-finish-line-boston-marathon/2085193/
</link>
  <description>At least three people died and more than 140 others were injured Monday after two blasts ripped through the crowd near the finish line of the Boston Marathon.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 15:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>As manhunt ends, new questions emerge in Boston bombings</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/suspect-in-custody-newspaper-says/2095845/
</link>
  <description>The Chechen brothers at the heart of the Boston Marathon bombing investigation lived regular American lives - until something changed them.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Philadelphia abortion clinic horror: Column</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2013/04/10/philadelphia-abortion-clinic-horror-column/2072577/
</link>
  <description>We've forgotten what belongs on Page One.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 20:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Details emerge on Boston suspect Dzhokhar Tsarnaev</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/dzhokhar-tsarnaev-boston-bombing/2095953/
</link>
  <description>The surviving Boston bomb suspect has been identified as Dzhokhar A. Tsarnaev, 19, of Cambridge, Mass, according to the Associated Press.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 07:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Investigators claim major progress in Boston bombings</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/17/boston-marathon-pressure-cooker-bomb/2089963/
</link>
  <description>Investigators combing through photos and videotape believe they have identified images of a suspect seen delivering one of the explosive devices that killed three people at the Boston Marathon.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 09:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Boston bombs were pressure cookers filled with metal</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/boston-marathon-explosions/2086853/
</link>
  <description>The explosive devices that killed three people and injured scores at the Boston Marathon finish line were pressure cookers filled with metal and ball bearings, according to a federal law enforcement official..</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 01:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2013 NFL draft: First round pick-by-pick analysis</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/25/nfl-draft-first-round-one-selections/2112739/
</link>
  <description>Check out every pick from the NFL draft's first round.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 20:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>MIT shooting triggers massive police operation in Boston</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/mit-shooting-cop-massachusetts/2095733/
</link>
  <description>A Cambridge, Mass., police officer said that an MIT police officer was shot Wednesday night.                MIT campus police referred a caller to the campus news bureau, where no one answered calls.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 23:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Marathon victim in iconic photo has both legs amputated</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/bauman-amputation-boston-marathon/2088325/
</link>
  <description>The father of a man injured in the Boston Marathon bombing says his son had both legs amputated. Jeff Bauman says his son, 27-year-old Jeff Bauman Jr., is the man pictured in an Associated Press photo.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 15:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Search continues in rubble of Texas fertilizer blast</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/waco-texas-plant-explosion/2092769/
</link>
  <description>Explosions rocked a fertilizer facility in West, Texas, on Wednesday evening as firefighters were battling an onsite blaze.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 06:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Uncle: Tamerlan Tsarnaev called, asked for forgiveness</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/tamerlan-tsarnaev-boston-bombing/2096189/
</link>
  <description>Police have identified Tamerlan Tsarnaev, 26, as the dead bombing suspect. He was killed in a dramatic firefight with police in nearby Watertown.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 09:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>FBI releases images of two suspects near Boston bomb sites</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/boston-bombing-marathon-investigation-fbi/2093037/
</link>
  <description>Investigators are exploring a number of promising leads in the Boston Marathon bombing case, including an image of a man believed possibly involved in one of Monday's twin explosions that killed three people.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 11:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>First Take: Vitriol infests Warren family grief</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/07/pastor-rick-warren-matthew-warren-suicide/2060337/
</link>
  <description>In the social media tide of response to the suicide of Pastor Rick Warren's son, Matthew, there are flames of condemnation for Warren and his Christian message.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 09:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Mississippi man arrested in ricin letters case</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/17/obama-letter-suspicious-substance/2090465/
</link>
  <description>The FBI said Wednesday it has arrested a Mississippi man </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 11:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Arrest of 3 teens in assault, suicide opens raw wounds</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2013/04/12/cyberbullying-sexual-assault-suicide-san-jose-arrest-teens/2076825/
</link>
  <description>The arrest of the 16-year olds on sexual battery charges on an intoxicated, unconscious teen have reopened raw wounds for the family of a 15-year-old who hanged over the incident in September.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 10:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Boston bombing suspect opening up to police</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/21/dzhokhar-tsarnaev-boston-bombing-investigation/2102093/
</link>
  <description>The surviving suspect in last week's Boston Marathon bombings began responding to investigators' questions Sunday evening.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 22:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Official: Boston suspect awake, responding in writing</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/21/boston-bombings-suspect-marathon/2100733/
</link>
  <description>Investigators are still waiting to interrogate Dzhokhar Tsarnaev, the surviving suspect in last week's Boston Marathon bombing.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 11:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Gwyneth Paltrow goes from 'beautiful' to 'humiliated'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/26/gwyneth-paltrow-goes-from-beautiful-to-humiliated/2115061/
</link>
  <description>Gwyneth Paltrow admits her sheer-sided 'Iron Man 3' premiere dress caused her to go from </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 08:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Texas student accused in stabbing spree at college</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/09/lone-star-college-stabbing/2067449/
</link>
  <description>At least 14 students were injured -- two critically -- in a stabbing spree on the campus of Lone Star College-CyFair near Houston.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 13:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jennifer Love Hewitt apologizes for 'wowser' dress</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/19/jennifer-love-hewitt-spills-out-ellen-wowza-dress/2096507/
</link>
  <description>Jennifer Love Hewitt wows with her dress today on The Ellen DeGeneres Show.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 11:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Guinness record holder dies tragically while repeating stunt</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/29/newser-india-guinness-world-records/2120717/
</link>
  <description>An Indian daredevil who made it into the Guinness Book of World Records died yesterday while repeating a version of his stunt, reports the BBC. Sailendra Nath Roy entered the record books in 2011 after</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 10:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Pastor Rick Warren blames son's death on depression</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/06/church-pastor-rick-warrens-son-commits-suicide/2059193/
</link>
  <description>Rick Warren, one of the best known evangelical pastors worldwide, announced Saturday his son had killed himself Friday night.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 13 17:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Gunman identified in Georgia SWAT shootout</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/10/firefighters-held-hostage-georgia/2071969/
</link>
  <description>A quiet subdivision in this suburb north of Atlanta was recovering Thursday from a violent confrontation that ended when police stormed a home Wednesday evening, killing a gunman who had held four firefighters hostage.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 17:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Background check compromise losing support</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/17/guns-background-checks-manchin-senate/2090105/
</link>
  <description>The Senate rejected a bipartisan deal to expand gun background checks, as it began voting on a host of amendments to a measure aimed at curbing gun violence.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 09:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>George Jones, country superstar, dies</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/music/2013/04/26/george-jones-country-superstar-has-died-at-81/2115323/
</link>
  <description>The peerless, hard-living country singer who recorded dozens of hits was 81.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 10:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kendra Wilkinson quits 'Splash'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/03/kendra-wilkinson-quits-splash/2048745/
</link>
  <description>She walked all the way up. She looked cute in her suit. But when it came time to dive, Kendra Wilkinson couldn't do it.  On Tuesday's Splash, the reality show star quit.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 08:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kmart's 'ship my pants' ad causes shockwaves and smiles</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2013/04/15/kmart-ship-my-pants-commercial-ad/2084131/
</link>
  <description>Sophomoric? Silly? Or a smart strategic move? The jury is out on a new Kmart ad that uses slight of mouth -- </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 11:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jets waive Tim Tebow after one season</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/29/tim-tebow-released-new-york-jets/2120333/
</link>
  <description>Tebow lasted just one season with the Jets after two years with the Broncos.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 08:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lindsey Vonn's ex-husband jokes about Tiger Woods</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/13/tiger-woods-lindsey-vonn-ex-husband/2081017/
</link>
  <description>Who called in Tiger's two-stroke penalty on Friday?</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 23:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Gate to Hell' discovered in Turkey</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/01/newser-turkey-gate-underworld/2042227/
</link>
  <description>As far as archaeological discoveries go, it's a darker one: Pluto's Gate -- aka, the fabled gate to the underworld -- has reportedly been unearthed in Turkey.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 11:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Trisha Yearwood wows with weight loss</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/09/trisha-yearwood-wows-with-weight-loss/2066605/
</link>
  <description>Trisha Yearwood wows with weight loss at the ACM show.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 09:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Maine hermit living in wild for 27 years arrested</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/10/maine-hermit-living-in-wild-for-27-years-arrested/2072505/
</link>
  <description>A man who lived like a hermit for decades in a makeshift camp in the woods and may be responsible for more than 1,000 burglaries for food and other staples.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 20:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Illinois mayor's nephew kills 5, dies after firefight</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/24/manchester-illinois-5-dead-shooting/2108991/
</link>
  <description>Five people -- including two children -- were killed in an overnight shooting in Manchester, Ill. Police later killed the gunman.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 09:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Officer killed in MIT standoff ID'd as Sean Collier, 26</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/boston-mit-officer-collier/2096329/
</link>
  <description>MIT police officer Sean Collier, 26, of Somerville, Mass., died last night after two men fired gun shots at Collier, who responded to a disturbance on the campus.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 10:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Warrant: Wife of ex-judge confesses in Texas DA killings</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/17/kaufman-county-prosecutors-killings-texas-wife-arrested/2090215/
</link>
  <description>The wife of a former Texas justice of the peace has been arrested on capital murder charges in the killings of of the Kaufman County district attorney, his wife and a second prosecutor, The Dallas Morning News reports.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 09:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Pressure-cooker bomb instructions in al-Qaeda magazine</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/al-qaeda-magazine-pressure-cooker-bomb-directions/2088109/
</link>
  <description>Instructions to make bombs out of pressure cookers similar to those believed the source of two fatal explosions in Boston Monday were published two years ago in Inspire, an online magazine tied to al-Qaeda.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 14:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Affidavits: Suspect in ricin case 'delusional'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/18/obama-letter-ricin-mississippi/2092795/
</link>
  <description>Suspect in ricin case allegedly believes he was the target of a wide-ranging government conspiracy after stumbling onto a plot to sell body parts.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 07:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2013 NFL draft: Team-by-team selections</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/25/2013-nfl-draft-team-by-team-picks/2113375/
</link>
  <description>See the picks for every team in the 2013 NFL draft.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 20:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Teen Mom' star now an adult film actress</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/10/teen-mom-star-now-an-adult-film-actress/2072009/
</link>
  <description>Farrah Abraham admits to starring in a porn clip, which she's shopping around.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 17:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Thousands post to Dzhokhar Tsarnaev on social media</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/djohar-tsarnaev-social-network-page/2097167/
</link>
  <description>The manhunt for Boston Marathon bombing suspect DzhokharTsarnaev ended Friday night, after thousands of posts on his VKontakte page during the search.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 17:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>3rd Boston fatality is Lu Lingzi of China</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/boston-university-marathon-victim/2088825/
</link>
  <description>The third person killed in the Boston Marathon bombings was a Chinese graduate student at Boston University named Lu Lingzi, a state-run Chinese newspaper reported Wednesday.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 18:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Omarosa fired from 'Celebrity Apprentice'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/01/omarosa-fired-from-celebrity-apprentice/2041789/
</link>
  <description>Celebrity Apprentice has lost a big villain. Donald Trump fired Omarosa on Sunday's episode.  </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 09:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kids killed as mom tries to go through train crossing</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/02/train-crossing-wreck-leaves-2-children-dead/2048317/
</link>
  <description>BATAVIA, Iowa -- The sound of passing freight trains is a constant backdrop in this small southeast Iowa community. So is the sight of people driving around lowered gates at the Fourth Street crossing.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 23:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Save Our Shows 2013</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/03/31/save-our-shows-survey-2013/1982781/
</link>
  <description>Vote on which scripted sitcoms and dramas deserve new seasons or to be discarded.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 13 18:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Tiger Woods gets 2-shot penalty, not disqualification</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2013/04/13/tiger-woods-assessed-2-shot-penalty-from-masters/2079725/
</link>
  <description>Tiger Woods is still in the Masters but has been assessed a two-shot penalty.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 09:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Yvette Prieto is Michael Jordan's fiancee: Who is she?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/03/08/yvette-prieto-michael-jordan/1973755/
</link>
  <description>1. Is a Cuban-American model. Prieto was born in Cuba. Most press accounts call her a model, but it's hard to find pictures of her modeling anywhere else than on MJ's arm. She's done it for some designers, but</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 13 13:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2 shot at Denver marijuana rally</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/20/denver-pot-holiday/2098755/
</link>
  <description>DENVER (AP) — Denver police say one person has been shot in the leg and another is down with unknown injuries after shots were fired at a marijuana celebration held to mark the counterculture holiday 4/20.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 13 05:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Roundup: The latest on the Boston Marathon explosions</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/16/boston-marathon-explosions-tuesday-morning-roundup/2087005/
</link>
  <description>A moment of silence is observed before Monday night's game between the Denver Nuggets and Milwaukee Bucks at the Bradley Center. (Photo: Jeff Hanisch, USA TODAY Sports) The morning after two explosions rocked</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 07:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ex-porn star Jenna Jameson arrested for battery</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/07/jenna-jameson-arrested-battery/2061767/
</link>
  <description>Ex-porn star Jenna Jameson was arrested for battery on Saturday night.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 20:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Five living presidents toast new Bush library</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/25/george-bush-presidential-library/2110547/
</link>
  <description>George W. Bush Presidential Center will be dedicated in Dallas on Thursday.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 01:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Comedian Jonathan Winters dies at age 87</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/12/comedian-jonathan-winters-dies-at-age-87/2077723/
</link>
  <description>Comedian Jonathan Winters died Thursday in California at 87.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2013 NFL draft grades: An 'A' for effort goes to ...</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/29/2013-nfl-draft-grades/2120157/
</link>
  <description>It takes about three seasons to accurately evaluate an NFL draft. It doesn't take 24 hours to unfairly grade it. So based on first impressions, USA TODAY Sports hands out report cards (written in pencil) for</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 02:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Adam Lanza's mom was alarmed by his gruesome images</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/08/adam-lanza-nancy-daily-news-shooter-gruesome-images/2063381/
</link>
  <description>Nancy Lanza, the mother of Newtown gunman Adam Lanza, had grown increasingly concerned about her son's state of mind but did not confront him after finding ghastly drawings of dead bodies in his room.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 12:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Witherspoon 'deeply embarrassed' about arrest</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/21/reese-witherspoon-husband-jim-toth-dui-atlanta/2101695/
</link>
  <description>The actress is accused of disobeying an officer's instructions.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 18:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Older Tsarnaev brother: 'I don't understand' Americans</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/brothers-suspects-boston-marathon-bombings/2096281/
</link>
  <description>Mystery shrouds trail of two brothers in Boston Marathon bombings.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 12:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Brad Johnson paying physical price for long NFL career</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/23/brad-johnson-price-of-nfl-career/2108063/
</link>
  <description>After playing 17 seasons in the NFL, hardest task for Brad Johnson is getting out of bed</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 21:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Michael Jordan wedding draws famous guests</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nba/2013/04/28/michael-jordan-yvette-prieto-wedding-palm-beach-jupiter/2119681/
</link>
  <description>Michael Jordan got married over the weekend in front of a few hundred of his family and closest friends.   The Charlotte Bobcats owner exchanged vows with 35-year-old former model Yvette Prieto on Saturday.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 19:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Disney Fan Club: Annette Funicello has died</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/08/disney-annette-funicello-dies/2063545/
</link>
  <description>Annette Funicello has died, according to Disney's official fan club Twitter.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 13:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>N. Korea approves 'merciless' attack on U.S.</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/02/north-korea-south-us/2048335/
</link>
  <description>North Korea stopped South Korean workers from entering a joint industrial complex in the North Wednesday, in the latest escalation of the weeks-long crisis on the long-troubled Korean Peninsula.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 23:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Woman's DNA found on Boston bomb</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/29/boston-marathon-bombings-female-dna/2121979/
</link>
  <description>Female DNA has been found on at least one of the Boston Marathon bombs, but investigators have not determined whose it is or whether it indicates a woman helped execute the April 15 bombings.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 17:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ex-Patriots lineman carried woman to safety after Boston blasts</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/15/joe-andruzzi-patriots-marathon/2086599/
</link>
  <description>More proof that Joe Andruzzi is a great guy.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 22:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>CIA wanted Boston suspect on terror watch list</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/24/dagestan-boston-bombing-fbi-interview-tsarnaev/2108835/
</link>
  <description>U.S. officials who traveled to to the Russian Republic of Dagestan have interviewed at length the mother of the Boston bombing suspects in an attempt to determine how her two sons were radicalized.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>FBI probes Ashley Judd tape at McConnell's request</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/09/mcconnell-mother-jones-tape-ashley-judd/2066725/
</link>
  <description>Senate GOP leader Mitch McConnell's campaign asked the FBI to investigate a tape leaked to Mother Jones magazine in which his aides discussed attacking Ashley Judd's mental health and policy views.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 10:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bubba Watson's hovercraft golf cart is real and it's spectacular</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/02/bubba-watson-hovercraft-golf-cart/2046711/
</link>
  <description>Check out the coolest golf cart you will ever see.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 13:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Cinnamon Challenge' fad could result in lung damage</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/22/cinnamon-challenge-lungs/2096163/
</link>
  <description>A stunt in which participants  willingly swallow a heaping, dry spoonful of the aromatic spice cinnamon in 60 seconds with no water went viral in 2012, becoming a social media sensation that resulted in more</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Video shows Rutgers coach Mike Rice abusing players</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/02/espn-airs-rutgers-coach-mike-rice-abusing-players/2047211/
</link>
  <description>Video footage showed coach Mike Rice hurling basketballs from close range at his players.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>1 hospitalized after Chicago sinkhole swallows 3 cars</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/chicago-sinkhole/2092965/
</link>
  <description>A sinkhole swallowed three cars on the southeast side of Chicago on Thursday, injuring one person.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 09:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Awful April: Spring hard to find across northern USA</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/weather/2013/04/29/cold-snowy-spring-weather/2121737/
</link>
  <description>April has been a freakishly cold month across much of the northern USA, with temperatures that are more typical of winter than spring.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 17:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Atlanta educators face hefty bail over cheating scandal</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/02/atlanta-school-cheating-scandal/2045139/
</link>
  <description>Educators accused in a massive cheating scandal at the city's public schools began turning themselves in at Fulton County Jail on Tuesday, with some lawyers complaining about the high bonds their clients face.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 06:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Broadcaster Al Michaels arrested, charged with DUI in California</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/21/al-michaels-arrested-for-dui/2100767/
</link>
  <description>Do you believe in designated drivers?!</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 10:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Louisville's Kevin Ware is moving around on crutches</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/01/louisville-kevin-ware-moving-on-crutches/2042351/
</link>
  <description>The sophomore guard, who broke his leg Sunday, took several steps around his hospital room.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 12:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Carnival ship fails health inspection</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/cruiselog/2013/04/11/carnival-fascination-cdc-health-inspection/2074175/
</link>
  <description>Citing live flies, dried food waste and a </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 12:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2nd teen hiker rescued in California canyon</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/04/california-hikers/2052163/
</link>
  <description>A second teenage hiker missing since Sunday was rescued Thursday in a rugged canyon near Los Angeles.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 07:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>NFL draft: Round 2 pick-by-pick analysis</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/26/nfl-draft-second-round-two-selections/2115477/
</link>
  <description>Every pick from the second round of the 2013 NFL draft.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 15:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Autopsy shows 'Buckwild' star Shain Gandee's death was accidental</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/04/02/buckwild-shain-gandee/2045783/
</link>
  <description>Autopsy shows 'Buckwild' star Shain Gandee's died of carbon monoxide poisioning outside Charleston, W. Va.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 12:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Size indeed matters, suggests male attractiveness study</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/08/size-male-attractiveness/2063951/
</link>
  <description>So much for that nice smile and neat haircut, women are indeed looking for a well-endowed guy, suggests am Australian study of male attractiveness</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 16:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Teen Mom' star Farrah Abraham sells sex tape</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/29/farrah-abraham-sex-tape-not-guilty-dui/2122101/
</link>
  <description>Farrah Abraham closes deal for adult video with Vivid Entertainment.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 18:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Domestic dispute led to Wash. shootings that killed 5</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/22/washington-shooting/2102603/
</link>
  <description>There was no immediate word what set off the gunfire in an apartment complex south of Seattle that has led to the death of 5 people, including a suspect.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 03:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lawyer: Widow of alleged Boston bomber suspected nothing</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/22/bombing-suspect-wife/2104315/
</link>
  <description>The young widow of Boston Marathon bombing suspect Tamerlan Tsarnaev learned of his alleged role in the attacks the same way millions of Americans did: She saw it on TV.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 17:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Boston amputee to fiancée: 'I am sorry for being there'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/22/boston-amputee-fiancee/2104883/
</link>
  <description>Jen Regan of Stoneham, Mass. spoke publicly for the first time Monday about the challenges facing her fiancé, Marc Fucarile, severely injured in the Boston Marathon bombings.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 18:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lindsey Vonn is watching boyfriend Tiger Woods at the Masters</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/11/lindsey-vonn-tiger-woods-masters-golf/2073673/
</link>
  <description>Tiger's girlfriend is there supporting his run in the Masters.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 10:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>For Reese Witherspoon, arrest is a 'PR nightmare'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/22/reese-witherspoon-arrest-fallout/2103425/
</link>
  <description>There's the art of persuasion, and then there's the power of perception.   In Hollywood, perception is guarded carefully by publicists, employed by studios and stars to keep projects hot and celebs in the</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 14:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kevin Ware never wants to 'watch replay' of gruesome injury</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/01/kevin-ware-on-gruesome-leg-break-not-a-lifetime-injury/2043461/
</link>
  <description>Kevin Ware </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 16:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Boat owner shaken after finding bombing suspect</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/20/boston-bombing-suspect-boat-backyard/2099377/
</link>
  <description>The man who found the Boston bombing suspect in his boat Friday night may be a hero, but he's an angry hero if the boat got shot up in the gunfire that preceded the fugitive's capture, a neighbor said.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 13 17:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Overwhelming kindness follows Boston Marathon blast</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/15/boston-marathon-blast-help/2086273/
</link>
  <description>Some acts of decency grew out of a terrible event.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 20:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Beauty Katherine Webb quits 'Splash' because of injury</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/17/injured-katherine-webb-quits-splash/2089957/
</link>
  <description>Beauty queen Katherine Webb had to bow out of the diving show.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 08:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Va. mall gunman announced shooting online minutes before</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/12/2-injured-1-in-custody-after-shooting-at-va-mall/2078633/
</link>
  <description>An 18-year-old community college student was charged with wounding two women with a shotgun at a mall branch of the school in southwestern Virginia Friday afternoon.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 15:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Man shoots himself in the head during NRA 500 at Texas</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nascar/2013/04/14/fan-death-investigation-texas-motor-speedway/2081395/
</link>
  <description>A medical examiner says a man who died in the infield during the NRA 500 at Texas Motor Speedway shot himself in the head.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 13 03:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Zack Greinke breaks collarbone in bench-clearing brawl</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2013/04/12/quentin-charges-greinke-after-being-hit-by-pitch/2076525/
</link>
  <description>Zack Greinke fractured his left collarbone in a bench-clearing brawl during the Dodgers' victory over the Padres, prompting enraged Matt Kemp to confront Carlos Quentin in the clubhouse tunnel after the game .</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 00:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Third Marathon death: Boston U. grad student from China</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/boston-marathon-scene-healing/2087583/
</link>
  <description>A day after tragedy struck the Boston Marathon, the city begins to move forward.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 11:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>After Boston blasts, Obama vows to get answers</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/15/explosions-crowd-boston-marathon/2085539/
</link>
  <description>Warns Americans not to jump to conclusions about who is responsible.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 16:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Dad of 8-year-old mourns: 'My dear son Martin has died'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/boston-bombing-boy-victim-8-year-old/2087645/
</link>
  <description>Family was cheering friends on in marathon when bomb exploded</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 13:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Famed movie critic Roger Ebert dies</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/04/critic-roger-ebert-dead/2053935/
</link>
  <description>The film critic fought salivary gland and thyroid cancer for a decade.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 15:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'American Idol' Top 4 results: The live blog</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/idolchatter/2013/04/25/american-idol-top-four-results-live-blog/2114115/
</link>
  <description>Which singers are in danger of going home? And what's the twist Ryan Seacrest promised?</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 19:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bodies recovered of 2 kids buried at N.C. work site</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/08/trapped-children-underground-dead/2062227/
</link>
  <description>Emergency crews early Monday found the bodies of two young children who were buried by a wall of dirt at a home construction site in rural North Carolina.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 00:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>NFL draft: Round 3 pick-by-pick analysis</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/26/nfl-draft-third-round-three-selections/2115513/
</link>
  <description>Every pick from the third round of the 2013 NFL draft.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 15:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Sharon Osbourne 'devastated' about Ozzy's relapse</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/23/sharon-osbourne-devastated-by-ozzy-relapse/2106951/
</link>
  <description>On Tuesday's episode of The Talk, Sharon Osbourne admitted she's 'upset' about husband Ozzy's relapse.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 14:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Disfigured veteran deals with disrespect at home</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/25/disfigured-veteran-deals-with-disrespect-at-home-/2113535/
</link>
  <description>Tony Porta, disfigured in Iraq, has sustained additional wounds at home.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 16:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Boston bombing suspects' mom in terror database</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/26/boston-bombing-suspects-mom-terror-database/2115939/
</link>
  <description>About 18 months before the Boston bombings, the CIA added the mother of the two suspects to a terrorism database after Russian authorities raised concerns she and her oldest son were religious militants.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 13:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Holmes' doctor warned police before Colo. theater attack</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/04/colorado-theater-james-holmes-records/2054753/
</link>
  <description>A University of Colorado psychiatrist told campus police a month before the Aurora movie theater attack that James Holmes had homicidal thoughts and was a public danger, according to records unsealed Thursday.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 19:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Obama seeks reprise of Speaker Pelosi</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/theoval/2013/04/04/obama-pelosi-2014-congressional-elections/2052145/
</link>
  <description>President Obama wants to work with congressional Republicans and all that, but he is also making it clear he wants Democrats to re-take control of the U.S. House and re-install Speaker Pelosi</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Buckwild' star Shain Gandee found dead</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/04/01/mtv-buckwild/2042865/
</link>
  <description>Buckwild star Shain Gandee found dead</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 14:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Rutgers fires coach Mike Rice, more actions ahead?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/03/amid-abuse-backlash-rutgers-fires-coach-mike-rice/2048903/
</link>
  <description>Rutgers University has fired coach Mike Rice less than 24 hours after revealing video footage.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 10:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Nicki Minaj: Lil Wayne 'refused to touch me'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/music/2013/04/03/nicki-minaj-lil-wayne-high-school-video/2049033/
</link>
  <description>You probably can't tell from Nicki Minaj's steamy new music video, </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 10:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>M*A*S*H star Allan Arbus dies at 95</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/23/mash-star-allan-arbus-dies-at-95/2106421/
</link>
  <description>Allan Arbus, known to many of us at the psychiatrist Maj. Sidney Freedman from M*A*S*H, has died at age 95.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 12:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>USA TODAY founder Al Neuharth dies at 89</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/al-neuharth-newspaper-founder-dies-at-89/2097995/
</link>
  <description>Allen H. Neuharth, the newspaper visionary and former Gannett chairman who founded USA TODAY, helped create a museum dedicated to news and became one of the industry's most influential and sometimes</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 18:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>American student gang raped in Brazil</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/02/rio-rape-american/2046819/
</link>
  <description>An American woman was gang raped and beaten aboard a public transport van while her French boyfriend was shackled, hit with a crowbar and forced to watch the attacks after the pair boarded the vehicle in Rio de Janeiro's showcase Copacabana beach neighborhood, police said.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 13:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>8-year-old family dog kills Georgia toddler</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/25/pit-bull-kills-toddler/2113713/
</link>
  <description>UNION CITY, Ga. — A family dog who had never shown aggression before  attacked and killed a 2-year-old boy  Wednesday in a subdivision about 15 miles south of Atlanta, police said. The mother, Angela Rutledge,</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 17:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kate Upton dating Diddy?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/10/kate-upton-dating-diddy/2070121/
</link>
  <description>Diddyup, everyone.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Man in cowboy hat in Boston photo faced many tragedies</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/newser-boston-marathon-iconic-photo/2087515/
</link>
  <description>Carlos Arredondo was waiting at the Boston Marathon finish line for runners who were racing on behalf of fallen soldiers -- one of those fallen soldiers being Arredondo's son -- and handing out American flags</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 10:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>No TV? 5 million U.S. households bid boob tube goodbye</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/07/zero-tv-homes/2061127/
</link>
  <description>Some people have had it with TV. They've had enough of the 100-plus channel universe. They don't like timing their lives around network show schedules. They're tired of $100-plus monthly bills.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 16:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Study: Synchronized sounds sharpen sleep</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/sciencefair/2013/04/11/sleep-memories-sounds/2075009/
</link>
  <description>Looking for better sleep? Lose the white-noise machine and listen for something a little more tuned to your brain's own rhythms, suggests a Thursday study performed by neuroscientists.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Pat Summerall, called a 'broadcasting giant,' has died</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/16/pat-summerall-cbs-fox-nfl/2088571/
</link>
  <description>For many sports fans in the 1960s through the 1990s, Pat Summerall was the voice of the NFL, starting with CBS' Sunday telecasts and later with Fox, famously paired for much of that time with John Madden.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 17:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Easter Egg Roll: Celebs, tots romp on White House lawn</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/01/obama-easter-egg-roll/2041811/
</link>
  <description>The Easter Bunny, dozens of professional athletes and thousands of children were hippity-hopping across the White House's South Lawn Monday for the annual egg roll.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 10:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Man slices arms with saws at Calif. Home Depot</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/10/man-slices-arms-home-depot/2072891/
</link>
  <description>Unidentified man grabbed hand saws and cut his arms to the bone inside a Home Depot store.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 23:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Gold selloff intensifies, price plunges 9.35%</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/markets/2013/04/15/gold-prices-tumble/2083537/
</link>
  <description>Gold is being mauled by the bear again in early trading Monday, knocking the yellow metal down more than 7% and below the key $1,400 per-ounce level. Gold is now down more than 26% from its Aug. 2011 peak.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 07:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kevin Ware on Louisville teammate that 'touched my heart'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/bigeast/2013/04/04/luke-hancock-kevin-ware-support-broken-leg/2052185/
</link>
  <description>Luke Hancock was the first person to reach Louisville's Kevin Ware after his broken leg against Duke. The teammate offered support and a prayer that touched Ware's heart.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 08:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Digging into the past of NCAA President Mark Emmert</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/02/ncaa-president-emmert-previous-cases-uconn-lsu/2047607/
</link>
  <description>A look at how NCAA President Mark Emmert handled scandals at previous jobs at UConn and LSU. Criticism has swirled over how the NCAA has handled the cases of Penn State and Miami under his leadership.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 18:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Officer accused of having Trayvon Martin targets</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/13/officer-accused-of-having-trayvon-martin-target/2080989/
</link>
  <description>Sgt. Ron King was leading a target practice with two other officers and a civilian when he pulled out the Trayvon Martin targets on April 4, officials said.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 21:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Winds scrub lift of World Trade Center spire</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/29/world-trade-center-911-human-remains/2120359/
</link>
  <description>When the last pieces of its spire rise to the roof of the One World Trade Center, the skyscraper that replaces the fallen twin towers will be just feet from becoming the highest in the Western Hemisphere.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 08:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Up to 15 dead, at least 160 injured in Texas plant blast</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/17/wace-plant-explosion/2092223/
</link>
  <description>Blasts at a Texas fertilizer plant leveled buildings for blocks in every direction.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 22:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>As manhunt ends, new questions emerge in Boston bombings</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2013/04/19/suspect-in-custody-newspaper-says/2095845/
</link>
  <description>The Chechen brothers at the heart of the Boston Marathon bombing investigation lived regular American lives - until something changed them.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 02:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Save Our Shows: Have you voted yet?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/04/07/save-our-shows/2053671/
</link>
  <description>The voting booth is still open in USA TODAY's 16th annual Save Our Shows poll, which asks readers to weigh in on which of 16 prime-time sitcoms and dramas </description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 19:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Dick Van Dyke bothered by 'neurological disorder'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/18/dick-van-dyke-battling-neurological-disorder/2093167/
</link>
  <description>The actor, 87, has had to cancel a New York appearance planned for next week.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 10:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Michigan's John Beilein explains his coaching gaffe</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/09/michigan-foul-coach-john-beilein-coaching-mistake/2066057/
</link>
  <description>Michigan wanted to get the ball back by fouling late in the NCAA men's basketball championship game, but Louisville wasn't in the bonus.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 00:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'American Idol' results: Which singer said goodbye?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/idolchatter/2013/04/11/american-idol-top-6-results/2076183/
</link>
  <description>It's down to five now. Is there a guy left on 'American Idol'?</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Leave It to Beaver's' Lumpy Rutherford dies</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/04/15/jerry-mathers-frank-bank-leave-it-to-beaver/2085123/
</link>
  <description>He didn't have Wally Cleaver's good looks, Eddie Haskell's conniving personality nor Beaver Cleaver's penchant for getting into trouble, but  Lumpy Rutherford will always be remembered as one of TV sitcoms' bullies</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 15:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Man of Steel' trailer puts the 'S' in Superman</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2013/04/17/man-of-steel-superman-movie-trailer/2089651/
</link>
  <description>A new </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 00:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Trayvon Martin's parents settle with Fla. HOA</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/05/trayvon-martins-parents-settle/2058239/
</link>
  <description>SANFORD, Fla. (AP) — The parents of a teenager who was fatally shot by a neighborhood watch volunteer last year have settled a wrongful-death claim against the homeowners association of the Florida subdivision where their son was killed.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 21:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'American Idol' results: Who went home?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/idolchatter/2013/04/04/american-idol-results-who-went-home/2054989/
</link>
  <description>Another guy goes home. But that wasn't the big surprise.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Officer: Trayvon Martin target a 'no-shoot training aid'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/14/travyon-martin-ron-king/2081467/
</link>
  <description>A Florida police officer fired for bringing targets resembling Trayvon Martin to a gun range apologized to the shooting victim's family but said the target is a valuable training tool.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 13 11:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Obama apologizes to California AG for comment on looks</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/05/obama-kamala-harris-attorney-general/2056991/
</link>
  <description>President Obama has apologized to California Attorney General Kamala Harris for commenting Thursday on her looks, an aide said Friday.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 14:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Good news for cable cord-cutters in Aereo win</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/04/01/aereo-wins-appeals-court-ruling/2042527/
</link>
  <description>A federal appeals court rejects an appeal by TV station owners, allowing Aereo to continue operation</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 12:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kevin Ware saw Rick Pitino's eyes and thought, 'Oh my God'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/03/kevin-ware-interview-sportscenter-louisville/2048919/
</link>
  <description>The injured Louisville player gave his first interview Wednesday morning.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 11:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lindsey Vonn is turning heads at the Masters</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/11/lindsey-vonn-tiger-woods-the-masters-augusta-turning-heads/2073823/
</link>
  <description>Take a picture, guys.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 11:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>China quake leaves nearly 200 dead, 6,700 injured</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/19/chinas-sichuan-earthquake/2098249/
</link>
  <description>A powerful earthquake struck the steep hills of China's southwestern Sichuan province on Saturday, leaving at least 156 people dead and more than 5,500 injured.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 20:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Google, YouTube, Twitter get into April Fools' action</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/04/01/april-fools-day-google-youtube-online/2041159/
</link>
  <description>Twitter, Google and YouTube are having some fun this April Fools' Day.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 00:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bomb suspects' mother will 'never' accept their guilt</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/25/boston-bomb-mother-tsarnaev-dagestan-news-conference/2111855/
</link>
  <description>The mother of the two Boston bombings suspects told reporters at a news conference Thursday that she will never accept the idea that her sons carried out the attacks.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 09:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'American Idol': Who soared, who stunk?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/idolchatter/2013/04/10/american-idol-top-6-recap-lazaro-arbos-candice-glover/2072727/
</link>
  <description>Wednesday's show had one of the best performances ever — and one of the worst.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 22:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>States look to tax guns, ammo</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/07/gun-taxes-owners-second-amendment/2049363/
</link>
  <description>Six states are instituting or considering taxes on purchases of guns, ammunition</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Suspect visible through ambulance window</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/boston-suspect-ambulance/2098489/
</link>
  <description>A glimpse of 19-year-old bombing suspect, Dzhokhar Tsarnaev, is visible through an ambulance window as the Boston Marathon bombing suspect is transported to the hospital.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 23:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Live coverage of George Zimmerman trial</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2013/04/16/live-news-coverage/2087403/
</link>
  <description>USA TODAY Live News Coverage</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 10:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jon Jones stops Chael Sonnen in first round at UFC 159</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ufc/2013/04/28/ufc-159-jon-jones-stops-chael-sonnen-first-round/2118543/
</link>
  <description>NEWARK, N.J. — While longtime middleweight Chael Sonnen was a long shot in his bid for the UFC light-heavyweight title, some believed that if he could get champ Jon Jones on his back, he might have a chance.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 01:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Charges dropped in ricin case; new home searched</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/23/ricin-letters-suspect-hearing/2105613/
</link>
  <description>JACKSON, Miss. -- After U.S. Magistrate Judge Allan Alexander issued an order for dismissal against the man accused of sending ricin-laced letters to President Obama, the nation has turned its eye to J. Everett Dutschke.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 05:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Cyberattackers hack into LivingSocial, 50 million customers impacted</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/26/liviing-social-hacked-passwords-amazon/2116485/
</link>
  <description>LivingSocial hacked but company officials say credit card information was not stolen</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 17:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Texas blast death toll at 14; only 1 or 2 missing</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/west-texas-fertilizer-blast/2095817/
</link>
  <description>Teams finished searching debris in devastated four-block area  after fertilizer plant explosion.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 01:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Naked Chelsea Handler, Conan O'Brien fight in the shower</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/04/naked-chelsea-handler-conan-obrien-fight-in-the-shower/2052207/
</link>
  <description>Look out. Conan O'Brien and Chelsea Handler are naked in a shower, fighting. They're even giving each other black eyes.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 08:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Man who sawed arms in Home Depot still critical</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/11/home-depot-man-critical/2075025/
</link>
  <description>A man who intentionally sawed his arms to the bone in a Home Depot store in California remained hospitalized in critical condition on Thursday while investigators tried to determine what led to the horrific action.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 15:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jodi Arias trial nearing its conclusion, judge says</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/24/arias-trial-nearing-its-conclusion/2111403/
</link>
  <description>PHOENIX -- The end is near. Maricopa County Superior Court Judge Sherry Stephens told the Jodi Arias jury that the guilt-and-innocence phase of the four-month-long murder trial will end a week from Friday.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 22:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Miss. killer overpowered detective during questioning</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/05/jackson-officer-suspect-dead-at-police-headquarters/2055703/
</link>
  <description>JACKSON, Miss. — A homicide suspect argued with an 18-year police veteran in an interview room Thursday, overpowering him and shooting him to death, law enforcement officials said.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 08:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Wolff: Someone at NBC should be fired</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/columnist/wolff/2013/03/31/michael-wolff-someone-at-nbc-should-be-fired/2040775/
</link>
  <description>Comcast's Steve Burke has found himself in the middle of an old-fashioned network drama at NBC,</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 13 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>AP Twitter feed hacked; no attack at White House</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/theoval/2013/04/23/obama-carney-associated-press-hack-white-house/2106757/
</link>
  <description>People are jumpy these days Social media and the stock market went wild, briefly, with this (hacked) AP tweet appeared: </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 13:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Dramatic images from West, Texas, explosion</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/west-texas-explosion/2093663/
</link>
  <description>The blast in a West, Texas plant is responsible for death, injury and destruction.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 12:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Diamond tribute: Yankees play 'Sweet Caroline'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2013/04/16/new-york-yankees-boston-marathon-sweet-caroline/2088269/
</link>
  <description>The Yankees will co-opt a Red Sox singalong to pay tribute to marathon victims</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Why Tim Tebow won't make an NFL roster in 2013</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/15/tim-tebow-reasons-he-wont-be-in-nfl-jets/2083741/
</link>
  <description>Tim Tebow (with Jets assistant special teams coach Louis Aguilar) arrives at the team facility for offseason workouts. (Photo: Mel Evans/AP) Tim Tebow appears to be following up on his promise to arrive at New</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 11:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>SEC, FBI probe fake tweet that rocked stocks</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/23/hack-attack-on-associated-press-shows-vulnerable-media/2106985/
</link>
  <description>The latest cyberattack on a venerable institution shows just how vulnerable we are to Twitter, Facebook and other social media.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 21:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>World's largest yacht - 590 ft. - is launched</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/13/lurssen-yacht-azzam/2067709/
</link>
  <description>A new yacht launched Friday by Lürssen, the German luxury boat builder, is now the largest motor yacht in the world. It's name is Azzam, and at 590 feet long, it has</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 15:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2 linked to al-Qaeda arrested in Canada terror plot</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2013/04/22/canada-terror-plot-arrested/2104065/
</link>
  <description>Canadian law enforcement has arrested two suspects in Toronto for allegedly plotting a terrorist attack in Canada, Canadian media reported.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 14:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Despite penalty, 14-year-old makes cut at Masters</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2013/04/12/14-year-old-guan-tianlang-masters-second-round/2078127/
</link>
  <description>The 14-year-old kept his cool on Friday and gave himself a chance to make the cut.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 14:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Boston suspects' mosque has ties to convicted terrorists, fugitives and radical speakers.</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/23/boston-mosque-radicals/2101411/
</link>
  <description>The Boston bombing suspects attended a mosque in Cambridge that has been tied to convicted terrorists suspects, fugitives and radical speakers.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 16:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>The best undrafted players of the 2013 NFL draft</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/28/best-undrafted-players-2013-nfl-draft/2118637/
</link>
  <description>Two quarterbacks lead the way on list of passed-over prospects.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 03:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>David Letterman grills Lindsay Lohan about rehab</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/09/david-letterman-grills-lindsay-lohan-about-rehab/2069337/
</link>
  <description>In her first interview since November 2012 and her fifth visit to the Late Show with David Letterman, Lindsay Lohan got grilled by Dave on Tuesday's show.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 20:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>War-torn Caucasus may be at root of the brothers' rage</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/19/boston-bombing-brothers-ties-chechnya/2097605/
</link>
  <description>The journey that led two brothers to become suspects in the Boston Marathon attack has its roots in the strife-ridden violent Muslim region of Russia known as North Caucasus.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 17:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Sara Gilbert's engaged to Linda Perry</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/08/sara-gilbert-gets-engaged-to-linda-perry/2064131/
</link>
  <description>Sara Gilbert shared big news on The Talk.  She announced she is engaged to girlfriend rock musician Linda Perry.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 15:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Report: Apple to start new iPhone production</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/04/02/apple-iphone/2046997/
</link>
  <description>The iPhone maker is getting ready to crank up production on its next iPhone, according to a report</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 14:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Fed: Redesigned $100 bill coming in October</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/24/redesigned-100-bill/2109809/
</link>
  <description>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve announced Wednesday that it will begin circulating a redesigned $100 bill this fall, more than two years after its initial target. The Fed has set a new target date of Oct</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 13:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bomb suspects planned second attack: Times Square</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/25/boston-bombing-times-square-dahokhar-tsarnaev-attack/2112991/
</link>
  <description>Three days after the Boston Marathon bombing, the Tsarnaev brothers intended to detonate their remaining explosives in Times Square but were thwarted by a bungled carjacking.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 13:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Louisville says Kevin Ware will have no medical bills</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/01/kevin-ware-louisville-cardinals-medical-bills/2044871/
</link>
  <description>Louisville guard Kevin Ware isn't expected to face out-of-pocket medical expenses after sustaining a compound fracture in his lower right leg and undergoing surgery, a school official says.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 23:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>3 planets discovered with right size, location for life</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/04/18/nasa-kepler-planets/2094325/
</link>
  <description>NASA's planet-hunting telescope has discovered three planets that seem like ideal places for some sort of life to flourish. They are at a distance that could allow for water, a key ingredient for life.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 15:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>5 of the biggest surprises from Day 2 of NFL draft</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/27/nfl-draft-five-surprises-day-2/2116985/
</link>
  <description>It was such a low-key, even boring, 2013 NFL Draft until the New York Jets got the Friday night party started with a wild, second-round cannonball into deeper quarterback controversy that rocked Radio Music</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 13 00:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Analysts debate whether signs point to N. Korea attack</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/10/south-korea-cyberattack/2069765/
</link>
  <description>Neighboring countries to North Korea are not panicked by its threats because it has not taken steps experts say must happen before a serious attack is launched.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 01:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Mock draft 5.0 (final): How many QBs join Geno Smith in Round 1?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/24/mock-draft-luke-joeckel-geno-smith-ryan-nassib/2108223/
</link>
  <description>If we know one thing about the NFL draft, it's that general managers will wheel and deal away Thursday night; a post-merger record 19 first-round picks ultimately switched hands in 2012. With that as a</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Was 9/11 landing gear hidden on purpose?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/27/sept-11-landing-gear-plane-new-york/2117305/
</link>
  <description>After surveyors discovered what appears to be plane landing gear from the 9/11 attacks, authorities are wondering how it got sandwiched between two buildings—one of them housing a much-debated Islamic community center.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 13 10:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Reese Witherspoon arrest video surfaces</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/23/reese-witherspoon-arrest-video-handcuffed/2107129/
</link>
  <description>Reese Witherspoon arrest  footage surfaces.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 15:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Which cities are the worst for people with allergies?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/02/allergy-cities-weather/2007489/
</link>
  <description>Jackson, Miss., is the worst city for people with allergies, according to a new report.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 00:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>10 best craft brew states in America</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/destinations/2013/04/21/10-best-craft-brew-states-in-america/2098517/
</link>
  <description>The craft beer movement continues to boom across the USA.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ancient Maya civilization's roots deepen</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/sciencefair/2013/04/25/maya-olmec-ceibal/2110781/
</link>
  <description>The ancient Maya started building their storied cities amid a construction boom in Central America around 1000 B.C., archaeologists report.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 14:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>GM, Ford to jointly develop 10-speed transmissions</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2013/04/15/ford-general-motors-gm-transmissions/2083485/
</link>
  <description>Ford and General Motors cooperate on high-tech nine- and 10-speed automatic transmission to save money, boost mpg, improve performance.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 03:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Pro golf elite sound off on Tiger's penalty</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/13/tiger-woods-penalty-2013-masters-twitter-reaction/2079759/
</link>
  <description>Twitter reacts to Tiger's penalty at Augusta</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>North Korean video shows imagined strikes on U.S.</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/13/north-korean-propaganda-video/2080805/
</link>
  <description>A video released by Saturday by North Korea shows nuclear launches against the United States reaching four sites, including Washington, D.C., California, Hawaii and Colorado Springs.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Matt Kemp, Carlos Quentin separated by police while leaving Petco Park</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2013/04/12/dodgers-matt-kemp-confronts-padres-carlos-quentin/2076637/
</link>
  <description>SAN DIEGO (AP) — Dodgers slugger Matt Kemp confronted San Diego's Carlos Quentin as they were leaving Petco Park after the teams had a bench-clearing brawl that left Los Angeles pitcher Zack Greinke with a</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 03:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Michael Jordan was poisoned before flu game, says trainer</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/18/michael-jordan-food-poisoning-flu-game-chicago-bulls/2093631/
</link>
  <description>MJ's former trainer has a new theory about why Jordan was ill for finals game.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 13:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lottery-winning hairdresser says she can prove her case</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/10/hairdressers-lottery-lawsuit/2069845/
</link>
  <description>INDIANAPOLIS -- A hairdresser, blocked last month from collecting a $9 million state lottery jackpot in a dispute with seven former co-workers, claims she has proof the winning ticket was not among those she</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 06:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Uncle calls Boston suspect 'loser,' says 'turn yourself in'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/uncle-boston-suspect/2096949/
</link>
  <description>An uncle of the two suspects in the Boston Marathon bombing says 19-year-old Dzhozkar Tsarnaev, the living suspect who is still on the run, should turn himself in to police and ask for forgiveness.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 12:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>New York police officer kills boyfriend, son, self</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/15/new-york-police-officer-kills-boyfriend-son/2084429/
</link>
  <description>A New York City police officer shot her boyfriend, turned the gun on her 1-year-old son and then shot herself in an apparent double murder-suicide at her home Monday morning.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 12:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Trailer alert! 'Hunger Games: Catching Fire'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2013/04/15/trailer-hunger-games-catching-fire/2083909/
</link>
  <description></description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 10:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Tiger Woods cursed on air after his first broadcast shot at the Masters</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/11/tiger-woods-masters-curse-expletive/2074781/
</link>
  <description>What did the Masters favorite say after his approach into No. 11?</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 14:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>4-year-old boy accidentally kills Tenn. deputy's wife</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/08/boy-accidental-shooting/2064627/
</link>
  <description>LEBANON, Tenn. — A 4-year-old who picked up a gun at a family cookout killed the wife of a Wilson County sheriff's deputy, authorities said Monday.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 16:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Cohabitation first is new norm for unmarrieds with kids</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/04/cohabitation-families-pregnancy/2050073/
</link>
  <description>New federal data - some never reported before - give a fuller picture of cohabitation in America with a focus on a women's first time live-in relationship with a male.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Reports: Halle Berry is pregnant</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/05/halle-berry-is-pregnant/2056827/
</link>
  <description>Big news breaking about Halle Berry. TMZ reports the actress, who is 46, is three-months pregnant with her second child.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 14:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Omaha Beef indoor team offers Tim Tebow $75-per-game contract</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/30/tim-tebow-omaha-beef-contract-offer/2124481/
</link>
  <description>The Omaha Beef have a job waiting for Tim Tebow if he wants it — and the Nebraska indoor football team will even pay him $75 a game.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 13 15:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>NYPD: Part of 9/11 plane's landing gear found</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/26/sept11-plane-nyc/2116431/
</link>
  <description>Police say a piece of landing gear believed to be from one of the planes destroyed in the Sept. 11 attacks has been discovered wedged between two New York City buildings.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 16:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Toll in Bangladesh building collapse climbs to 275</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/24/bangladesh-building-collapse/2108727/
</link>
  <description>The death toll from an eight-story building housing several garment factories that collapsed near Bangladesh's capital Wednesday morning has reached at least 194 people.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 04:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Obama: We need to close Guantanamo Bay</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/30/obama-news-conference-100-days/2123391/
</link>
  <description>President Obama holds a news conference at 10:30 a.m.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 13 10:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Investigators probe Lion Air crash in Bali</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2013/04/13/lion-air-plane-skids-into-sea-in-bali-indonesia/2079623/
</link>
  <description>Plane with more than 100 passengers skidded into the sea on the Indonesian resort island.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 05:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Wesley Snipes finishes jail time for tax evasion</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/05/wesley-snipes-finishes-jail-time-for-tax-evasion/2057455/
</link>
  <description>Wesley Snipes has moved from prison to house arrest.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Dancing With the Stars' eliminates sweet athlete</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/23/dancing-with-the-stars-sends-star-packing-ortiz/2108099/
</link>
  <description>'Dancing With the Stars' sends another star home. Who got the boot this week?</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 22:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Sen. McCaskill says there's a suspect in possible ricin-tainted letter</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/ricin-letter-wicker/2088969/
</link>
  <description>An letter addressed to Sen. Roger Wicker, R-Miss, tested positive for ricin or another poison, says Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid, D-Nev., according to the Associated Press.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 18:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Pilot Flying J in damage control</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/22/pilot-flying-j-damage-control/2105057/
</link>
  <description>NASHVILLE, Tenn. -- In the wake of last week's FBI raid and an ongoing federal probe into a rebate scheme, Pilot Flying J CEO Jimmy Haslam on Monday announced changes the company is taking.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 20:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Amanda Knox: 'I have a life that I want to live'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/30/amanda-knox-interview-retrial-italy/2121871/
</link>
  <description>An interview with Amanda Knox on the battle for her freedom, the lessons she's learned and her dreams for the future</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 13 00:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Disappointed by draft position, Geno Smith fires agents</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/jets/2013/04/30/quarterback-geno-smith-fire-agents-after-nfl-draft/2124113/
</link>
  <description>After being selected by the Jets in the second round, the quarterback is looking for new representation</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 13 13:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Man tries to take photo of beaver; it kills him</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/mailworld/2013/04/11/newser-beaver-kills-man/2074145/
</link>
  <description>Forget sharks: It's beavers that are truly terrifying. A fisherman in Belarus was bitten to death by one, and all he was doing was trying to take its picture, Sky News reports. The man spotted the beaver while</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 12:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jada Pinkett Smith responds to open marriage rumors</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/04/jada-pinkett-smith-responds-to-open-marriage-rumors/2053931/
</link>
  <description>Will Smith and Jada Pinkett Smith have been married for 15 years, and they have long been plagued by rumors that an </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 16:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ben Affleck to live on $1.50 a day</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/23/ben-affleck-to-live-on-150-a-day/2106553/
</link>
  <description>Could you live on $1.50 a day?  Ben Affleck, Josh Groban, Sophia Bush and Debi Mazar are among the celebs show have committed to take the 2013 Live Below the Line challenge issue by The Global Poverty Project.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 12:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>10 longest bridges to drive across</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/destinations/2013/04/28/10-longest-bridges-to-drive-across/2118739/
</link>
  <description>The world's biggest bridges cater to cars, and we've rounded up 10 memorable crossings.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 09:08:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lelisa Desisa, Rita Jeptoo win Boston Marathon</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/olympics/2013/04/15/lelisa-desisa-rita-jeptoo-boston-marathon/2084501/
</link>
  <description>BOSTON (AP) — Lelisa Desisa of Ethiopia has won the 117th edition of the Boston Marathon.It's just his second race at the 26.2-mile distance. Desisa outsprinted two other East Africans down Boylston Street to</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 12:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jordan extremist 'happy to see the horror' of bombing</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/15/boston-marathon-explosions-jordan/2086237/
</link>
  <description>The head of an extremist Jordanian Muslim Salafi group said early Tuesday that he was </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 19:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Retirement: Plan ahead for these 5 nasty surprises</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/columnist/brooks/2013/04/08/retirement-shocks-pension-insurance/2056533/
</link>
  <description>You think you're all set for retirement. You've been saving for years. And you're just two years away. Then, boom! Something happens and you are back to square one.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 15:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Dead man found dangling from Calif. high rise</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/01/sacramento-tower-graffiti-rope-dead/2043931/
</link>
  <description>An apparent graffiti tagger was found dead in a rope harness on the side of an 18-story office tower near the California Capitol on Monday morning, Sacramento police said.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 17:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Obama to visit Boston Thursday, calls attack terrorism</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2013/04/16/obama-boston-marathon-bombing-remarks/2087565/
</link>
  <description>President Obama said Tuesday the FBI is investigating the Boston Marathon bombings as an </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 11:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Hooters tries surviving middle age with makeover</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/27/hooters-restaurant-turns-30-terrance-marks/2094799/
</link>
  <description>As if middle age isn't tough enough for regular folks, for Hooters, where every wrinkle counts and every blemish is magnified – it's agonizing. So it's undergoing a massive makeover.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 13 07:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jay Leno announces his departure from 'Tonight'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/04/03/leno-leaving-tonight-2014/2049497/
</link>
  <description>Jay Leno announces his departure from 'Tonight'</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 12:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'300: Rise of an Empire' heads to new seas</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2013/04/08/300-rise-of-an-empire-sea/2064101/
</link>
  <description>'300: Rise of an Empire' takes on a new look and philosophy from the original '300.'</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 19:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Masters reviews Tiger Woods' drop on 15; was it legal?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2013/04/13/masters-tiger-woods-drop-on-15th-hole/2079679/
</link>
  <description>Woods' drop on the 15th hole Friday might have violated rules.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 08:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Is next college sports realignment a split from NCAA?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2013/04/21/college-football-ncaa-split/2097115/
</link>
  <description>College football's most powerful entities will assemble in Pasadena, Calif., this week for meetings that will determine several aspects of the new playoff system that begins in 2014. It will be a celebration of progress and riches for the schools involved and a validation of the bowl industry, which kept its seat at the table despite heavy criticism in recent years.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 19:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Timeline: Manhunt for Boston bombing suspects</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/timeline-boston-marathon-suspects/2096123/
</link>
  <description>Within hours of releasing surveillance photos of the suspects in the Boston Marathon bombings, police followed a trail from Cambridge to Watertown, where a firefight ensued. This is what's currently known.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bombing survivor: 'He saved my life. He's a true hero'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/21/boston-bombing-survivor-grateful/2101403/
</link>
  <description>Kaitlynn Cates nearly lost her life during the Boston marathon bombing.  Yet today, she's feeling thankful.  Cates, 25, says she owes her life to a friend who rescued her after the bomb went off.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 19:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Air bag recalls involve 1.3 million vehicles in U.S.</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2013/04/11/toyota-honda-nissan-airbag-recall/2073183/
</link>
  <description>Carmakers Toyota, Honda and Nissan on Thursday recalled more than 3 million vehicles worldwide due to defects with air bags.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 02:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jodi Arias trial topics turn to fairy tales</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/04/jodi-arias-trial-topics-turn-to-fairy-tales/2055271/
</link>
  <description>PHOENIX -- Angry men, including the prosecutor, were the topic of conversation at the Jodi Arias murder trial on Thursday. So was the fairy tale Snow White.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 23:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'People' mag picks 'World's Most Beautiful Woman'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/24/people-mag-worlds-most-beautiful-woman-gwyneth-paltrow/2108791/
</link>
  <description>'People' mag picks 'World's Most Beautiful Woman' and it's Gwyneth Paltrow.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 07:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>A FGCU player and Florida cheerleader fraternize pregame</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/03/29/fgcu-player-florida-cheerleader/2037445/
</link>
  <description>Before the game, it's all smiles.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 13 23:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Tom Cruise on divorce: 'Did not expect that'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/09/tom-cruise-on-divorce-did-not-expect-that/2067411/
</link>
  <description>The star is finally opening up - a little - about his split from Katie Holmes.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 13:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>G-8 to N. Korea: Refrain from 'further provocative acts'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/11/north-korea-missile-test/2073229/
</link>
  <description>PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — As neighboring nations kept a close eye on missile movements in North Korea, people in the country's capital began celebrating a series of April holidays, including the</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 05:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>R.I. neighborhood shaken by connection to Boston case</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/20/boston-bombings-suspect-wife-family/2099833/
</link>
  <description>NORTH KINGSTOWN, R.I. – Katherine Russell and her parents live in the kind of neighborhood that has a bike path to the beach, where the lawns are neat and the dogs stay politely tucked behind electric fences.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 13 18:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Want to watch Tiger's first round at the Masters live? Too bad</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/10/tiger-woods-augusta-masters-first-round-online-stream/2070707/
</link>
  <description>The curious case of 2013 Masters featured group scheduling.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 13:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Kim Kardashian barely contains her curves</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/04/kim-kardashian-barely-contains-breasts-curves/2052571/
</link>
  <description>New photos of Kim Kardashian making a fro-yo run are causing big buzz for her big breasts.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 10:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Police chief details chase, capture of bombing suspects</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/21/police-chief-details-bomb-suspects-capture/2101501/
</link>
  <description>Watertown Police Chief Ed Deveau marveled that he's not at his desk planning a police officer's funeral.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 16:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Dead basking shark washes ashore on R.I. beach</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/28/dead-shark-ashore/2119961/
</link>
  <description>WESTERLY, R.I. (AP) — A 28-foot-long dead basking shark has washed ashore on a Rhode Island beach.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 23:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Roger Ebert's wife: He 'smiled, and passed away'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/05/roger-eberts-wife-he-smiled-and-passed-away/2055855/
</link>
  <description>Roger Ebert is resting in peace.    </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 09:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Suspect hunted in fatal stabbing of 8-year-old at home</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/28/girl-stabbed-california-manhunt/2119639/
</link>
  <description>Authorities in California are searching for the killer of an 8-year-old girl.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 18:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Johnson out, ex-CEO Ullman in at J.C. Penney</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/08/ron-johnson-penney-ceo/2064723/
</link>
  <description>Ron Johnson is out as JC Penney's CEO, CNBC is reporting, citing an unnamed source.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2013 NFL draft: Round 4 picks</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/26/nfl-draft-fourth-round-four-selections/2116365/
</link>
  <description>Every pick from the fourth round of the 2013 NFL draft.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 16:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Forecasting the NCAA basketball top 25 in 2013-14</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/09/forecasting-the-ncaa-basketball-top-25-in-2013-14/2061989/
</link>
  <description>USA TODAY Sports' college basketball staff previews what the top 25 will look like in 2013-14.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 02:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>S. Korea: N. Korea moves missile to east coast</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/04/north-korea-missile/2052139/
</link>
  <description>South Korea says North Korea has moved a missile with </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 06:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Frugal pope nixes bonus for Vatican employees</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/18/pope-francis-vatican-bonus/2094171/
</link>
  <description>The Vatican said Thursday that Pope Francis, known for his frugal ways, had decided Vatican employees won't be getting the bonus that traditionally comes with the election of a new pope.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 14:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>7-Eleven robbery not related to Boston bombing suspects</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/7-eleven-robbery-boston/2097915/
</link>
  <description>There was a 7-Eleven robbery in Cambridge last night, but it had nothing to do with the Boston Marathon bombing suspects. Margaret Chabris, the director of corporate communication at 7- Eleven.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 18:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Boston doctors 'finish the job' of traumatic amputations</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/marathons-wounded-victims/2087779/
</link>
  <description>Some Boston Marathon victims had as many as 40 pieces of shrapnel embedded in their bodies.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Robin Roberts hospitalized for 'a few days'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/18/robin-roberts-hospitalized-gma-infection/2092951/
</link>
  <description>If you've been wondering where exactly Robin Roberts has been lately, she's explaining it herself in a Facebook note.  The GMA anchor who hasn't been on the air this week was hospitalized 'for a few days.'</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 09:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Woman guilty of throwing husband's penis in garbage disposal</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/29/woman-cuts-off-penis/2121821/
</link>
  <description>SANTA ANA, Calif. (AP) — A Southern California jury has convicted a woman who was accused of drugging her estranged husband before severing his penis and tossing it in the garbage disposal. Jurors found</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 16:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>FCC overlooks Ortiz's passionate, profane speech to Red Sox fans</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/20/david-ortiz-boston-red-sox-speech-fcc/2100051/
</link>
  <description>Big Brother lets one slide.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 13 18:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Oops! Michelle Obama calls herself 'single mother'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/theoval/2013/04/05/obama-michelle-obama-single-mother/2056927/
</link>
  <description>One little slip of the tongue and Twitter goes crazy. First lady Michelle Obama accidentally described herself as a </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 14:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Masters: Snedeker, Cabrera top crowded leaderboard</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2013/04/13/brandt-snedeker-angel-cabrera-masters-third-round/2080873/
</link>
  <description>AUGUSTA, Ga. — A day that began with controversy over Tiger Woods and a two-shot penalty ended with Angel Cabrera and Brandt Snedeker on top of a crowded leaderboard at the Masters.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 19:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Toddler shoots Tenn. deputy's wife in unguarded moment</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/09/child-shooting-deputy-wife/2066289/
</link>
  <description>LEBANON, Tenn. — Only a few seconds passed from the time the handgun was placed on a bed to when a 4-year-old boy picked it up and pulled the trigger. Only a few seconds for a friendly cookout at a Wilson County deputy's home to turn tragic.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 07:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2 women hurt during L.A. manhunt to receive $4.2M</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/23/los-angeles-dorner-settlement/2107289/
</link>
  <description>Los Angeles will pay two women $4.2 million for wounds suffered when police shot up their truck during the February manhunt for former officer Christopher Dorner.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Basketball Hall of Fame finalist 'can't sleep' over snub</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nba/2013/04/07/spencer-haywood-basketball-hall-of-fame-not-inducted/2060479/
</link>
  <description>Spencer Haywood was told he was in, told he finally cracked the Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame entry 30 years after his last NBA game. The former ABA MVP and NBA All-Star was told wrong.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 11:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Save Our Shows: Vote ends, wait begins</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/04/28/usa-today-save-our-shows-poll/2116427/
</link>
  <description>No. 1 was 'CSI: NY,' but results among the 116,800 votes bear further investigation.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 19:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Brewers base runner 'steals' first base in odd play</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/brewers/2013/04/19/brewers-jean-segura-steals-first-base/2098519/
</link>
  <description>Brewers shortstop Jean Segura may be a baseball pioneer.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 23:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2013 American Idol Meter</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/music/2013/03/13/american-idol-meter/1974023/
</link>
  <description>Each week, see which American Idol contestants have the best chances of success.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 13 17:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Gas leak suspected in Prague explosion</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/29/prague-explosion/2120205/
</link>
  <description>Emergency workers search for people who may have been trapped in rubble when a powerful explosion rocked the old quarter of the Czech capital Monday.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 05:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Cut down by injury, Louisville's Kevin Ware cuts down net</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/04/09/louisville-kevin-ware-cuts-down-championship-net/2066145/
</link>
  <description>ATLANTA – The script played out like it was supposed to, like it had to. Because after a week of universal support from across the country, what other way could Kevin Ware have ended the season? Certainly, not</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 03:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Video of Texas explosion caught on cellphone</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/texas-fertilizer-explosion-cellphone-video/2093293/
</link>
  <description>An explosion at a Texas fertilizer plant knocks Erick Perez to the ground as he films the fire.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 11:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Joe Theismann feels shiver over Kevin Ware injury</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2013/03/31/kevin-ware-joe-theisman-broken-leg-injury/2040749/
</link>
  <description>A shiver went through Joe Theismann as he sat inside his Loudon County, Va. home office Sunday, watching the Duke-Louisville NCAA tournament game. The horrific right leg injury suffered by Louisville guard</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 13 19:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Drive On: New 4Runner looks like 'angry robot'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/driveon/2013/04/30/toyota-4runner-robot/2122731/
</link>
  <description>Has the aggressive look gone overboard with the new four-wheeler?</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 13 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ricin case resembles a Mississippi tall tale</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/28/ricin-letters-elvis-impersonator-mississippi/2117451/
</link>
  <description>What looked at first like classic terrorism -- poisoned letters sent to the president and other public officials -- now seems more likely to be the product of a local feud.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lindsay Lohan tweets: 'Its official. Pregnant...'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/02/lindsay-lohan-tweets-its-official-pregnant/2045179/
</link>
  <description>Was it an April Fool's joke? Perpetually unpredictable Lindsay Lohan, who made news yesterday by spilling out of her dress while getting out of a helicopter in Brazil, is making more news today.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 07:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Few Chechen immigrants make it to U.S.</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/chechens-immigrants-us-population/2097065/
</link>
  <description>There are probably fewer than about 200 Chechen immigrants in the United States, and most of them are settled in the Boston area, as many U.S. cities have refused to accept asylum applicants from the war-torn</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 14:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Nicki Minaj bares breasts in 'double nip slip'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/03/22/nicki-minaj-bares-breasts-in-double-nip-slip/2009781/
</link>
  <description>Nicki Minaj bares her breasts in behind-the-scenes video.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 13 12:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>N. Korea urges foreigners in S. Korea to evacuate</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/09/korean-factories-tension/2066073/
</link>
  <description>North Korea warns foreigners to leave South Korea to avoid harm in the event of war, and closes the joint industrial zone that had remained the only functioning example of cross-border cooperation on the peninsula.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 00:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Obama to return 5% of salary because of sequester</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/03/obama-salary-furlough-hagel/2050121/
</link>
  <description>President Obama plans to return 5% of his salary in response to federal workers who are going to be furloughed, an official said Wednesday. The decision comes a day after a similar move by Defense Secretary</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 14:53:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ron Paul slams Boston police response to blasts</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/onpolitics/2013/04/29/boston-bombings-manhunt-paul-patrick/2121727/
</link>
  <description>Former congressman Ron Paul was no fan of the police presence and manhunt in the Boston Marathon bombings.  The libertarian-thinking Republican slammed what he called the </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Teen in fear after paper shows him as bombing suspect</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/teen-portrayed-bombing-suspect/2095259/
</link>
  <description>REVERE, Mass. (AP) — A teenager said he is scared to go outside after he was portrayed on the Internet and on the front page of the New York Post as connected to the Boston Marathon bombings.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 21:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bombing suspects' mother says her faith deepened</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/28/mother-bomb-suspects-faith/2119685/
</link>
  <description>Zubeidat Tsarnaeva has drawn increased attention after a wiretap revealed she discussed jihad with her son.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 19:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Security incidents reported at LaGuardia, Boston Logan</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/todayinthesky/2013/04/16/security-incidents-reported-at-laguardia-boston-logan/2087587/
</link>
  <description>A US Airways flight is at the center of an undetermined security incident, according to CBS Boston and other local media reports out of Boston.  The flight in question is US Airways Flight 1716, which arrived</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 11:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Peyton Manning pranks Eric Decker with phony bill</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/10/peyton-manning-pranks-eric-decker-phony-practice-bill/2072833/
</link>
  <description>Peyton Manning might be all business on the field, but the man knows a good prank. The Denver Broncos quarterback worked out at Duke with new teammate Wes Welker and Eric Decker on Wednesday. And it looks like</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 23:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>New drug gives growth to girl born with no bones</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/22/girl-without-bones-drug-therapy/2102683/
</link>
  <description>NASHVILLE -- Born with the most severe form of hypophosphatasia -- a genetic disorder that prevents skeletal mineralization -- Janelly Martinez-Amador  didn't have the ribs to support breathing. Her parents, Salvador Martinez and Janet Amador of Antioch, were facing the prospect of having to decide whether to continue life-sustaining interventions.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 07:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Could four gay NFL players come out at same time?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/05/brendon-ayanbadejo-gay-nfl-players-four/2056205/
</link>
  <description>Brendon Ayanbadejo says it's a possibility.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 13 11:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Reports conflict on North Korea's nuclear capabilities</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/11/obama-north-korea-belligerent/2075493/
</link>
  <description>President Obama raised concerns on Thursday about North Korea's </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 17:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Another Carnival cruise ship loses power at sea</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/cruiselog/2013/04/18/carnival-cruise-ship-power-loss/2092793/
</link>
  <description>Another Carnival cruise ship has experienced a power failure at sea, albeit a brief one, a Florida news outlet is reporting.  Orlando's News 13 says the 2,052-passenger Carnival Ecstasy lost power late</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 07:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>6 keyboard shortcuts every computer user must know</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/columnist/komando/2013/04/12/keyboard-shortcuts-mac-pc/2063483/
</link>
  <description>Get in the habit of using these shortcuts, and your mouse will soon start collecting dust!</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>World's most beautiful airports</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2013/04/07/worlds-most-beautiful-airports/2056899/
</link>
  <description>As the gateway to a city or country, airports are often striking works of architecture. Here are ten of the best from around the world.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Berlin airport fiasco an embarrassment for Germans</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/todayinthesky/2013/04/08/berlin-airport-fiasco-an-embarrassment-for-germans/2062533/
</link>
  <description>By KIRSTEN GRIESHABER Associated Press BERLIN (AP) - Rabbits scamper over quiet runways. Only the call of a crow disturbs the silence around a gleaming, empty terminal that should be humming with the din of</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 21:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Hubble captures preview of comet that could upstage moon</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/sciencefair/2013/04/23/hubble-ison-comet/2107177/
</link>
  <description>A comet headed for a starring role in the nighttime sky later this year has gotten a sneak peek from NASA's Hubble space telescope</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 15:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Obama provides comfort in Boston:  'You will run again'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/18/boston-marathon-bombings-obama-interfaith-service/2092901/
</link>
  <description>President Obama spoke at an interfaith service dedicated to victims of the Boston Marathon bombings.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 08:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>S. Korea denies reports of N. Korea nuke test</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/08/north-korea-missle-test/2062333/
</link>
  <description>Military and government officials in South Korea denied earlier reports Monday that Seoul had detected signs North Korea was preparing for an imminent nuclear arms test.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 00:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Save Our Shows: Comedies need dramatic help</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/03/31/save-our-shows-survey/2035709/
</link>
  <description>They make up more than half of the shows on the bubble this year.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 13 20:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Veronica Roth 'Divergent' video reveal: Book 3 is ...</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/books/2013/04/17/veronica-roth-divergent-reveal-video/2091139/
</link>
  <description>'Divergent' author Veronica Roth reveals the title of the final book in the series.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 23:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'American Idol' Top 6 performance night: The live blog</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/idolchatter/2013/04/10/american-idol-top-6-performances-live-blog/2072351/
</link>
  <description>The remaining finalists get two songs each tonight.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 18:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bible Belt loves the message from 'Duck Dynasty' clan</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/28/duck-dynasty-bible-belt-message/2119495/
</link>
  <description>NASHVILLE, Tenn. -- Members of Duck Dynasty's Robertson family go on the road to spread hunting tips and their brand of </description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 17:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Fighter jets part of increased U.S. focus on Korea</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/01/north-korea-south-korea-tension/2041441/
</link>
  <description>The arrival in South Korea of two F-22 fighter jets, the world's most advanced warplanes, is a showy display of the American commitment to confronting North Korea.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 01:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Temporary celebrity Spike Albrecht spits game at Kate Upton</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/09/spike-albrecht-michigan-wolverines-kate-upton-tweet/2067305/
</link>
  <description>He gets an A+ for effort.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Marijuana's celebrity stigma goes up in smoke</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/02/rihanna-gaga-bieber-celebrity-pot-smoking/2015633/
</link>
  <description>Young stars are acknowledging, if not celebrating, their cannabis consumption.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 19:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Photo of suspect leaving scene of Boston Marathon emerges</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/19/fla-runner-gets-photo-of-suspect-fleeing-marathon/2097521/
</link>
  <description>JACKSONVILLE BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Seconds after the Boston Marathon bombs exploded, David Green pulled out his smartphone and took a photo of the chaos developing a couple hundred yards in front of him — the</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 16:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Duchess Kate's pregnancy more visible than ever today</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/21/duchess-kates-pregnancy-more-visible-than-ever-today/2096939/
</link>
  <description>Duchess Kate's pregnancy stands out at Windsor Castle.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 12:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Gold prices dive 5% to $1,487 an ounce</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/markets/2013/04/12/gold-prices-plummet-below-1500-ounce/2077545/
</link>
  <description>The price of gold plummeted Friday to its lowest level in nearly three years as economists grew increasingly worried about the economy's forward momentum heading into spring.  Precious metal investors appear</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 12:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Senators reach deal on gun background checks</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2013/04/10/guns-background-checks-senate-manchin-toomey/2070099/
</link>
  <description>A bipartisan agreement was reached to expand background checks for gun purchases. The deal would treat purchases made at gun shows and online essentially the same as those made at stores.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 13 09:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Mock draft 4.0: Will Geno Smith go in top 10 picks?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/16/nfl-mock-draft-geno-smith-luke-joeckel-eric-fisher/2086961/
</link>
  <description>In our latest Round 1 forecast, the scenario surrounding West Virginia passer might surprise you.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 03:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Alleged carjack victim tells of Boston suspects</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/22/carjacking-cambridge-marathon-bombers/2104145/
</link>
  <description>The complaint against Boston Marathon bombing suspect Dzhokhar Tsarnaev includes a chilling account from an unidentified man who says he was carjacked by the Tsarnaev brothers in Cambridge, Mass.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 16:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ten retailers urged to pull potentially toxic products</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/09/retailers-products-toxic-chemicals/2067113/
</link>
  <description>Health and environmental groups will launch a national campaign Thursday to prod 10 major retailers -- including Walmart, Target and Costco -- to clear store shelves of products with hazardous chemicals.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 18:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Zimmerman waives pre-trial immunity hearing</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/30/trayvon-martin-zimmerman-self-defense-hearing/2122991/
</link>
  <description>The man charged with murdering Trayvon Martin waived his right to a pre-trial self-defense immunity hearing during a Tuesday morning court appearance in Sanford, Fla.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 13 07:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Rihanna lets loose after latest Chris Brown breakup</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/09/rihanna-lets-loose-after-latest-chris-brown-breakup/2067565/
</link>
  <description>Yes, Rihanna and Chris Brown are supposedly over and done with. Again.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 14:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Facebook Home interface unveiled for Android</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/04/04/live-coverage-facebook-android/2052751/
</link>
  <description>Facebook hosting event where they may reveal new smartphone.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 11:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Dish Network makes $25.5B bid for Sprint</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/15/dish-sprint-nextel-bid/2083523/
</link>
  <description>Dish Network said Monday that it wants to buy Sprint Nextel for $25.5 billion, the largest acquisition proposal for a U.S. technology company this year that pits the offer against another from Japan's Softbank.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 06:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Talk of Brittney Griner in NBA sparks debate</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaaw/2013/04/03/brittney-griner-mark-cuban-nba-draft/2051599/
</link>
  <description>Nancy Lieberman, Ann Meyers Drysdale and Lynette Woodard discuss Baylor forward Brittney Griner's prospects for the NBA.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 21:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Second-round mock draft: Where do Manti Te'o and the quarterbacks go?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/26/second-round-2-mock-draft/2115423/
</link>
  <description>Round 1 of the 2013 NFL draft is now etched in stone. But USA TODAY Sports will break out the chisel again to carve out a Round 2 mock draft before the event resumes Friday night. 33. Jacksonville Jaguars — QB</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 11:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Mortgage rates fall, 15-year fixed at record</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/25/15-year-mortgage-rate-record-low/2112351/
</link>
  <description>Average rate on 15-year fixed mortgage hit record low 2.61%; 30-year fixed down to 3.4%</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 11:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Dolphins shake up NFL draft by picking Dion Jordan</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/dolphins/2013/04/25/miami-dolphins-dion-jordan/2114617/
</link>
  <description>NEW YORK – Miami Dolphins general manager Jeff Ireland pulled the first stunner of the 2013 NFL draft. Ireland traded up nine spots from No. 12 to the third overall slot, giving the Oakland Raiders Miami's</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 22:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Another juror released from Jodi Arias murder trial</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/12/juror-released-arias-trial/2079253/
</link>
  <description>PHOENIX (AP) — A juror was released Friday from the high-profile Jodi Arias murder trial, the second jury member to be dismissed this month.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 13 20:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Mom: Teen kills herself after rape, bullying</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/09/mom-teen-suicide-rape-bullying/2069243/
</link>
  <description>HALIFAX, Nova Scotia (AP) — A grieving Canadian mother said Tuesday her daughter hanged herself after she never recovered from an alleged rape by four teenage boys that left her deeply depressed and bullied in</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 20:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Gabby Giffords on Senate gun vote: 'I'm furious'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/onpolitics/2013/04/18/giffords-guns-senate-background-checks/2093001/
</link>
  <description>Gabrielle Giffords is angry, too.  In an emotional op-ed column for The New York Times, the former congresswoman and now gun control advocate blasted the U.S. Senate for rejecting a proposal to expand</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 09:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Ancient creature mixed human, apelike traits</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/04/11/ancient-creature-traits/2075105/
</link>
  <description>Scientists have gained new insights into an extinct South African creature with an intriguing mix of human and apelike traits, and apparently an unusual way of walking.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 15:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>TMZ: Nicole Eggert hospitalized after 'Splash' dive</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/19/nicole-eggert-splash-hospitalized/2097845/
</link>
  <description>The 'Baywatch' star botched her dive with a back-flop.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 17:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>April Fools' Day at the White House</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/theoval/2013/04/01/obama-white-house-kid-president-april-fools-day/2042169/
</link>
  <description>Everybody's getting into the April Fool's act, even the White House</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 12:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Faith Hill: No more 'Sunday Night Football' song</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/15/faith-hill-done-sunday-night-football-song-nbc/2084497/
</link>
  <description></description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 12:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Police: Boys sexually battered girl who hanged herself</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/11/teens-charged-girl-suicide/2076275/
</link>
  <description>Attorneys say students shared photos of the attack on their cellphones.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 21:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Fuming Brad Keselowski sounds off after NRA 500</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nascar/2013/04/14/brad-keselowski-nra-500-penske-penalties/2081187/
</link>
  <description>An angry Brad Keselowski accused NASCAR of unfairly targeting his Penske Racing team after Saturday night's NRA 500 in Texas.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 13 00:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Arrest in kidnapping of L.A. girl who was found hours later</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/01/los-angeles-girl-kidnapping-arrest/2043657/
</link>
  <description>Los Angeles police have made an arrest in the kidnapping of a 10-year-old girl from her home last week, a department spokeswoman says.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 13 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2013 NFL draft: Round 6 picks</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/26/2013-nfl-draft-sixth-round-6-selections/2116371/
</link>
  <description>Check out all the selections from Round 6 in the 2013 NFL draft.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Game over for LucasArts studio</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/gaming/2013/04/03/disney-lucasarts-closing-star-wars/2050055/
</link>
  <description>Disney has confirmed it will shut down the beloved game studio LucasArts in favor of a licensing model leveraging the popular Star Wars brand and other properties.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 14:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Cut salt, add potassium, live longer, researchers say</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/04/salt-blood-pressure/2053687/
</link>
  <description>Decrease salt, increase potassium intake to reduce blood pressure and improve health. But the Salt Institute begs to differ.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Newtown couple shocked again at Boston Marathon</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/15/boston-marathon-newtown-connection/2086669/
</link>
  <description>Ed and Valerie Lucas, from Newtown, Conn., had looked forward to being part of the Boston Marathon, where people support one another and share good feelings.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 23:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Why is Justin Bieber acting...well, strange?</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/25/why-is-justin-bieber-acting-well-strange/2086007/
</link>
  <description>Growing up and being a superstar: Everyone watching as Bieber tries to figure it all out.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 13 12:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Zagat picks the USA's most iconic restaurants</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/destinations/2013/04/02/zagat-iconic-restaurants/2044301/
</link>
  <description>Restaurant and online publisher Zagat picks iconic restaurants in 15 U.S. cities for USA TODAY's business travelers.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 09:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Brennan: Administrators fail Rutgers University</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/columnist/brennan/2013/04/03/brennan-rutgers-coach-mike-rice-fired/2049063/
</link>
  <description>Rutgers, of all universities, should have known better. Rutgers should have known that a coach who fires basketballs at the heads of his players and assaults them at practice should not keep his job. The so-called leaders of Rutgers University should have known that if a coach is hurling homophobic and misogynistic insults at his male players, he shouldn't be allowed to represent the school for one more hour, much less four more months.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 10:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Classmates: Bombing suspect was pot-smoking party boy</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/23/tsarnaev-umass-boston-marathon-bombings/2107813/
</link>
  <description>Students at the UMass dorm where one of the Boston Marathon bombers lived say he was not a frightening figure at all - in fact, he liked to party with them</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 19:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Adam Scott wins Masters, the first for Australia</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2013/04/14/adam-scott-beats-angel-cabrera-wins-masters/2082587/
</link>
  <description>AUGUSTA, Ga. — Carrying the weight of an entire continent on his back and hauling around the burden of expectation for years hasn't been easy at times for Adam Scott of Australia.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 13 19:38:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Report: Auburn paid players, altered grades under Gene Chizik</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaaf/2013/04/03/ncaa-football-auburn-violations-gene-chizik/2051041/
</link>
  <description>Report alleges Auburn's program paid players, altered grades and violated recruiting rules.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 18:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Magnitude-7.8 quake hits Iran, Pakistan; dozens killed</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2013/04/16/earthquake-iran-pakistan/2087047/
</link>
  <description>Seismologists say a major earthquake has struck a region near the Iran-Pakistan border.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 07:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bill Clinton tweets with Stephen Colbert's help</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/onpolitics/2013/04/09/bill-clinton-twitter-stephen-colbert/2066463/
</link>
  <description>Look out Twitterverse: Bill Clinton is now among you, sharing his thoughts in 140 characters or less.  Comedy Central host Stephen Colbert helped the former president set up his own Twitter account, complete</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 09:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Rush rules Rock and Roll Hall of Fame induction</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/music/2013/04/19/rock-and-roll-hall-of-fame-induction-ceremony/2095627/
</link>
  <description>Rush was the crowd-pleaser at Thursday's Rock and Roll Hall of Fame induction ceremony  that also ushered in Heart, Randy Newman, Public Enemy, Donna Summer, Albert King, Quincy Jones and Lou Adler.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 13 06:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bell: Geno Smith the latest to pay the black tax</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/21/bell-geno-smith-racial-bias/2101977/
</link>
  <description>Not a student of the game. Not committed or focused. Marginal work ethic. When a Pro Football Weekly scouting report on West Virginia quarterback Geno Smith surfaced recently, containing  damning proclamations</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 20:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2013 NFL draft: Round 5 picks</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/04/26/2013-nfl-draft-fifth-round-5-selections/2116385/
</link>
  <description>See all the selections made in the fifth round of the 2013 NFL draft.</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 13 16:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Young U.S. diplomat mourned as 'bright and brave'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/07/diplomat-killed-afghanistan/2060845/
</link>
  <description>A 25-year-old foreign service officer from suburban Chicago who was among five Americans killed in an explosion in southern Afghanistan was being remembered Sunday as </description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 13 14:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Report: Carnival Triumph damaged again in repair yard</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/cruises/2013/04/03/carnival-triumph-breaks-loose-alabama/2050455/
</link>
  <description>The fire-damaged Carnival Triumph reportedly suffered additonal damage today when it broke free from its moorings at the Alabama shipyard where it is under repair. The Mobile Press-Register reports that there</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 13 16:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Hostess reopens bakeries for Twinkies, Ho Hos</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/29/hostess-bakeries-indiana-illinois/2121559/
</link>
  <description>The new Hostess Brands said Monday that it will open bakeries in Indiana and Illinois, following announcements last week that it will reopen bakeries in Georgia and Kansas in its effort to bring back some of its snack brands.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 13:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Double up: Diet, exercise together are key to success</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/21/diet-and-exercise-together/2097229/
</link>
  <description>People who tackle diet and exercise at the same time do better at making healthy changes, according to a new study.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 13 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'Family Guy' creator condemns bomb-clip mashup</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2013/04/16/seth-macfarlane-family-guy-hoax/2088869/
</link>
  <description>Family Guy creator Seth MacFarlane is speaking out against an edited mash-up of show clips that suggest a prediction of Monday's Boston Marathon bombing.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 19:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>George Jones' funeral will be open to the public</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/music/2013/04/28/george-jones-funeral-open-to-the-public/2119683/
</link>
  <description>The funeral for country singer George Jones, who died Friday morning at age 81, will take place Thursday at the Grand Ole Opry House in Nashville, and will be open to the public.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 13 18:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Brent Celek: Chip Kelly's system is 'insane'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/eagles/2013/04/17/eagles-chip-kelly-innovations/2091631/
</link>
  <description>PHILADELPHIA – Eagles tight end Brent Celek gushed after his second minicamp practice working new coach Chip Kelly's system. Compared to coach Andy Reid's cumbersome West Coast verbiage, Celek believes he is</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 17:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Snow, other wild wintry weather springs up</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/weather/2013/04/09/winter-storm-blizzard-tornadoes/2066639/
</link>
  <description>A ferocious storm is dumping heavy snow across portions of the Rockies and northern Plains Tuesday. Winter storm warnings are in effect from New Mexico to Wisconsin.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 13 10:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bribery probe snares NYC Democrat seeking mayor's seat</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/02/ny-politicians-arrested/2045609/
</link>
  <description>A New York state lawmaker was arrested along with several other politicians in an alleged plot to bribe his way into the race for mayor of New York City.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 13 10:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jay-Z answers Cuba critics in 'Open Letter'</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/11/jay-z-answers-cuba-critics-in-open-letter/2073577/
</link>
  <description>Jay-Z answers Cuba critics in 'Open Letter.'</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 10:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lawmakers question Beyonce and Jay-Z's Cuba trip</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/08/lawmakers-question-beyonce-and-jay-zs-cuba-trip/2062471/
</link>
  <description>Two Republican members of Congress are wondering why the superstars were allowed to travel to Cuba.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 13 07:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Jennifer Aniston sports short shorts</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/17/jennifer-aniston-short-shorts-call-me-crazy-premiere/2089921/
</link>
  <description>It's nice to see Jennifer Aniston back on a red carpet.  She stepped out in a summery black shorts outfit to promote 'Call Me Crazy.'</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 07:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bombing victim Krystle Campbell remembered, honored</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/16/boston-marathon-bombing-victims/2087777/
</link>
  <description>She had worked as a manager at Jimmy's Steer House in Arlington, Mass., only a short while but 29-year-old Krystle Campbell had left an impression.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 13 16:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>NBA player Jason Collins comes out as a gay man</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nba/2013/04/29/jason-collins-gay-athlete/2121127/
</link>
  <description>Jason Collins, a 12-year NBA veteran, is the first male athlete in a major American team sport to come out as a gay.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 13 12:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Cloning takes California's ancient redwood trees abroad</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/22/redwood-trees-climate-change-environment/2102667/
</link>
  <description>California's mighty redwoods are going international, cloned in an effort to promote reforestation and deal with climate change.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 13 07:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Chaz Bono continues to slim down</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/23/chaz-bono-continues-to-slim-down/2105689/
</link>
  <description>In February, Dancing With the Stars alum Chaz Bono revealed he had lost more than 40 pounds.  Over the weekend, he showed off an even slimmer shape at the GLAAD Awards in Los Angeles.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 07:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Lindsey Vonn and Tiger Woods have matching Masters outfits</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/14/lindsey-vonn-tiger-woods-matching-sunday-red-outfits/2082051/
</link>
  <description>Call her a traditionalist.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 13 15:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Chevy Cruze diesel: 46 highway mpg, but only 27 in town</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2013/04/18/chevrolet-diesel-cruze-volkswagen-jetta-tdi-mpg/2091633/
</link>
  <description>Chevrolet says the diesel version of its Cruze compact sedan will be rated by the government at 46 miles per gallon on the highway, the best of any non-hybrid car.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 13 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>'American Idol': Oh, yes, it's ladies' night</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/idolchatter/2013/04/17/american-idol-top-5-ladies-night-live-blog/2091885/
</link>
  <description>The girls get a 'Divas' theme and pick songs from the years they were born.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 13 19:24:46 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Justices decline N.Y. case restricting guns in public</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/15/supreme-court-guns-new-york-law/2083907/
</link>
  <description>The Supreme Court on Monday declined to consider whether the Second Amendment protects the right to carry a gun outside the home.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 10:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Gwyneth Paltrow says she lights up once a week</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2013/04/11/gwyneth-paltrow-says-she-lights-up-once-a-week/2074149/
</link>
  <description>The single light American Spirit is her guilty pleasure.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 13 12:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Photo tour: Best all-inclusive resorts in the Caribbean</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/hotels/2013/04/24/all-inclusive-resorts-caribbean/2106411/
</link>
  <description>Oyster.com has visited dozens of all-inclusive resorts in the Caribbean, and while it's not easy to single just one out, here's a list of our very favorites, from a secluded spot on gorgeous Turks and Caicos</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 08:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Bubba Watson is no fan of viewers calling in violations</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2013/04/13/masters-bubba-watson-tiger-woods-violations/2080421/
</link>
  <description>Watson had his own stories about callers accusing him of breaking a rule.</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 13 14:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Samsung Galaxy S4  is loaded with gee whiz features</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/columnist/baig/2013/04/24/samsung-galaxy-s4-review/2104959/
</link>
  <description>With its Galaxy smartphone franchise, Samsung has emerged as Apple's chief rival in the smartphone space.</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 13 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>2nd child of Pa. couple dies after only praying</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2013/04/23/child-pa-dies-praying/2106457/
</link>
  <description>Couple is already on probation for the death one son after they chose to prayer instead of a doctor.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 13 12:37:19 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>Obama praises Calif. AG's looks</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/theoval/2013/04/04/obama-california-kamala-harris/2054131/
</link>
  <description>We can't help but wonder what the first lady is going to think of this. At a fundraiser Thursday in California, President Obama had nothing but praise for state Attorney General Kamala Harris -- including her</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 13 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
</item>


<item>
  <title>11 reasons Jack Nicklaus is better than Tiger Woods</title>
  <link>http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2013/04/15/tiger-woods-jack-nicklaus-comparison/2083049/
</link>
  <description>Things may change, but the Golden Bear beats Tiger for now.</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 13 11:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
